<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<results>
  <result author="Daniel Zeman">Pravděpodobnostní model významových zápisů vět</result>
  <result author="Jan Hajič">Syntax v českém národním korpusu</result>
  <result author="Daniel Zeman">A Statistical Approach to Parsing of Czech</result>
  <result author="Petr Sgall">Valency and underlying structure: An alternative view on dependency</result>
  <result author="Geert-Jan M. Kruijff">Clarendon Press/Oxford Science Publications, 1996. ISBN 0-19-853833-2</result>
  <result author="Petr Sgall">Teorie valence a její formální zpracování</result>
  <result author="Kiril Ribarov">Living Conservation of the Lexis of Old Church Slavonic</result>
  <result author="Alevtina Bémová">Modelling Lexical Resources in KPML for Generating Instructions in Slavic languages</result>
  <result author="Eva Hajičová">Focus, Topic, and Semantics</result>
  <result author="Ivana Kruijffová">Specification of grammatical resources for the Initial Demonstrator</result>
  <result author="Jarmila Panevová">Ellipsis and zero elements in the structure of the sentence</result>
  <result author="Petr Sgall">K poznámce O. Uličného v ČJL 1998, č. 1-2</result>
  <result author="Jarmila Panevová">New Prague School Publications</result>
  <result author="Petr Sgall">Problems of Dialogue Research in Spoken Czech</result>
  <result author="Jan Hajič">Core Natural Language Technology Applicable to Multiple Languages, Workshop ´98 Final Report</result>
  <result author="Petr Sgall">Revisiting the Classification of the Dependents. Interesting Results and Tempting Topics for Further Research</result>
  <result author="Petr Sgall">Structure, meaning and use</result>
  <result author="Jarmila Panevová">Úvahy nad novou Skladbou češtiny M. Grepla a P. Karlíka. I</result>
  <result author="Jan Hajič">Tagging Inflective Languages: Prediction of Morphological Categories for a Rich, Structured Tagset</result>
  <result author="Petr Sgall">Věta, kontext a slovosled</result>
  <result author="Jarmila Panevová">Ještě k teorii valence</result>
  <result author="Petr Sgall">Functionalism in Czech Linguistics and in the World</result>
  <result author="Geert-Jan M. Kruijff">Basic dependency-based grammar</result>
  <result author="Jarmila Panevová">Verbal Categories, Meaning and Typology</result>
  <result author="Petr Sgall">Word, sentence, and discourse</result>
  <result author="Vladislav Kuboň">Two Useful Measures of Word Order Complexity</result>
  <result author="Eva Hajičová">The ordering of valency slots from a communicative point of view</result>
  <result author="Jan Hajič">Building a Syntactically Annotated Corpus: The Prague Dependency Treebank</result>
  <result author="Jarmila Panevová">K asymetrii mezi rovinami jazykového systému</result>
  <result author="Eva Hajičová">Prague Dependency Treebank: From analytic to tectogrammatical annotations</result>
  <result author="Jarmila Panevová">Language Resources Need Annotations To Make Them Really Reusable: The Prague Dependency Treebank</result>
  <result author="Barbora Vidová Hladká">PoS tags for automatic tagging and syntactic structures</result>
  <result author="Ivana Kruijffová">Topic-Focus Articulation and the Dynamics of Discourse Representation</result>
  <result author="Eva Hajičová">Salience in dialogues</result>
  <result author="Jan Hajič">Czech Language Processing – PoS Tagging</result>
  <result author="Eva Hajičová">Oldřich Leška`s seventieth birthday</result>
  <result author="Geert-Jan M. Kruijff">Proceedings of the ESSLLI Third Student Session (editors)</result>
  <result author="Romana Králíková">Tagging of Parallel Corpora</result>
  <result author="Jarmila Panevová">Ještě k teorii valence - tentokrát na materiálu českých adjektiv primárních</result>
  <result author="Geert-Jan M. Kruijff">Kluwer Academic Press, Dordrecht, the Netherlands, 1997. ISBN 079234345x</result>
  <result author="Petr Sgall">The Micro and the Macro of Linguistic Description</result>
  <result author="Ivana Kruijffová">Automatic Generation of Instructions in a Multilingual Environment</result>
  <result author="Ivana Kruijffová">Grammatical Resource Implementation for for Bulgarian, Czech and Russian</result>
  <result author="Petr Sgall">Český pohled na dějiny lingvistiky</result>
  <result author="Ivana Kruijffová">Generation of simple text structures in Bulgarian, Czech and Russian</result>
  <result author="Petr Sgall">Meaning and "propositional attitudes"</result>
  <result author="Petr Sgall">Remarks on Parsing Written and Spoken Discourse</result>
  <result author="Jiří Hana">Lexical-morphological specifications and resources grant Evropske unie v ramci programu INCO-Copernicus a jeho cislo je PL961104</result>
  <result author="Eva Hajičová">Šestnáctý kongres lingvistů</result>
  <result author="Jan Hajič">Core Natural Language Processing Technology Applicable to Multiple Languages</result>
  <result author="Eva Hajičová">Movement rules revisited</result>
  <result author="Geert-Jan M. Kruijff">Discerning Relevance in Discourse Using TFA</result>
  <result author="Markéta Straňáková-Lopatková">Ambiguity in Czech Sentences, Its Classification and Searching for It</result>
  <result author="Jarmila Panevová">Koreference v gramatice a v textu (nutnost strukturního popisu a jeho hranice)</result>
  <result author="Alevtina Bémová">Tagging and analysis of instructional texts in the software domain</result>
  <result author="Eva Hajičová">Jarmila Panevová's anniversary</result>
  <result author="Petr Sgall">Neochuzujme spisovnou češtinu</result>
  <result author="Petr Sgall">Věta, promluva a slovosled</result>
  <result author="Ivana Kruijffová">The Dynamic Potential of Topic and Focus: A Praguian Approach to Discourse Represemtation Theory</result>
  <result author="Eva Hajičová">Topic-focus articulation, tripartite structures, and semantic content</result>
  <result author="Geert-Jan M. Kruijff">Proceedings of the Joint Conference on Formal Grammar, Head-driven Phrase Structure Grammar, and Categorial Grammar (editors)</result>
  <result author="Petr Sgall">Introduction</result>
  <result author="Martin Čmejrek">Automatic Translation Lexicon Extraction from Czech-English Parallel Texts</result>
  <result author="Geert-Jan M. Kruijff">Robustness in Tabular Deduction for Multimodal Logical Grammar - Part 1</result>
  <result author="Alena Böhmová">The Prague Dependency Treebank I; How Much of the Underlying Syntactic Structure Can Be Tagged Automatically?</result>
  <result author="Petr Sgall">Na gymnáziu za války (a potom v Praze)</result>
  <result author="Geert-Jan M. Kruijff">Dordrecht, Netherlands, 1997, ISBN 0-7923-4446-4, 466p</result>
  <result author="Geert-Jan M. Kruijff">Implementation Tabular Deduction for Multimodal Logical Grammar</result>
  <result author="Petr Sgall">Čekající možnosti a číhající propasti</result>
  <result author="Petr Sgall">Sbližování spisovné a obecné češtiny</result>
  <result author="Petr Sgall">D. G. Hays o předstupních civilizace</result>
  <result author="Jarmila Panevová">Some Types of Syntactic Ambiguity; How to Treat Them in an Automatic Procedure</result>
  <result author="Jan Hajič">Large Vocabulary Speech Recognition for Read and Broadcast Czech</result>
  <result author="Petr Sgall">Prague School Typology</result>
  <result author="Petr Sgall">Remarks on Sentence Prosody and Topic-Focus Articulation</result>
  <result author="Pavel Květoň">A maximum entropy approach to the natural language modeling</result>
  <result author="Petr Sgall">Proměny hovorové češtiny a škola</result>
  <result author="Petr Sgall">Lingvistika a zákon schválnosti</result>
  <result author="Jan Hajič">A Statistical Parser for Czech</result>
  <result author="Petr Sgall">Závislostní gramatika a slovosled v češtině a v analytických jazycích</result>
  <result author="Petr Sgall">The Archimedes Problem</result>
  <result author="Eva Hajičová">Silver Medal of Charles University to John Benjamins</result>
  <result author="Geert-Jan M. Kruijff">Text Structuring in a Multilingual System for Generation of Instructions</result>
  <result author="Eva Hajičová">Aktuální členění věty a výstavba promluvy</result>
  <result author="Petr Sgall">Issues of Colloquial and Standard Czech</result>
  <result author="Jan Hajič">Word Sense Disambiguation of Czech Texts</result>
  <result author="Ivana Kruijffová">Issues of Valency and Meaning. Studies in Honour of Jarmila Panevová (ed. Eva Hajičová), 1998, 307 s</result>
  <result author="Alevtina Bémová">Morphological and Syntactic Tagging of the Prague Dependency Treebank</result>
  <result author="Jarmila Panevová">Valence a její univerzální a specifické projevy</result>
  <result author="Jan Hajič">The syntactic Tagging of Corpora: New Issues for Explicit Syntactic Description of Czech</result>
  <result author="Markéta Straňáková-Lopatková">Selected Types of Pg-Ambiguity.</result>
  <result author="Jarmila Panevová">Úvahy nad novou Skladbou češtiny M. Grepla a P. Karlíka. II</result>
  <result author="Petr Sgall">Nestát vývoji v cestě. Rozhovor připravil L. Kasal</result>
  <result author="Eva Hajičová">The Prague Dependency Treebank: Crossing the Sentence Boundary</result>
  <result author="Alena Böhmová">How Much of the Underlying Syntactic Structure Can Be Tagged Automatically?</result>
  <result author="Eva Hajičová">Prague Dependency Treebank: Restoration of Deletions</result>
  <result author="Petr Sgall">Types of languages and probabilistic implication laws</result>
  <result author="Geert-Jan M. Kruijff">Handling Word Order in a Multilingual System for Generation of Instructions</result>
  <result author="Jarmila Panevová">Syntactic Tagging: Procedure for the Transition from the Analytic to the Tectogrammatical Tree Structure</result>
  <result author="Nino Peterek">The experimental results from NSF Workshop'99 CLSP Johns Hopkins University. Part II.: Automatic Speech Recognition</result>
  <result author="Petr Sgall">Aktuální členění věty - jeho postavení v jazykovém systému a jeho význam pro překlad</result>
  <result author="Jarmila Panevová">Poznámky k valenci podstatných jmen</result>
  <result author="Petr Sgall">Od významové stavby k formální sémantice</result>
  <result author="Geert-Jan M. Kruijff">Contextually Appropriate Ordering of Nominal Expressions</result>
  <result author="Barbora Vidová Hladká">Corpus Linguistics - Investigating Language Structure and Use, Cambridge, 1998</result>
  <result author="Jan Hajič">Machine Translation of Very Close Languages</result>
  <result author="Petr Sgall">The Freedom of Language</result>
  <result author="Martin Holub">Use of Dependency Microcontexts in IR</result>
  <result author="Jarmila Panevová">Opisanije dvux tipov konversivnyx par</result>
  <result author="Ivana Kruijffová">Intonational Phonology. Cambridge University Press, 1996</result>
  <result author="Jarmila Panevová">Building an electronic language database nowadays: The Prague Dependency Treebank</result>
  <result author="Eva Hajičová">Dependency as a universal ingredient in syntactic theories</result>
  <result author="Jan Štěpánek">Knowledge, Language and Logic:Questions for Quine, Kluwer Academic Publishers Dordrecht/Boston/London</result>
  <result author="Jan Hajič">The Prague Dependency Treebank: A Three-Level Annotation Scenario</result>
  <result author="Ivana Kruijffová">Discourse Connectives, Inference and Information Structure</result>
  <result author="Eva Hajičová">Deletions and their reconstruction in tectogrammatical syntactic tagging of very large corpora</result>
  <result author="Jan Štěpánek">Formalism for a Description of Relations between Tectogrammatics and Morphemics</result>
  <result author="Jarmila Panevová">Počítačová lingvistika ve vztahu k informatice</result>
  <result author="Eva Hajičová">A TFA-Based Glance at Optimality Theory</result>
  <result author="Anoop Sarkar">Automatic Extraction of Subcategorization Frames for Czech</result>
  <result author="Ivana Kruijffová">Presuppositional Interpretation of Causal and Additive "although". Abstract</result>
  <result author="Barbora Vidová Hladká">Czech Language Tagging. PhD Thesis, UFAL, MFF UK</result>
  <result author="Jarmila Panevová">Funkoní styly a automatické zpracování jazyka</result>
  <result author="Ivana Kruijffová">Papers in Honour of Eva Hajičová (eds. B. H. Partee , P. Sgall; John Benjamins Publishing Company; Amsterdam/Philadelphia; 1995)</result>
  <result author="Eva Hajičová">Mysteries of Order</result>
  <result author="Jarmila Panevová">Coreference in Annotating a Large Corpus</result>
  <result author="Eva Hajičová">Dependency-Based Underlying-Structure Tagging of a Very Large Czech Corpus</result>
  <result author="Petr Sgall">Konvence v jazyku</result>
  <result author="Geert-Jan M. Kruijff">Flexible text structuring for the final prototype (documentation to the software). AGILE project deliverable Work Package 5: TEXM3-Cu, TEXM3-Ru, TEXM3-Bg</result>
  <result author="Petr Sgall">English Syntax in Functional Generative Description, Topic-focus articulation (information structure) of the sentence, Syntax and semantics</result>
  <result author="Jarmila Panevová">More Remarks on Control</result>
  <result author="Eva Hajičová">Item Ordering in the Sentence</result>
  <result author="Markéta Straňáková-Lopatková">Selected Types of Pg-ambiguity; Processing Based on Analysis by Reduction</result>
  <result author="Jiří Havelka">Lexical Semantics and Knowledge Representation in Multilingual Text Generation</result>
  <result author="Geert-Jan M. Kruijff">Processing as abduction+deduction: A sentence processing model</result>
  <result author="Petr Sgall">Remarks on the Semantics of the Focus</result>
  <result author="Eva Hajičová">Tagging of a very large corpora: Topic-Focus Articulation</result>
  <result author="Jan Hajič">Morpheme Based Language Models for Speech Recognition of Czech</result>
  <result author="Eva Hajičová">The International Scene</result>
  <result author="Geert-Jan M. Kruijff">Text Structuring Specification for the Final Prototype. AGILE project deliverable Work Package 5: TEXS3-Cu, TEXS3-Ru, TEXS3-Bg</result>
  <result author="Petr Sgall">Sémantika a pragmatika v jazycích různých typů</result>
  <result author="Petr Sgall">Jakobson entre l'Est et l'Ouest, 1915-1939</result>
  <result author="Geert-Jan M. Kruijff">Resources for multilingual text generation in three Slavic languages</result>
  <result author="Martin Holub">Context Information Mining I., Motivation and Syntactic Issues</result>
  <result author="Eva Hajičová">Výzkum syntaxe nad ČNK</result>
  <result author="Jarmila Panevová">Deminutivní substantiva v Českém národním korpusu a možnosti jejich automatického zpracování</result>
  <result author="Nino Peterek">Towards Language Independent Acoustic Modeling</result>
  <result author="Petr Sgall">On Comparison of Approaches</result>
  <result author="Petr Sgall">Sketches of Slavic Scholars</result>
  <result author="Ivana Kruijffová">Linguistic, Cognitive and Computational Perspectives</result>
  <result author="Kiril Ribarov">Stochastically-Based Semantic Analysis, Kluwer, 1999</result>
  <result author="Jarmila Panevová">Selected Types of Ambiguity of Prepositional Groups; Classification, Criteria and Method for Automatic Processing (Abstract)</result>
  <result author="Nino Peterek">Computer Analysis of Czech Speech and Prosody</result>
  <result author="Karel Oliva">The Linguistics Basis of a Rule-Based Tagger of Czech</result>
  <result author="Eva Hajičová">Evaluation of Tectogrammatical Annotation of PDT</result>
  <result author="Petr Sgall">Problémy mluvené češtiny v Praze</result>
  <result author="Geert-Jan M. Kruijff">A Multilingual System for Text Generation in Three Slavic Languages</result>
  <result author="Roman Ondruška">Syntactic Frames Extraction</result>
  <result author="Jarmila Panevová">A Manual for Tectogrammatical Tagging of the Prague Dependency Treebank</result>
  <result author="Daniel Zeman">Learning Verb Subcategorization from Corpora: Counting Frame Subsets</result>
  <result author="Eva Hajičová">Language Resources and Evaluation Conference in Granada: a View from Prague</result>
  <result author="Ivana Kruijffová">Evaluation of the Final Prototype. AGILE project deliverable Work Package 9:EVALI-Bu, EVALI-Cz, EVALI-Ru</result>
  <result author="Eva Hajičová">Semantico-Syntactic Tagging of Very Large Corpora: the Case of Restoration of Nodes on the Underlying Level</result>
  <result author="Veronika Řezníčková">Valency frames of nouns and adjectives from PDT point of view</result>
  <result author="Kiril Ribarov">Rule-Based Tagging: Morphological Tagsets versus Tagset of Analytical Functions</result>
  <result author="Ivana Kruijffová">recenze na:James D. McCawley: The Syntactic Phenomena of English (Second Edition). Chicago University Press</result>
  <result author="Jiří Havelka">Topic-Focus Articulation and Discourse Theories</result>
  <result author="Petr Sgall">Foundations of Computational Linguistics. Man-Machine Communication in Natural Language</result>
  <result author="Geert-Jan M. Kruijff">Generation of Contextually Appropriate Word Order</result>
  <result author="Jarmila Panevová">Actants and circonstants: Criteria for their determination</result>
  <result author="Geert-Jan M. Kruijff">Processing as abduction: A sentence processing model</result>
  <result author="Jarmila Panevová">A Semi-Automatic Resolution of Anaphora and Ellipsis in a Large Corpus of Czech</result>
  <result author="Geert-Jan M. Kruijff">Categories, Constructions, and Dependency Relations</result>
  <result author="Eva Hajičová">Focalizers and Their Status in the Topic/Focus Articulation of the Sentence</result>
  <result author="Geert-Jan M. Kruijff">Evaluation of the intermediate prototype. AGILE project deliverable Work Package 9:EVALI-Bu, EVALI-Cz, EVALI-Ru</result>
  <result author="Martin Holub">Use of Dependency Tree Structures for the Microcontext Extraction</result>
  <result author="Nino Peterek">Automatic speech recognition and prosody</result>
  <result author="Jan Hajič">Morphological Tagging: Data vs. Dictionaries</result>
  <result author="Eva Hajičová">A Praguian view on Optimality Theory</result>
  <result author="Jarmila Panevová">Větná skladba (z hlediska pojetí v osnovách různých vzdělávacích systémů)</result>
  <result author="Eva Hajičová">Dependency, Coordination, and Projectivity</result>
  <result author="Ivana Kruijffová">Language at work. Analyzing communication breakdown in the workplace to inform systems design. CSLI Lecture Notes Number 66</result>
  <result author="Martin Čmejrek">Statistical Modelling in Machine Translation - Segmentation of Parallel Texts</result>
  <result author="Geert-Jan M. Kruijff">Formal specification of full grammar models and Implementation of tactical generation resources for all three languages in a Finale Prototype. AGILE project deliverable Work Package 6: SPEC3-Bg, SPEC3</result>
  <result author="Eva Hajičová">How Many Topics/Foci</result>
  <result author="Jan Cuřín">The experimental results from NSF Workshop'99 CLSP Johns Hopkins University. Part I.: Czech/English Statistical Machine Translation</result>
  <result author="Petr Sgall">Jan Firbas, Functional sentence perspective in written and spoken communication</result>
  <result author="Eva Hajičová">Teorie optimality a aktuální členění věty</result>
  <result author="Ivana Kruijffová">Information Structure and the Interpretation of Discourse Connectives in English and Czech (Abstrac)</result>
  <result author="Kiril Ribarov">The (Un)Deterministic Nature of Morphological Context</result>
  <result author="Jan Hajič">Česílko - an MT system for closely related languages</result>
  <result author="Barbora Vidová Hladká">The Contex (not only) for Human</result>
  <result author="Geert-Jan M. Kruijff">Aggregation and Contextual Reference in Automatically Generated Instructions</result>
  <result author="Markéta Straňáková-Lopatková">Ambiguity of Prepositional Groups: Classification, Criteria and Method for Automatic Processing.</result>
  <result author="Markéta Straňáková-Lopatková">Homonymie předložkových skupin v češtině a možnost jejího automatického zpracování</result>
  <result author="Vladislav Kuboň">A Method of Accurate Robust Parsing for Czech</result>
  <result author="Vladislav Kuboň">Word-Order Relaxations &amp; Restrictions within a Dependency Grammar</result>
  <result author="Vladislav Kuboň">Problems of Robust Parsing of Czech</result>
  <result author="Petr Sgall">Aspect, Eventuality Types and Nominal Reference. Garland Publishing, New York - London 1999</result>
  <result author="Jan Hajič">Serial Combination of Rules and Statistics: A Case Study in Czech Tagging</result>
  <result author="Zdeněk Žabokrtský">How to Make Constrained Fuzzy Arithmetic Efficient</result>
  <result author="Eva Hajičová">The Current Status of the Prague Dependency Treebank</result>
  <result author="Markéta Straňáková-Lopatková">Enhancing the Valency Dictionary of Czech Verbs: Tectogrammatical Annotation</result>
  <result author="Jarmila Panevová">K možnému pojetí všeobecnosti aktantu</result>
  <result author="Daniel Zeman">Parsing with Regular Expressions: A Minute to Learn, a Lifetime to Master</result>
  <result author="Eva Hajičová">A reusable corpus needs syntactic annotations: Prague Dependency Treebank</result>
  <result author="Petr Sgall">Structural and Formal Linguistics in Prague (Preface)</result>
  <result author="Petr Sgall">A remark on Semantics and Pragmatics in Natural Language</result>
  <result author="Eva Hajičová">Topic-focus and salience</result>
  <result author="Markéta Straňáková-Lopatková">Ambiguity of Prepositional Groups and the Possibility of Its Automatic Processing.</result>
  <result author="Petr Sgall">Linguistics: Information Structure</result>
  <result author="Jarmila Panevová">Manuál pro tektogramatické značkování (III. verze, prosinec 2001)</result>
  <result author="Jarmila Panevová">Tectogrammatics in corpus tagging</result>
  <result author="Jiří Hana">The AGILE System</result>
  <result author="Eva Hajičová">Čeština a počítače (Abstrakt)</result>
  <result author="Jiří Havelka">Reference and Anaphoric Relations. Studies in Linguistics and Philosophy 72, Kluwer Academic Publishers: Dordrecht, The Netherlands. ISBN 0-7923-6070-2</result>
  <result author="Petr Sgall">On the interface between langue and parole (abstract)</result>
  <result author="Petr Sgall">Ohlédnutí pražského lingvisty za dvacátým stoletím</result>
  <result author="Jarmila Panevová">Building an Electronic Language Database Nowadays</result>
  <result author="Jarmila Panevová">Problémy reflexivního zájmena v češtině</result>
  <result author="Jan Hajič">Prague Dependency Treebank 1.0 (Final Production Label)</result>
  <result author="Eva Hajičová">Syntaktický výzkum nad Českým národním korpusem</result>
  <result author="Markéta Straňáková-Lopatková">Ambiguity Problems in Human-Computer Interaction</result>
  <result author="Martin Holub">MATES -- An Experimental Linguistic Database System</result>
  <result author="Jarmila Panevová">Zpráva o spolupráci Jazykovědného sdružení ČR s MŠMT ČR.</result>
  <result author="Markéta Straňáková-Lopatková">Některé typy syntaktické homonymie (z hlediska možnosti automatického zpracování)</result>
  <result author="Silvie Cinková">/Sýnihefti sagnorðabókar/: andere 
Betrachtungsweise der lexikographischen Bearbeitung der Verben</result>
  <result author="Jan Hajič">The Prague Dependency Treebank: Annotation Structure and Support</result>
  <result author="Petr Sgall">Pravdivost jako východisko sémantiky (Truth as a starting point of semantics)</result>
  <result author="Nino Peterek">Recent Methods of Prosody Analysis</result>
  <result author="Eva Hajičová">Possibilities and Limits of Optimality in Topic-Focus Articulation</result>
  <result author="Petr Sgall">Volnost jako univerzální vlastnost jazyka</result>
  <result author="Barbora Vidová Hladká">Corpus Linguistics. Investigating Language Structure and Use. Cambridge Approaches to Linguistics. Cambridge University Press: Cambridge 1998</result>
  <result author="Jarmila Panevová">Některé typy chyb ve stylu odborném a žurnalistickém a možnost jejich automatického odstranění</result>
  <result author="Vladislav Kuboň">A Method for Analyzing Clause Complexity</result>
  <result author="Petr Sgall">Bedeutung, Sinn und Bezeichnung</result>
  <result author="Jan Cuřín">Jak počítače umějí český jazyk</result>
  <result author="Ivona Kučerová">Teoretická lingvistika a statistické zpracování přirozeného jazyka</result>
  <result author="Jarmila Panevová">Upotreblenie glagoµnych vremen v nekotorych tipach složnopodčinennych predloženij (na materiale češskogo jazyka)</result>
  <result author="Jan Hajič">Statistické modelování a automatická analýza přirozeného jazyka (morfologie, syntax, překlad)</result>
  <result author="Jarmila Panevová">Valency Frames: Extension and Reexamination.</result>
  <result author="Zdeněk Žabokrtský">Representing Linguistic Hedges by L-Fuzzy Modifiers</result>
  <result author="Markéta Straňáková-Lopatková">Homonymie předložkových skupin a možnost jejího automatického zpracování</result>
  <result author="Alena Böhmová">Automatic Procedures in Tectogrammatical Tagging</result>
  <result author="Martin Čmejrek">Automatic Extraction of Terminological Lexicon from Czech-English Parallel Texts</result>
  <result author="Zdeněk Žabokrtský">Automatic Functor Assignment in the Prague Dependency Treebank</result>
  <result author="Jan Štěpánek">CD-ROM Prague Dependency Treebank 1.0. Institute of Formal and Applied Linguistics &amp; Linguistic Data Lab. Published by Linguistic Data Consortium, University of Pennsylvania.</result>
  <result author="Petr Sgall">Etničeskij jazyk. Opyt funkcional'noj differenciacii. Specimina philologiae Slavicae, vol.121, 1999.</result>
  <result author="Daniel Zeman">How Much Will a RE-based Preprocessor Help a Statistical Parser?</result>
  <result author="Eva Hajičová">Information Structure and Syntactic Complexity</result>
  <result author="Petr Sgall">Functional Generative Description, Word Order and Focus</result>
  <result author="Ivona Kučerová">Subjekt-predikátová shoda v češtine: univerzální, nebo specifická jazyková forma?</result>
  <result author="Jiří Hana">Manual for Morphological Annotation</result>
  <result author="Martin Holub">Word Frequency Distributions</result>
  <result author="Eva Hajičová">Argument/Valency Structure in PropBank, LCS Database and Prague Dependency Treebank: A Comparative Pilot Study</result>
  <result author="Petr Podveský">Finite-state machines in speech recognition</result>
  <result author="Petr Sgall">Underlying Structures in Annotating Czech National Corpus</result>
  <result author="Jarmila Panevová">řada hesel publikace</result>
  <result author="Barbora Vidová Hladká">Pražský závislostní korpus aneb Co tady před padesáti lety nebylo</result>
  <result author="Václav Honetschläger">Analytical and Tectogrammatical Syntactic Parsing</result>
  <result author="Łukasz Dębowski">Testing the Limits -- Adding a New Language to an MT System</result>
  <result author="Barbora Vidová Hladká">Exploring Textual Data</result>
  <result author="Petr Sgall">Recenze: Czech through Russian</result>
  <result author="Otakar Smrž">Sherds from an Arabic Treebanking Mosaic</result>
  <result author="Petr Sgall">The freedom of language</result>
  <result author="Petr Sgall">Spoken Czech revisited</result>
  <result author="Veronika Řezníčková">PDT: Two Steps in Tectogrammatical Annotation with respect to some Issues of Deletion</result>
  <result author="Kiril Ribarov">Old Sources and Modern Procedures: Computer Processing of Old-Church Slavonic</result>
  <result author="Otakar Smrž">Prague Dependency Treebank for Arabic: Multi-Level Annotation of Arabic Corpus</result>
  <result author="Markéta Pravdová">K povaze reklamního diskurzu</result>
  <result author="Markéta Straňáková-Lopatková">Valency Dictionary of Czech Verbs: Complex Tectogrammatical Annotation</result>
  <result author="Eva Hajičová">Dependency syntax in Functional Generative Desription</result>
  <result author="Eva Hajičová">Corpus Annotation on the Tectogrammatical Layer: Summarizing the First Stages of Evaluations</result>
  <result author="Jan Hajič">Natural Language Generation in the Context of Machine Translation</result>
  <result author="Jarmila Panevová">Za poleznosta na elektronskite jazični korpusi (vrz primerot na eden tip na imenskata fraza vo češkiot jazik)</result>
  <result author="Karel Oliva">(German) Corpus representativity, bigrams, and PoS-tagging quality</result>
  <result author="Jarmila Panevová">Ješčo raz po povodu nulevyx elementov v strukture predloženija</result>
  <result author="Jarmila Panevová">K nové úrovni bohemistické práce: Využití anotovaného korpusu. Část 1</result>
  <result author="Petr Homola">Machine translation among Slavic languages</result>
  <result author="Jarmila Panevová">K valenci substantiv (s ohledem na jejich derivaci)</result>
  <result author="Jan Štěpánek">Building on Frege</result>
  <result author="Eva Hajičová">Recenze knihy: Studie z korpusové lingvistiky</result>
  <result author="Eva Hajičová">Umějí děti česky?</result>
  <result author="Petr Savický">Measures of Word Commonness</result>
  <result author="Jarmila Panevová">Čím může bohemistice přispět současná počítačová lingvistika?</result>
  <result author="Jarmila Panevová">K nové úrovni bohemistické práce: Využití anotovaného korpusu. Část 2</result>
  <result author="Martin Plátek">D-trivial Dependency Grammars with Global Word-Order Restrictions</result>
  <result author="Karel Oliva">Linguistically Motivated Bigrams in Part-of-Speech Tagging of Language Corpora</result>
  <result author="Petr Sgall">Moravská a pražská (malostranská) koncepce aktuálního členění</result>
  <result author="Jiří Mírovský">NetGraph System: Searching through the Prague Dependency Treebank</result>
  <result author="Pavel Pecina">Sémanticky signifikantní kolokace</result>
  <result author="Markéta Lopatková">Tektogramaticky anotovaný valenční slovník českých sloves</result>
  <result author="Eva Hajičová">Theoretical description of language as a basis of corpus annotation: The case of Prague Dependency Treebank</result>
  <result author="Markéta Straňáková-Lopatková">Valenční slovník stokrát jinak: co je pod povrchem?</result>
  <result author="Ivona Kučerová">Transforming Penn Treebank Phrase Trees into (Praguian) Tectogrammatical Dependency Trees</result>
  <result author="Jarmila Panevová">Towards a Relational - Perspective Approach to Syntactic Semantics</result>
  <result author="Jarmila Panevová">Úvod do teoretické a počítačové lingvistiky I. -- Teoretická lingvistika</result>
  <result author="Daniel Zeman">Can Subcategorization Help a Statistical Dependency Parser?</result>
  <result author="Petr Sgall">Češskij jazyk v povsednevnom razgovore</result>
  <result author="Martin Čmejrek">Czech-English Dependency-based Machine Translation: Data Preparation for the Starting up Experiments</result>
  <result author="Veronika Řezníčková">Recenze: Beiträge der Europäischen Slavistischen Linguistik</result>
  <result author="Kiril Ribarov">On the Rule-Based Parsing of Czech</result>
  <result author="Karel Mokrý">External Tools Not Only for ArabTeX Documents</result>
  <result author="Petr Sgall">A Machine Learning Approach to Automatic Functor Assignment in the Prague Dependency Treebank</result>
  <result author="Markéta Pravdová">McSvět a místo člověka v něm</result>
  <result author="Daniel Zeman">Detris</result>
  <result author="Jarmila Panevová">The Theory of Control Applied to the Prague Dependency Treebank (PDT)</result>
  <result author="Jan Hajič">Tectogrammatical Representation: Towards a Minimal Transfer in Machine Translation</result>
  <result author="Eva Hajičová">Are Linguistic Frameworks Comparable?</result>
  <result author="Petr Sgall">The Simple Core and the Complex Periphery of Natural Language -- a Formal and a Computational View</result>
  <result author="Jarmila Panevová">Corpus-based Grammar or Corpus Grammar-based?</result>
  <result author="Pavel Květoň">(Semi-)Automatic Detection of Errors in PoS-Tagged Corpora</result>
  <result author="Kiril Ribarov">Searching for non-linearities in natural language</result>
  <result author="Jan Hajič">Automatic Transcription of Czech Language Oral History in the MALACH Project: Resources and Initial Experiments</result>
  <result author="Jan Hajič">Cross-Language Access to Recorded Speech in the MALACH Project</result>
  <result author="Roman Ondruška">Searching through Prague Dependency Treebank-Conception and Architecture</result>
  <result author="Karel Oliva">Achieving an Almost Correct PoS-Tagged Corpus</result>
  <result author="Markéta Lopatková">Valency Lexicon for Czech: from Verbs to Nouns</result>
  <result author="Jarmila Panevová">Několik poznámek k potřebě terminologických slovníků jazykovědných pojmů pro školy (na okraj slovníku P. Hausera a kol.)</result>
  <result author="Petr Sgall">Formalizing a Functional Description</result>
  <result author="Daniel Zeman">How to Decrease the Performance of a Statistical Parser</result>
  <result author="Markéta Lopatková">Testování konzistence a úplnosti valenčního slovníku českých sloves</result>
  <result author="Pavel Květoň">Language for Grammatical Rules</result>
  <result author="Jan Hajič">PDT-VALLEX: Creating a Large-coverage Valency Lexicon for Treebank Annotation</result>
  <result author="Petr Sgall">Slavistics and the history of topic-focus studies</result>
  <result author="Giuseppe Camuglia">Computer Processing of a Clopen Language System: Old-Church Slavonic</result>
  <result author="Eva Hajičová">Topic-Focus Articulation and degrees of salience in the Prague Dependency Treebank</result>
  <result author="Ivona Kučerová">Korpus jako výzva k syntaktické analýze. Poznámky k syntaktické derivaci deverbativních substantiv v češtině</result>
  <result author="Petr Sgall">From Data to Speech. Language Generation in Context</result>
  <result author="Jarmila Panevová">O jednom typu kauzativní konstrukce v češtině</result>
  <result author="Markéta Lopatková">Valency in the Prague Dependency Treebank: Building the Valency Lexicon</result>
  <result author="Jan Hajič">A Simple Multilingual Machine Translation System</result>
  <result author="Silvie Cinková">Belegsuche bei der lexikographischen Bearbeitung von selten gebrauchtem Wortschatz</result>
  <result author="Alena Böhmová">The Prague Dependency Treebank: A Three-Level Annotation Scenario</result>
  <result author="Monia Camuglia">Old-Church Slavonic in Codes</result>
  <result author="Petr Sgall">From functional sentence perspective to topic-focus articulation</result>
  <result author="Jan Hajič">Language Model Data Selection for Czech ASR in the MALACH Project</result>
  <result author="Petr Sgall">Lingvistické ohlédnutí za dvacátým stoletím</result>
  <result author="Witold Drożdżyński">Adapting SProUT to processing Baltic and Slavonic languages</result>
  <result author="Jiří Kocanda">Statistical Parsing</result>
  <result author="Vladislav Kuboň">Multilingual Aspects of Monolingual Corpora</result>
  <result author="Kateřina Veselá">Topic-Focus Articulation in PDT: Prosodic Characteristics of Contrastive Topic</result>
  <result author="Petr Homola">Shallow machine translation - in between of two extremes</result>
  <result author="Eva Hajičová">Topic-focus articulation in the Czech National Corpus</result>
  <result author="Eva Hajičová">Dependency syntax in Functional Generative Description</result>
  <result author="Petr Sgall">Topic-Focus Articulation in Corpus Annotation</result>
  <result author="Kiril Ribarov">Incorporation of Old-Church Slavonic Card-Files into a Corpus</result>
  <result author="Ondřej Bojar">Towards Automatic Extraction of Verb Frames</result>
  <result author="Radu Gramatovici">On the Recognition Power of Non-Expansive Go-Through Automata</result>
  <result author="Martin Holub">Approaches to Building Semantic Lexicons</result>
  <result author="Markéta Lopatková">Issue of Valency in Prague Dependency Treebank: Creating valency lexicon of Verbs. (Abstract) </result>
  <result author="Owen Rambow">Automatically Deriving Tectogrammatical Labels from Other Resources: A Comparison of Semantic Labels Across Frameworks</result>
  <result author="Eva Hajičová">Syntactic theory and corpus annotation need each other</result>
  <result author="Jiří Semecký">Semantic Word Classes Extracted from Text Clusters</result>
  <result author="Martin Plátek">Restarting Automata: Motivations and Applications</result>
  <result author="Christian Bering">Corpora and evaluation tools for multilingual names entity grammar development</result>
  <result author="Petr Sgall">Dynamics in the meaning of the sentence and of discourse</result>
  <result author="Eva Hajičová">Information Structure, Translation and Discourse</result>
  <result author="Zdeněk Žabokrtský">Word Sense Disambiguation. The Case for Combinations of Knowledge Sources</result>
  <result author="Eva Hajičová">Aspects of discourse structure</result>
  <result author="Jan Hajič">Annotation Lexicons: Using the Valency Lexicon for Tectogrammatical Annotation</result>
  <result author="Eva Hajičová">Information structure and contrastive topic</result>
  <result author="Eva Hajičová">Discourse Semantics and the Salience of Referents</result>
  <result author="Markéta Lopatková">O homonymii předložkových skupin v češtine (Co umí počítač?)</result>
  <result author="Břetislav Kupera">Genetic Algorithms and Artificial Neural Network in Natural Language Processing</result>
  <result author="Eva Hajičová">Information structure and syntactic complexity</result>
  <result author="Jarmila Panevová">Existuje chyba v syntaxi?</result>
  <result author="Ondřej Bojar">ENTI -- Simulátor přirozeného prostředí lidského světa</result>
  <result author="Jan Hajič">Tagging as a Key to Successful MT</result>
  <result author="Ondřej Bojar">AX - Systém pro automatizovanou extrakci lexikálně-syntaktických údajů</result>
  <result author="Veronika Řezníčková">Czech Deverbal Nouns: Issues of Their Valency in Linear and Dependency Corpora</result>
  <result author="Roman Ondruška">An Exploitation of the Prague Dependency Treebank: A Valency Case</result>
  <result author="Zdeněk Žabokrtský">Arabic Syntactic Trees: from Constituency to Dependency</result>
  <result author="Martin Čmejrek">Czech-English Dependency-based Machine Translation</result>
  <result author="Jarmila Panevová">Some Issues of Syntax and Semantics of Verbal Modifications</result>
  <result author="Václav Hlaváč">Rozpoznávání jako jeden z přístupů porozumění složitým jevům</result>
  <result author="Eva Hajičová">Contextual boundness and discourse patterns</result>
  <result author="Kateřina Veselá">Some observations on contrastive topic in Czech spontaneous speech</result>
  <result author="Petr Sgall">Introductory remarks (to the Workshop on Discourse Patterns)</result>
  <result author="Alena Böhmová">Large Language Data and the Degrees of Automation</result>
  <result author="Ondřej Bojar">Building Subcorpora Suitable for Extraction of Lexico-Syntactic Information</result>
  <result author="Martin Holub">A New Approach to Conceptual Document Indexing: Building a Hierarchical System of Concepts Based on Document Clusters</result>
  <result author="Josef Psutka">Towards Automatic Transcription of Spontaneous Czech Speech in the MALACH Project</result>
  <result author="Václav Honetschläger">Using a Czech Valency Lexicon for Annotation Support</result>
  <result author="Tomáš Holan">A Theoretical Basis of an Architecture of a Shell of a Reasonably Robust Syntactic Analyser</result>
  <result author="Pavel Krbec">Combination of a Hidden Tag Model and a Traditional N-gram Model: A Case Study in Czech Speech Recognition</result>
  <result author="Karel Oliva">The Computational Complexity of Rule-Based Part-of-Speech Tagging</result>
  <result author="Josef Psutka">Large Vocabulary ASR for Spontaneous Czech in the MALACH Project</result>
  <result author="Josef Psutka">Building LVCSR System for Transcription of Spontaneously Pronounced Russian Testimonies in the MALACH Project: Initial Steps and First Results</result>
  <result author="Jana Klímová">Využití ČNK a PZK pro ověřování valenčních vlastností deverbativních substantiv se zabudovanou rolí</result>
  <result author="Martin Čmejrek">Treebanks in Machine Translation</result>
  <result author="Jan Hajič">Linguistic Annotation: from Links to Cross-Layer Lexicons</result>
  <result author="Kateřina Veselá">Anotování aktuálního členění věty v Pražském závislostním korpusu</result>
  <result author="Markéta Lopatková">VALLEX 1.0 Valency Lexicon of Czech Verbs</result>
  <result author="Lucie Kučová">Annotation of Coreference in the Prague Dependency Treebank</result>
  <result author="Petr Homola">On some aspects on machine translation among related languages</result>
  <result author="Daniel Zeman">Data-Oriented Parsing by Rens Bod, Remko Scha, and Khalil Sima'an</result>
  <result author="Jan Hajič">Anotace na tektogramatické rovině (úroveň 3)</result>
  <result author="Petr Homola">How can shallow NLP help a machine translation system</result>
  <result author="Magda Razímová">Funkce adverbálního dativu v hloubkové a povrchové stavbě české věty (diplomová práce FF UK Praha)</result>
  <result author="David Klusáček">Optimal Detection in Case of the Sparse Training Data</result>
  <result author="Josef V. Psutka">Issues in annotation of the Czech spontaneous speech corpus in the MALACH project</result>
  <result author="Veronika Kolářová">Valence deverbálních substantiv: Některé specifické posuny v povrchových realizacích participantů</result>
  <result author="Anett Frank">Corpus-based Induction of an LFG Syntax-Semantics Interface for Frame Semantic Processing</result>
  <result author="Markéta Pravdová">Reklama jako zvláštní typ sdělování</result>
  <result author="Jan Hajič">Disambiguation of Rich Inflection (Computational Morphology of Czech)</result>
  <result author="Kiril Ribarov">ACT - Computer Processing of Written Cultural Heritage Sources</result>
  <result author="Jaroslava Hlaváčová">Derivational Relations in Flectional Languages - Czech Case</result>
  <result author="Silvie Cinková">Mats Wahlberg (ed.): Svenskt ortnamnslexikon (Švédský slovník místních jmen)</result>
  <result author="Zdeňka Urešová">The verbal valency in the Prague Dependency Treebank from the annotator's point of view</result>
  <result author="Petr Homola">Distributed translation memories and shallow MT</result>
  <result author="Jan Hajič">Anotace na analytické rovině. Návod pro anotátory</result>
  <result author="Lucie Kučová">Prague Dependency Treebank: Enrichment of the Underlying Syntactic Annotation by Coreferential Mark-Up</result>
  <result author="Markéta Lopatková">Valence vybraných skupin sloves (k některým slovesům dandi a recipiendi)</result>
  <result author="Markéta Pravdová">K způsobům persvaze v reklamních projevech</result>
  <result author="Kiril Ribarov">The Annotation Corpora of Text (ACT) Tool</result>
  <result author="Lucie Kučová">Coreferential Relations in the Prague Dependency Treebank</result>
  <result author="Daniel Zeman">Neprojektivity v Pražském závislostním korpusu (PDT)</result>
  <result author="Otakar Smrž">Finite State Morphology</result>
  <result author="Jaroslava Hlaváčová">Automatické rozpoznávání českých derivačních předpon</result>
  <result author="Petr Sgall">K obohacování spisovné češtiny</result>
  <result author="Eva Hajičová">The Prague Dependency Treebank: How much of the underlying syntactic structure can be tagged automatically?</result>
  <result author="Ondřej Bojar">Czech Syntactic Analysis Constraint-Based, XDG: One Possible Start</result>
  <result author="Jan Hajič">Validating and Improving the Czech WordNet via Lexico-Semantic Annotation of the Prague Dependency Treebank</result>
  <result author="Václava Benešová">Delimitace lexií českých sloves z hlediska jejich syntaktických vlastností (diplomová práce)</result>
  <result author="Jan Hajič">The Prague Dependency Treebank. Annotation on tectogrammatical level</result>
  <result author="Kiril Ribarov">Automatic Building of a Dependency Tree - The Rule-Based Approach and Beyond</result>
  <result author="Eva Hajičová">Translation and Information Structure</result>
  <result author="Karel Oliva">O korpusu jako o zdroji jazykových dat</result>
  <result author="Martin Holub">Searching for Topics in a Large Collection of Texts</result>
  <result author="Renata Blatná">Frekvenční slovník češtiny</result>
  <result author="Silvie Cinková">Extraction of Swedish Verb-Noun Collocations from a Large Msd-Annotated Corpus</result>
  <result author="Kiril Ribarov">Towards Intelligent Written Cultural Heritage Processing - Lexical Processing</result>
  <result author="Eva Hajičová">Issues of Projectivity in the Prague Dependency Treebank</result>
  <result author="Silvie Cinková">Recenze - Ruslan Mitkov (ed.) The Oxford Handbook of Computational Linguistics</result>
  <result author="Jakub Piskorski">Information extraction for Polish using the SProUT platform</result>
  <result author="Jan Cuřín">Prague Czech-English Dependency Treebank Version 1.0</result>
  <result author="Josef V. Psutka">The Development of ASR for Slavic Languages in the MALACH Project</result>
  <result author="Petr Sgall">Co pomůže češtině. O potřebě přejít od školské spisovnosti ke standardnímu vyjadřování</result>
  <result author="Petr Homola">A translation model for languages of acceding countries</result>
  <result author="Eva Hajičová">Degrees of Contrast and the Topic-Focus Articulation</result>
  <result author="Eva Hajičová">Topic and focus, anaphoric relations and degrees of salience</result>
  <result author="Eva Hajičová">Kontrast v základu výpovědi ve světle Pražského závislostního korpusu</result>
  <result author="Petr Sgall">Jak psát a nepsat česky</result>
  <result author="William J. Byrne">Automatic Recognition of Spontaneous Speech for Access to Multilingual Oral History Archives</result>
  <result author="Louise Guthrie">Large Scale Experiments for Semantic Labeling of Noun Phrases in Raw Text</result>
  <result author="Ondřej Bojar">Problems of Inducing Large Coverage Constraint-Based Dependency Grammar for Czech</result>
  <result author="Silvie Cinková">Manuál pro tektogramatickou anotaci angličtiny</result>
  <result author="Jan Hajič">Prague Arabic Dependency Treebank 1.0</result>
  <result author="Markéta Lopatková">Závislostní redukční analýza přirozených jazyků</result>
  <result author="Vladislav Kuboň">Využití existujících zdrojů pro systém automatického překladu</result>
  <result author="Kateřina Veselá">Annotators' Agreement: The Case of Topic-Focus Articulation</result>
  <result author="Martin Čmejrek">Prague Czech-English Dependency Treebank. Syntactically Annotated Resources for Machine Translation</result>
  <result author="Petr Sgall">Deep Syntactic Annotation: Tectogrammatical Representation and Beyond</result>
  <result author="Martin Čmejrek">Prague Czech-English Dependency Treebank: Any Hopes for a Common Annotation Scheme?</result>
  <result author="Zdeněk Žabokrtský">Valency Frames of Czech Verbs in VALLEX 1.0</result>
  <result author="Petr Homola">Mašininis vertimas tarp artimų kalbų</result>
  <result author="Ondřej Bojar">Automated Extraction of Lexico-Syntactic Information</result>
  <result author="Petr Sgall">Types of Languages and the Simple Pattern of the Core of Language</result>
  <result author="Daniel Zeman">Parsing with a Statistical Dependency Model</result>
  <result author="Kateřina Veselá">Condition of Projectivity in the Underlying Dependency Structures</result>
  <result author="Kateřina Veselá">Prosodic Characteristics of Czech Contrastive Topic</result>
  <result author="Otakar Smrž">MorphoTrees of Arabic and Their Annotation in the TrEd Environment</result>
  <result author="Ondřej Bojar">Processing noncanonical word order in Czech</result>
  <result author="Jan Hajič">Prague Arabic Dependency Treebank: Development in Data and Tools</result>
  <result author="Jarmila Panevová">Všeobecné aktanty očima Pražského závislostního korpusu (PZK)</result>
  <result author="Jan Hajič">History of Computational Linguistics</result>
  <result author="Ondřej Bojar">Budování česko-anglického slovníku pro strojový překlad</result>
  <result author="Pavel Straňák">Review of Leonard Talmy: Toward a Cognitive Semantics, Volume I, Concept Structuring Systems</result>
  <result author="Kiril Ribarov">Kořenové stromy a závislostní parsing</result>
  <result author="Magda Razímová">Morphological Meanings in the Prague Dependency Treebank 2.0</result>
  <result author="Ondřej Bojar">An MT System Recycled</result>
  <result author="Iveta Kouřilová">Review of A Student Grammar of Modern Standard Arabic by Eckehard Schultz, Cambridge University Press, 264p.</result>
  <result author="Lucie Kučová">Anaphora in Czech: Large Data and Experiments with Automatic Anaphora</result>
  <result author="Václava Benešová">Valency and Semantic Features of Verbs</result>
  <result author="František Čermák">Od školské spisovnosti ke standardní češtině</result>
  <result author="Jarmila Panevová">Sloveso: centrum věty, valence: centrální pojem syntaxe</result>
  <result author="Markéta Lopatková">Modeling syntax of Free Word-Order Languages: Dependency Analysis By Reduction</result>
  <result author="Jiří Semecký">Automatic assignment of Frame Semantics using Syntax-Semantics Interface in LFG</result>
  <result author="Eva Hajičová">Written and spoken language: The case of ambiguities</result>
  <result author="Ondřej Bojar">Problems of Reusing an existing MT System</result>
  <result author="Martin Plátek">O roztržitosti a volnosti slovosledu pomocí restartovacích automatů</result>
  <result author="Markéta Lopatková">Valency Lexicon of Czech Verbs VALLEX: Recent Experiments with Frame Disambiguation</result>
  <result author="Ondřej Bojar">VALEVAL: Testing VALLEX Consistency and Experimenting with Word-Frame Disambiguation</result>
  <result author="Magda Razímová">Meanings of Morphological Categories on the Tectogrammatical Level</result>
  <result author="Alfonso Medina Urrea">Automatic Recognition of Czech Derivational Prefixes</result>
  <result author="Ryan McDonald">Non-Projective Dependency Parsing using Spanning Tree Algorithms</result>
  <result author="Barbora Vidová Hladká">Prague Dependency Treebank as an Exercise Book of Czech</result>
  <result author="Jiří Havelka">Projektivita v úplně uspořádaných kořenových stromech: alternativní definice projektivity a optimální algoritmy pro zprojektivnění a nalezení neprojektivních hran</result>
  <result author="Martin Čmejrek">Prague Czech-English Dependency Treebank: Resource for Structure-based MT</result>
  <result author="Petr Sgall">Recenze: R. Nicolaï and P. Zima (eds.): Lexical and structural diffusion: Interplay of internal and external factors of language development in the west African Sahel. Corpus. Les cahiers 1. Nice: Faculté des lettres, arts et sciences humaines de Nice</result>
  <result author="Martin Čmejrek">Strojový překlad (50 let od zrodu)</result>
  <result author="Keith Brendan Hall">Corrective Modeling for Non-Projective Dependency Parsing</result>
  <result author="Eva Hajičová">On some aspects of translation</result>
  <result author="Petr Němec">Making the Good Taggers Even Better: Application of Artificial Neural Networks in Morphological Tagging of Czech</result>
  <result author="Petr Němec">Application of Backpropagation in Morphological Tagging for Czech</result>
  <result author="Martin Holub">Review of Peter Jackson and Isabelle Moulinier: Natural Language Processing for Online Applications: Text Retrieval, Extraction and Categorization</result>
  <result author="Lucie Kučová">Topic-focus articulation and anaphoric relations: A corpus based probe</result>
  <result author="Zdeněk Žabokrtský">Resemblances between Meaning-Text Theory and Functional Generative Description</result>
  <result author="Silvie Cinková">Swedish-Czech Combinatorial Valency Lexicon of Predicate Nouns: Describing Event Structure in Support Verb Constructions</result>
  <result author="Josef Psutka">Automatic transcription of Czech, Russian, and Slovak Spontaneous Speech in the MALACH Project</result>
  <result author="Jaroslava Hlaváčová">Orwell's 1984 - playing with Czech and Slovak versions</result>
  <result author="Petr Homola">A Machine Translation System into a Minority Language</result>
  <result author="Jan Cuřín">Building a parallel bilingual syntactically annontated corpus</result>
  <result author="Petr Sgall">Eva Hajičova's birthday</result>
  <result author="Jiří Havelka">Projectivity in Totally Ordered Rooted Trees: An Alternative Definition of Projectivity and Optimal Algorithms for Detecting Non-Projective Edges and Projectivizing Totally Ordered Rooted Trees</result>
  <result author="Drahomíra Doležalová">Automatic Construction of a Valency Lexicon of Czech Adjectives</result>
  <result author="Jiří Mírovský">Pražský závislostní korpus a jeho dostupnost pomocí vyhledávacího programu Netgraph</result>
  <result author="Veronika Řezníčková">K syntaktické anotaci textu Českého národniho korpusu: od analytické k tektogramatické rovině</result>
  <result author="Ondřej Bojar">The Project ENTs: Towards Modelling Human-like Artificial Agents</result>
  <result author="Eva Hajičová">Harvesting the fruit from Treebanks: Information structure and the stock of shared knowledge</result>
  <result author="Ondřej Bojar">Extracting Translations Verb Frames</result>
  <result author="Eva Hajičová">What Golem was not yet able to do (and what e-Golem should learn)</result>
  <result author="Veronika Kolářová">Valence vybraných skupin verbálních a dějových substantiv z pohledu čísel</result>
  <result author="Šárka Lešnerová">Postavení syntetického predikátu v humanistické češtině</result>
  <result author="Pavel Pecina">An Extensive Empirical Study of Collocation Extraction Methods</result>
  <result author="Petr Podveský">Speech Recognition of Czech - Inclusion of Rare Words Helps</result>
  <result author="Šárka Zikánová">Latinské vlivy v humanistické češtině</result>
  <result author="Petr Sgall">A note on the destruction and the revival of the Prague Linguistic Circle</result>
  <result author="Eva Hajičová">The position of information structure in the core of language</result>
  <result author="Jan Hajič">Feature-based Tagger of Approximations of Functional Arabic Morphology</result>
  <result author="Erika Rimkutė">Morfologinių samplaikų atpažinimas ir klasifikavimas</result>
  <result author="Petr Pajas">A Generic XML-Based Format for Structured Linguistic Annotation and Its Application to Prague Dependency Treebank 2.0</result>
  <result author="Silvie Cinková">Treating support verb constructions in a lexicon: Swedish-Czech combinatorial valency lexicon of predicate nouns</result>
  <result author="Hans Uszkoreit">Language Technology from a European Perspective</result>
  <result author="Eva Hajičová">Edward Göbbel: Syntactic and focus-structural aspects of triadic constructions</result>
  <result author="Eva Hajičová">Corpus Evidence of Contextual Boundness and Focus</result>
  <result author="Daniel Zeman">Improving Parsing Accuracy by Combining Diverse Dependency Parsers</result>
  <result author="Šárka Zikánová">Příspěvek k aktuálnímu členění věty v humanistické češtině</result>
  <result author="Marie Mikulová">Anotace na tektogramatické rovině Pražského závislostního korpusu. Anotátorská příručka</result>
  <result author="Ondřej Bojar">Problémy recyklování systému automatického překladu</result>
  <result author="Markéta Lopatková">Formální specifikace podkladové struktury pro popis přirozeného jazyka</result>
  <result author="Martin Holub">Models, Similarity, and Topics of Texts (PhD thesis)</result>
  <result author="Daniel Zeman">DZ Parser 1.0</result>
  <result author="Miroslav Spousta">Automatické přiřazování tvaroslovných vzorů v češtině (master's thesis)</result>
  <result author="Veronika Kolářová">Valence deverbativních substantiv v češtině (PhD thesis)</result>
  <result author="Pavel Krbec">Language Modeling for Speech Recognition of Czech (PhD thesis)</result>
  <result author="Zdeněk Žabokrtský">Valency Lexicon of Czech Verbs (PhD thesis)</result>
  <result author="Jan Votrubec">Volba vhodné sady rysů pro morfologické značkování češtiny</result>
  <result author="Jiří Hana">Manual for Morphological Annotation, Revision for the Prague Dependency Treebank 2.0</result>
  <result author="Jaroslava Hlaváčová">Average Reduced Frequency</result>
  <result author="Pavel Schlesinger">Fisher linear discriminant analysis as a method for protein classification</result>
  <result author="Jan Hajič">Microsoft Office Add-on: Czech Grammar Checker</result>
  <result author="Pavel Schlesinger">Numerical aspects of Fisher linear discriminant analysis</result>
  <result author="Jiří Mírovský">Full Tagging of Real Data Using Memory-Based Learning</result>
  <result author="Pavel Schlesinger">Implementations of Fisher's linear discriminant analysis from the numerical point of view</result>
  <result author="Jan Hajič">Treebanks and Tagsets</result>
  <result author="Jiří Semecký">Constructing an English Valency Lexicon</result>
  <result author="Craig G. Murray">Leveraging Reusability: Cost-Effective Lexical Acquisition for Large-scale Ontology Translation</result>
  <result author="Eva Hajičová">Old linguists never die, they only get obligatorily deleted</result>
  <result author="Eva Hajičová">Eighty years of the Prague Linguistic Circle</result>
  <result author="Miroslav Spousta">Web as a Corpus</result>
  <result author="Jan Hajič">Complex Corpus Annotation: The Prague Dependency Treebank</result>
  <result author="Jarmila Panevová">Na co jsme pyšní a čemu zůstaneme věrní (Poznámky k valenci několika českých adjektiv)</result>
  <result author="Eva Hajičová">Natural Language Comprehension and Translation</result>
  <result author="Ondřej Kučera">Pražský závislostní korpus jako elektronická cvičebnice jazyka českého</result>
  <result author="Silvie Cinková">Nouns as Components of Support Verb Constructions in the Prague Dependency Treebank</result>
  <result author="Eva Hajičová">K některým otázkám závislostní gramatiky</result>
  <result author="Pavel Pecina">CLEF 2006 CL-SR Test Collection</result>
  <result author="Ondřej Bojar">CzEng: Czech-English Parallel Corpus, Release version 0.5</result>
  <result author="Eva Hajičová">Petr Sgall Octogenerian</result>
  <result author="Jiří Semecký">Automatic Verb Valency Frames Disambiguation from Czech</result>
  <result author="Jindřich Matoušek">On Building Phonetically and Prosodically Rich Speech Corpus for Text-to-Speech Synthesis</result>
  <result author="Boštjan Dvořák">Exploiting Similarity in the MT into a Minority Language</result>
  <result author="Vladislav Kuboň">Segmentation of Complex Sentences</result>
  <result author="Eva Hajičová">An Annotated Corpus as a Test Bed for Discourse Structure Analysis</result>
  <result author="Pavel Pecina">Combining Association Measures for Collocation Extraction</result>
  <result author="Ondřej Kučera">A corpus-based exercise book of Czech language</result>
  <result author="Douglas W. Oard">Overview of the CLEF-2006 Cross-Language Speech Retrieval Track</result>
  <result author="Petr Sgall">Review of Prager Strukturalismus. Methodologische Grundlagen. - Prague Structuralism. Methodological Fundamentals.</result>
  <result author="Jaroslava Hlaváčová">New Approach to Frequency Dictionaries - Czech Example</result>
  <result author="Zdeňka Urešová">Verbal Valency in the Prague Dependency Treebank from the Annotator's Viewpoint</result>
  <result author="Jiří Mírovský">Netgraph: A Tool for Searching in Prague Dependency Treebank 2.0</result>
  <result author="Eva Hajičová">Využití korpusu pro ověřování lingvistických hypotéz</result>
  <result author="Tomáš Holan">Combining Czech Dependency Parsers</result>
  <result author="Jan Hajič">Complex Corpus Annotation: The Prague Dependancy Treebank</result>
  <result author="Jan Ptáček">Synthesis of Czech Sentences from Tectogrammatical Trees</result>
  <result author="Eva Hajičová">K osmdesátinám Petra Sgalla</result>
  <result author="Václav Klimeš">Rule-Based Analytical Parsing of Czech</result>
  <result author="Věra Jílková">Osudy litomyšlské rodiny Sgallových</result>
  <result author="Sašo Džeroski">Towards a Slovene Dependency Treebank</result>
  <result author="František Čermák">K diskusi o standardní a "spisovné" češtině</result>
  <result author="Otakar Smrž">Tips and Tricks of the Prague Arabic Dependency Treebank</result>
  <result author="Silvie Cinková">From PropBank to EngValLex: Adapting the PropBank-Lexicon to the Valency Theory of the Functional Generative Description</result>
  <result author="Eva Hajičová">On translating and Understanding, Plurality of Languages and Cultures</result>
  <result author="Magda Razímová">Annotation of Grammatemes in the Prague Dependency Treebank 2.0</result>
  <result author="Jiří Semecký">On Automatic Assignment of Verb Valency Frames in Czech</result>
  <result author="Petr Němec">Annotation of Temporal Relations within a Discourse</result>
  <result author="Ondřej Bojar">Strojový překlad: zamyšlení nad účelností hloubkových jazykových analýz</result>
  <result author="Petr Sgall">Poznámka k pojmu hyperkorektnost</result>
  <result author="Philipp Koehn">Open Source Toolkit for Statistical Machine Translation: Factored Translation Models and Confusion Network Decoding</result>
  <result author="Barbora Vidová Hladká">One day with Eva Hajičová</result>
  <result author="Jan Votrubec">Morphological Tagging Based on Averaged Perceptron</result>
  <result author="Petr Němec">Tree Searching/Rewriting Formalism</result>
  <result author="Eva Hajičová">K tzv. vzdáleným závislostem očima Pražského závislostního korpusu</result>
  <result author="Eva Hajičová">Towards the Underlying Structure Annotation of a Large Corpus of Texts</result>
  <result author="Václav Klimeš">Transformation-Based Tectogrammatical Analysis of Czech</result>
  <result author="Markéta Lopatková">Valency Lexicon of Czech Verbs: Alternation-Based Model</result>
  <result author="Václav Novák">On Distance between Deep Syntax and Semantic Representation</result>
  <result author="Jiří Semecký">Extensive Study on Automatic Verb Sense Disambiguation in Czech</result>
  <result author="Ondřej Bojar">Czech-English Word Alignment</result>
  <result author="Barbora Vidová Hladká">Proměny Českého akademického korpusu</result>
  <result author="Eva Hajičová">Corpus annotation as a test of a linguistic theory</result>
  <result author="Petr Sgall">Proti černobílé spisovnosti. Rozhovor s Bohumilem Vykypělem</result>
  <result author="Petr Sgall">Běžná mluva a lingvisté v Čechách a na Moravě</result>
  <result author="Eva Hajičová">Introduction</result>
  <result author="Eva Hajičová">O jazyce, jeho exaktním popisu (Pražská škola v lingvistice kdysi a dnes)</result>
  <result author="Jan Štěpánek">Post-annotation checking of Prague Dependency Treebank 2.0 data</result>
  <result author="Eva Hajičová">80th Birthday of Petr Sgall</result>
  <result author="Ivana Kruijffová">Annotation Guidelines for Czech-English Word Alignment</result>
  <result author="Jurjen Duintjer Tebbens">Efficient Implementation of Optimal Linear Discriminant Analysis</result>
  <result author="Vladislav Kuboň">O segmentaci českých vět</result>
  <result author="Magda Ševčíková-Razímová">Systematic Parameterized Description of Pro-forms in the Prague Dependency Treebank 2.0</result>
  <result author="Petr Pajas">XML-Based Representation of Multi-Layered Annotation in the PDT 2.0</result>
  <result author="Petr Homola">A Structural Similarity Measure</result>
  <result author="Petr Sgall">Valence jako jádro jazykového systému</result>
  <result author="Jan Štěpánek">Post-annotation Checking of Prague Dependency Treebank 2.0 Data</result>
  <result author="Ondřej Bojar">Czech-English Phrase-Based Machine Translation</result>
  <result author="Květa Sgallová">Zemřel Miroslav Červenka</result>
  <result author="Petr Sgall">Kořeny mé životní dráhy – Můj otec, má matka a má mateřština</result>
  <result author="Silvie Cinková">Semi-automatic Building of Swedish Collocation Lexicon</result>
  <result author="Václava Benešová">Czech Verbs of Communication and the Extraction of their Frames</result>
  <result author="Petr Sgall">Čeština standardní a běžně mluvená</result>
  <result author="Václav Novák">Perspectives of Turning Prague Dependency Treebank into a Knowledge Base</result>
  <result author="Petr Sgall">Language in its multifarious aspects</result>
  <result author="David Klusáček">Maximum Mutual Information and Word Classes</result>
  <result author="Jan Romportl">Development of Data-Driven Prosody Model for German TTS Synthesis</result>
  <result author="Jarmila Panevová">Dvě poznámky k tzv. vágnosti</result>
  <result author="Craig G. Murray">Leveraging Recurrent Phrase Structure in Large-scale Ontology Translation</result>
  <result author="Eva Hajičová">Standardní čeština a korpus</result>
  <result author="Markéta Lopatková">Recent developments of the theory of valency in the light of the Prague Dependency Treebank</result>
  <result author="Otakar Smrž">Impressive Haskell</result>
  <result author="Pavel Schlesinger">Křivky typu ROC a evaluace metod komputační lingvistiky</result>
  <result author="Ondřej Kučera">Pražský závislostní korpus jako cvičebnice jazyka českého</result>
  <result author="Eduard Bejček">Automatické přiřazování významu - "Sense-tagging"</result>
  <result author="Nino Peterek">Tools and Data for Analysis of Spoken Czech and its Prosody</result>
  <result author="Václav Klimeš">Analytical and Tectogrammatical Analysis of a Natural Language</result>
  <result author="Jan Hajič">Prague Dependency Treebank 2.0</result>
  <result author="Jan Štěpánek">Závislostní zachycení větné struktury v anotovaném syntaktickém korpusu (nástroje pro zajištění konzistence dat)</result>
  <result author="Jan Hajič">Czech Grammar Checker</result>
  <result author="Václav Klimeš">Automatic analyser of Czech language at the tectogrammatical layer</result>
  <result author="Eduard Bejček">The lexico-semantic annotation of PDT: Some results, problems and solutions</result>
  <result author="Jan Votrubec">Using Morphological Tagger for Learning Prosody</result>
  <result author="Zdeňka Urešová">Valency and Ellipsis Resolution in the Prague Dependency Treebank</result>
  <result author="Magda Razímová">System of Pronominal Words in Czech with Respect to German and English</result>
  <result author="Šárka Zikánová">Slovosled ve starší češtině (1500-1620): Postavení syntetického přísudku ve větě hlavní</result>
  <result author="Petr Homola">Die Sprachsituation im Teschener Schlesien aus historischer Perspektive</result>
  <result author="Otakar Smrž">Encode Arabic</result>
  <result author="Jiří Mírovský">Netgraph, version 1</result>
  <result author="Otakar Smrž">Functional Arabic Morphology: Principles of Design</result>
  <result author="Otakar Smrž">Prague Treebanking for Everyone: Prague Arabic Dependency Treebank</result>
  <result author="Marie Mikulová">Annotation on the tectogrammatical level in the Prague Dependency Treebank. Reference book</result>
  <result author="Silvie Cinková">LEMPAS: A Make-Do Lemmatizer for the Swedish PAROLE-Corpus </result>
  <result author="Jan Hajič">Pražský závislostní korpus mluvené češtiny. Rekonstrukce standardizovaného textu z mluvené češtiny</result>
  <result author="Marie Mikulová">Anotace na tektogramatické rovině Pražského závislostního korpusu. Referenční příručka</result>
  <result author="Veronika Kolářová">Valency of Deverbal Nouns in Czech</result>
  <result author="Markéta Lopatková">Functional Generative Description, Restarting Automata and Analysis by Reduction</result>
  <result author="Marie Mikulová">Annotation on the tectogrammatical level in the Prague Dependency Treebank. Annotation manual</result>
  <result author="Ondřej Bojar">Some Computational Experiments with Czech</result>
  <result author="Markéta Lopatková">VALLEX 2.0 - Valency Lexicon of Czech Verbs</result>
  <result author="Šárka Zikánová">What do the data in Prague Dependency Treebank say about systemic ordering in Czech?</result>
  <result author="Silvie Cinková">Annotation of English on the tectogrammatical level</result>
  <result author="Markéta Lopatková">Valency Lexicon of Czech Verbs VALLEX 2.0</result>
  <result author="Kiril Ribarov">When a statistically oriented parser was more efficient than a linguist: A case of treebank conversion</result>
  <result author="Keith Brendan Hall">Log-linear Models of Non-projective Trees, k-best MST Parsing and Tree-ranking</result>
  <result author="Giang Linh Nguy">Rule-based Approach to Pronominal Anaphora Resolution Applied on the Prague Dependency Treebank 2.0 Data</result>
  <result author="Klára Hrstková">Czech Prefixed Verbs in a Valency Lexicon. Preliminary Study</result>
  <result author="Markéta Lopatková">Towards a Formal Model for Functional Generative Description: Analysis by Reduction and Restarting Automata</result>
  <result author="Eduard Bejček">Selected Sense Enumerated Lexical Resources for Czech</result>
  <result author="Johanka Doležalová">Shallow Parsing of Czech Sentence Based on Correct Morphological Disambiguation</result>
  <result author="Pavel Češka">Charles University at CLEF 2007 Ad-Hoc Track</result>
  <result author="Jiří Navrátil">On Linear DETs</result>
  <result author="Vladislav Kuboň">A Linguistically-Based Segmentation of Complex Sentences</result>
  <result author="Markéta Lopatková">Valence vybraných sloves pohybu v češtině</result>
  <result author="Ondřej Kučera">STYX 2007</result>
  <result author="Zdeňka Urešová">PDT Vallex 2.0</result>
  <result author="Petr Němec">Capturing the Meaning of Time Expressions: A Functional Approach</result>
  <result author="Eva Hajičová">Information Structure from the Point of View of the Relation of Function and Form</result>
  <result author="Tomáš Jelínek">Morfologické značkování a lemmatizace v korpusech ČNK</result>
  <result author="Daniel Zeman">Unsupervised Acquiring of Morphological Paradigms from Tokenized Text</result>
  <result author="Jarmila Panevová">Gradation of adjectives and valency</result>
  <result author="Eva Hajičová">Jazyk a umělá inteligence: kudy a kam?</result>
  <result author="Jan Hajič">CoNNL 2007 Shared Task Arabic Test Set, Part 1</result>
  <result author="Magda Ševčíková">Named Entities in Czech: Annotating Data and Developing NE Tagger</result>
  <result author="Otakar Smrž">Demo Proposal: Extensible Integrated Treebank Annotation Environment</result>
  <result author="Pavel Pecina">Overview of the CLEF-2007 Cross-Language Speech Retrieval Track</result>
  <result author="Jan Romportl">Prosody Modelling in Czech Text-to-Speech Synthesis</result>
  <result author="Pavel Ircing">Information Retrieval Test Collection for Searching Spontaneous Czech Speech</result>
  <result author="Pavel Češka">Charles University at CLEF 2007 CL-SR Track</result>
  <result author="Petr Homola">Biblio</result>
  <result author="Petr Homola">Current development tendencies in the dialect of Jablunkov</result>
  <result author="Petr Pajas">MEd - an editor of interlinked multi-layered linearly-structured linguistic annotations</result>
  <result author="Ondřej Bojar">English-to-Czech Factored Machine Translation</result>
  <result author="Michal Marek">Web Page Cleaning with Conditional Random Fields</result>
  <result author="Petr Sgall">O názorové pluralitě a hledání konsenzu v lingvistice</result>
  <result author="Karel Oliva">Ohlédnutí za 32. ročníkem Olympiády v českém jazyce</result>
  <result author="Jan Hajič">CoNNL 2007 Shared Task Arabic Training Set</result>
  <result author="Drahomíra Spoustová">Pravidlová disambiguace a získávání informací o povrchové valenci sloves a adjektiv z ČNK</result>
  <result author="Václav Novák">Large Semantic Network Manual Annotation</result>
  <result author="Petr Homola">Morphosyntaktische Unterbestimmtheit und der Schwund von Klitika</result>
  <result author="Drahomíra Spoustová">The Best of Two Worlds: Cooperation of Statistical and Rule-Based Taggers for Czech</result>
  <result author="Petr Homola">K některým aspektům strojového překladu mezi baltoslovanskými jazyky</result>
  <result author="Magda Ševčíková">Zpracování pojmenovaných entit v českých textech</result>
  <result author="Jan Raab">Comparing Prosody Formalisms for Machine Learning</result>
  <result author="Jana Šindlerová">EngVallex 1.0</result>
  <result author="Jiří Havelka">Beyond Projectivity: Multilingual Evaluation of Constraints and Measures on Non-Projective Structures</result>
  <result author="Pavel Pecina">CLEF 2007 CL-SR Test Collection</result>
  <result author="Pavel Pecina">CLEF 2007 Ad-Hoc Test Collection</result>
  <result author="Petr Sgall">Issues of verb valency in syntactic annotation of a large corpus</result>
  <result author="Martin Plátek">Funkční generativní popis a formální  teorie  překladů</result>
  <result author="Silvie Cinková">“Movement towards Structure”: Foreign Learners, Language Patterns and Learners' Lexicons</result>
  <result author="Václav Novák">Cedit - Semantic Networks Manual Annotation Tool</result>
  <result author="Markéta Lopatková">VALLEX 2.5 - Valency Lexicon of Czech Verbs, version 2.5</result>
  <result author="Šárka Zikánová">Connectives as Discourse Landmarks. Agnès Celle, Ruth Huart (eds.) Amsterdam, Philadelphia: John Benjamins Publishing Company, 2007, 212 pp. ISBN 978-90-272-5404-7</result>
  <result author="Jarmila Panevová">On Reciprocity</result>
  <result author="Václav Novák">Feature Engineering in Maximum Spanning Tree Dependency Parser</result>
  <result author="Natalia Klyueva">Semantics in Machine Translation</result>
  <result author="Jan Ptáček">Sentence Synthesis in Machine Translation</result>
  <result author="Eva Hajičová">The Need of Deep Annotation of Corpus: A Case Study</result>
  <result author="Douglas W. Oard">Overview of the CLEF-2006 Cross-Language Speech Retrieval Track</result>
  <result author="Adam Przepiórkowski">Towards the Automatic Extraction of Definitions in Slavic</result>
  <result author="Václav Klimeš">Transformation-Based Tectogrammatical Dependency Analysis of English</result>
  <result author="Zdeněk Žabokrtský">Valency Information in VALLEX 2.0: Logical Structure of the Lexicon</result>
  <result author="Jaroslava Hlaváčová">Korpusové chyby</result>
  <result author="Jana Šindlerová">An Application of the PDT-scheme to a Parallel Treebank</result>
  <result author="Jiří Havelka">Relationship between Non-Projective Edges, Their Level Types, and Well-Nestedness</result>
  <result author="Domen Marinčič">Parsing Aided by Intra-Clausal Coordination Detection</result>
  <result author="Eva Hajičová">On some aspects of Praguian functionalism</result>
  <result author="David Klusáček">mmi_clustering</result>
  <result author="Jan Hajič">Some of Our Best Friends are Statistician</result>
  <result author="Zdeněk Žabokrtský">Set of tools for converting valency lexicons into PDF and HTML presentation format</result>
  <result author="Jan Ptáček">Dependency-based Sentence Synthesis Component for Czech</result>
  <result author="Eva Hajičová">The Position of TFA (Information Structure) in a Dependency Based Description of Language</result>
  <result author="Otakar Smrž">ElixirFM -- Implementation of Functional Arabic Morphology</result>
  <result author="Otakar Smrž">Learning to Use the Prague Arabic Dependency Treebank</result>
  <result author="Philipp Koehn">Moses: Open Source Toolkit for Statistical Machine Translation</result>
  <result author="Petr Homola">Česílko - hloubkový transfer pro příbuzné jazyky</result>
  <result author="Jiří Hana">Lexical Annotation Workbench (LAW), Version 0.7</result>
  <result author="Jan Hajič">CoNNL 2007 Shared Task Arabic Test Set, Part 2</result>
  <result author="Nino Peterek">Digitisation and Automatic Alignment of the DIALOG Corpus: Prosodically Annotated Corpus of Czech Television Debates</result>
  <result author="Jarmila Panevová">Znovu o reciprocitě</result>
  <result author="Petr Němec">Automatic Analysis of Temporal Relations within a Discourse</result>
  <result author="Eva Hajičová">Corpus annotation as a test of a linguistic theory: The case of  Prague Dependency Treebank</result>
  <result author="Eva Hajičová">Medailon</result>
  <result author="Ondřej Bojar">Towards English-to-Czech MT via Tectogrammatical Layer</result>
  <result author="Daniel Zeman">DZ Interset 0.2</result>
  <result author="Ondřej Bojar">Czech-English Machine Translation Dictionary</result>
  <result author="Ondřej Bojar">Tree-based Translation, Synchronous Tree Substitution Grammars</result>
  <result author="Ondřej Bojar">Interaktivní ukázka česko-anglického strojového překladu</result>
  <result author="Marie Mikulová">Annotation on the tectogrammatical level in the Prague Dependency Treebank</result>
  <result author="Jana Šindlerová">Zachycení koordinace v závislostním popisu (se zvláštním zřetelem ke koordinaci nestejných kategorií)</result>
  <result author="Barbora Vidová Hladká">Czech Academic Corpus 1.0 Guide</result>
  <result author="Barbora Vidová Hladká">Czech Academic Corpus 1.0</result>
  <result author="Šárka Zikánová">Identification of Topic and Focus in Czech: Evaluation of Manual Parallel Annotations</result>
  <result author="Eva Hajičová">Contextual Boundness and Contrast in the Prague Dependency Treebank</result>
  <result author="Otakar Smrž">ElixirFM</result>
  <result author="Otakar Smrž">Functional Arabic Morphology. Formal System and Implementation</result>
  <result author="Zdeňka Urešová">Valency in the family of Prague Dependency Treebanks </result>
  <result author="Jan Hajič">Syntax and Semantics in the family of Prague Dependency Treebanks </result>
  <result author="Barbora Hladká">A Corpus-based exercise book of Czech</result>
  <result author="Jiří Havelka">Mathematical Properties of Dependency Trees and their Application to Natural Language Syntax</result>
  <result author="Petr Pajas">Structure of Submodels - Diagonal indiscernibility in Models of Arithmetic</result>
  <result author="Drahomíra Spoustová">Kombinované statisticko-pravidlové metody značkování češtiny</result>
  <result author="Jurjen Duintjer Tebbens">Improving implementation of linear discriminant analysis for the high dimension/small sample size problem</result>
  <result author="Jarmila Panevová">Ještě jednou o reciprocitě</result>
  <result author="Jiří Semecký">Verb Valency Frames Disambiguation</result>
  <result author="Ondřej Bojar">The Hot, Dusty, Corrugated Road to Deep Syntactic Machine Translation</result>
  <result author="Ondřej Bojar">CzEng 0.7</result>
  <result author="Ondřej Bojar">TreeDecode 0.5</result>
  <result author="Ondřej Bojar">Using Mercury (for NLP), Manarchive</result>
  <result author="Ondřej Bojar">The Challenge of Syntax-Based Machine Translation</result>
  <result author="Ondřej Bojar">Mathematical Model of Tree Transformations</result>
  <result author="Otakar Smrž">Functional Arabic Morphology: Dissertation Summary</result>
  <result author="Jan Raab">Morče - Czech morphological tagger</result>
  <result author="Barbora Hladká">Our lucky moments with Frederick Jelinek</result>
  <result author="Otakar Smrž">Prague Arabic Dependency Treebank: A Word on the Million Words</result>
  <result author="Silvie Cinková">The Tectogrammatics of English: on Some Problematic Issues from the Viewpoint of the Prague Dependency Treebank</result>
  <result author="Lucie Mladová">K problematice vztahu rematizátorů a textových konektorů</result>
  <result author="Drahomíra Spoustová">Validating the Quality of Full Morphological Annotation</result>
  <result author="Giang Linh Nguy">Machine Learning Approaches to Coreference Resolution</result>
  <result author="Petr Homola">Improving Machine Translation Between Closely Related Romance Languages</result>
  <result author="Pavel Pecina">Overview of the CLEF-2007 Cross-Language Speech Retrieval Track</result>
  <result author="Ondřej Bojar">English-Hindi Translation in 21 Days</result>
  <result author="Petr Pajas">Recent Advances in a Feature-Rich Framework for Treebank Annotation</result>
  <result author="Eduard Bejček">Annotation of Multiword Expressions in the Prague Dependency Treebank</result>
  <result author="Daniel Zeman">Cross-Language Parser Adaptation between Related Languages</result>
  <result author="Zdeněk Žabokrtský">TectoMT: Highly Modular MT System with Tectogrammatics Used as Transfer Layer</result>
  <result author="Vladislav Kuboň">Využití jazykových technologií v oblasti eLearningu</result>
  <result author="Anja Nedolužko">Cинтаксически аннотированный корпус чешского языка</result>
  <result author="Petr Homola">Implementace unifikační gramatiky pro strojový překlad</result>
  <result author="Jarmila Panevová">Povaha stupňování adjektiv (K "nesrovnávacímu" užití stupňovaných forem)</result>
  <result author="Eduard Bejček">Anotace víceslovných výrazů v Pražském závislostním korpusu</result>
  <result author="Václava Benešová">Enhancing Czech Valency Lexicon with Semantic Information from FrameNet: The Case of Communication Verbs</result>
  <result author="Václav Novák">Inter-sentential Coreferences in Semantic Networks: An Evaluation of Manual Annotation</result>
  <result author="Martin Čmejrek">Tree Aligner 0.8, Java implementation</result>
  <result author="Drahomíra Spoustová">Morphium</result>
  <result author="Magda Ševčíková">Proper Nouns in Czech Corpora</result>
  <result author="Jan Raab">Compost Czech</result>
  <result author="Jan Štěpánek">Pražský závislostní korpus</result>
  <result author="Jaroslava Hlaváčová">Pravopisné varianty a morfologická anotace korpusů</result>
  <result author="Ondřej Kučera">Automaticky vytvořená cvičebnice češtiny</result>
  <result author="Miroslav Spousta">Victor: the Web-Page Cleaning Tool</result>
  <result author="Miroslav Týnovský">Hybrid Approaches in Machine Translation</result>
  <result author="Václava Kettnerová">Semantic Roles in Valency Lexicon of Czech Verbs: Verbs of Communication and Exchange</result>
  <result author="Magda Ševčíková">Pronouns Introducing Content Clauses</result>
  <result author="Tomáš Jelínek">Nové značkování v Českém národním korpusu</result>
  <result author="Pavel Pecina">Reference Data for Collocation Extraction: Czech Surface Bigrams from the Prague Dependency Treebank</result>
  <result author="Petr Homola">Rozšířený interpret Q-systémů</result>
  <result author="Markéta Lopatková">Functional Generative Description, Restarting Automata and Analysis by Reduction</result>
  <result author="Petr Kaderka">Minulost, současnost a budoucnost korpusu DIALOG</result>
  <result author="Pavel Pecina">A Machine Learning Approach to Multiword Expression Extraction</result>
  <result author="Daniel Zeman">Unsupervised Acquiring of Morphological Paradigms from Tokenized Text</result>
  <result author="Marie Mikulová">Pražský závislostní korpus: Specifikace významů prostorových určení</result>
  <result author="Jarmila Panevová">České konstrukce tzv. slovanského akuzativu s infinitivem</result>
  <result author="Eva Hajičová"> Coreferential relations in the Prague Dependency Treebank </result>
  <result author="Petr Homola">A Distributed Database for Mobile NLP Applications</result>
  <result author="Michal Marek">Victor</result>
  <result author="Markéta Lopatková">Valence a její formální popis. Vybrané aspekty budování slovníku VALLEX</result>
  <result author="Enrico Zovato">Speech synthesis and emotions: a compromise between flexibility and believability</result>
  <result author="Pavel Pecina">Frequency Data for Collocation Extraction: Czech Surface Bigrams from the Prague Dependency Treebank</result>
  <result author="Miroslav Spousta">Victoria</result>
  <result author="Jaroslava Hlaváčová">Variants and Homographs: Eternal Problem of Dictionary Makers</result>
  <result author="Jan Hajič">PDTSL: An Annotated Resource For Speech Reconstruction</result>
  <result author="Jiří Mírovský">Learning to Search in the Prague Dependency Treebank</result>
  <result author="Pavel Pecina">Frequency Data for Collocation Extraction: Czech Surface Bigrams from the Czech National Corpus</result>
  <result author="Silvie Cinková">Lemmatisierung der verbalen Reflexivität im entstehenden Großen Deutsch-Tschechischen akademischen Wörterbuch</result>
  <result author="Markéta Lopatková">Valenční slovník českých sloves</result>
  <result author="Petr Homola">A Hybrid Machine Translation System for Typologically Related Languages</result>
  <result author="Markéta Lopatková">K významnému životnímu jubileu Jarmily Panevové</result>
  <result author="Václava Benešová">Modality in dependent content clauses with Czech verbs of communication with imperative features</result>
  <result author="Šárka Zikánová">Clitic Climbing and Theta-Roles in Upper Sorbian and Czech</result>
  <result author="Viktor Bielický">Building the Valency Lexicon of Arabic Verbs</result>
  <result author="Šárka Zikánová">Problematické syntaktické struktury: k rozborům aktuálního členění v Pražském závislostním korpusu</result>
  <result author="Jiří Mírovský">Towards a Simple and Full-Featured Treebank Query Language</result>
  <result author="Petr Homola">Słowjeńska mjeńšyna w Awstriskej</result>
  <result author="Tomáš Duběda">Pitch Accents, Boundary Tones and Contours: Automatic Learning of Czech Intonation</result>
  <result author="Václava Kettnerová">Semantic Classes in Czech Valency Lexicon: Verbs of Communication and Verbs of Exchange</result>
  <result author="Jindřich Matoušek">Building of a Speech Corpus Optimised for Unit Selection TTS Synthesis</result>
  <result author="Petr Sgall">Ideje Pražského lingvistického kroužku jsou i dnes aktuální</result>
  <result author="Jan Ptáček">Two Tectogrammatical Realizers Side by Side: Case of English and Czech</result>
  <result author="Silvie Cinková">Two Languages - One Annotation Scenario? Experience from the Prague Dependency Treebank</result>
  <result author="Eva Hajičová">Úloha Pražského lingvistického kroužku při vývoji i ve vyhlídkách české jazykovědy</result>
  <result author="Jarmila Panevová">Problémy se slovanským reflexivem</result>
  <result author="Barbora Hladká">An Annotated Corpus Outside Its Original Context: A Corpus-Based Exercise Book</result>
  <result author="Pavel Pecina">Reference Data for Collocation Extraction: Czech Surface Bigrams from the Czech National Corpus</result>
  <result author="Petr Homola">Česílko 2.0</result>
  <result author="Ondřej Kučera">STYX 2008</result>
  <result author="Markéta Lopatková">Vztahy mezi segmenty – segmentační schémata českých vět</result>
  <result author="Šárka Zikánová">Několik vět a mezivětných vztahů úvodem</result>
  <result author="Lucie Mladová">From Sentence to Discourse: Building an Annotation Scheme for Discourse Based on Prague Dependency Treebank</result>
  <result author="Pavel Češka">Charles University at CLEF 2007 Ad-Hoc Track</result>
  <result author="Petr Homola">Pólske Morawarje we pšuskej Šlazyńskej</result>
  <result author="Pavel Pecina">Frequency Data for Collocation Extraction: Czech Dependency Bigrams from the Prague Dependency Treebank</result>
  <result author="Jana Šindlerová">Using the Constructionist Approach when Building a Multilingual Valency Lexicon</result>
  <result author="Jiří Mírovský">Netgraph - Making Searching in Treebanks Easy</result>
  <result author="Eva Hajičová">Ověřování lingvistické teorie nad počítačovým korpusem</result>
  <result author="Marie Mikulová">Rekonstrukce standardizovaného textu z mluvené řeči v Pražském závislostním korpusu mluvené češtiny. Manuál pro anotátory</result>
  <result author="Jaroslava Hlaváčová">Morfologie češtiny znovu a lépe</result>
  <result author="Ondřej Bojar">Tree-based Translation</result>
  <result author="Daniel Zeman">Using Unsupervised Paradigm Acquisition for Prefixes</result>
  <result author="Petr Pajas">PML Tree Query 0.5alpha</result>
  <result author="Jiří Mírovský">PDT 2.0 Requirements on a Query Language</result>
  <result author="Michal Křen">Corpus as a Means for Study of Lexical Usage Changes</result>
  <result author="Silvie Cinková">An Annotation Scheme for Speech Reconstruction on a Dialog Corpus</result>
  <result author="Ondřej Bojar">Phrase-Based and Deep Syntactic English-to-Czech Statistical Machine Translation</result>
  <result author="Drahomíra Spoustová">Combining Statistical and Rule-Based Approaches to Morphological Tagging of Czech Texts</result>
  <result author="Pavel Pecina">Reference Data for Czech Collocation Extraction</result>
  <result author="Jaroslava Hlaváčová">“Affisix” Tool for Prefix Recognition</result>
  <result author="Ondřej Bojar">CzEng 0.7: Parallel Corpus with Community-Supplied Translations</result>
  <result author="Vladislav Kuboň">Multilingual Approach to e-Learning from a Monolingual Perspective</result>
  <result author="Zuzanna Bedřichová">Částice implikující presupozici jako podstatná složka větného významu</result>
  <result author="Pavel Pecina">Reference Data for Collocation Extraction: Czech Dependency Bigrams from the Prague Dependency Treebank</result>
  <result author="Petr Homola">Partial Parsing in a Simple MT System</result>
  <result author="Natalia Klyueva">UMC 0.1: Czech-Russian-English Multilingual Corpus</result>
  <result author="Petr Homola">A Method of Hybrid MT for Related Languages</result>
  <result author="David Mareček">Automatic Alignment of Czech and English Deep Syntactic Dependency Trees</result>
  <result author="Drahomíra Spoustová">Compost English</result>
  <result author="Jiří Mírovský">Does Netgraph Fit Prague Dependency Treebank?</result>
  <result author="Magdaléna Rysová">Nejednoznačnost aktuálního členění výpovědi v básnické tvorbě Otokara Březiny</result>
  <result author="Daniel Zeman">Reusable Tagset Conversion Using Tagset Drivers</result>
  <result author="Ondřej Bojar">Hloubkový syntaktický strojový překlad: dosud nesplněná očekávání</result>
  <result author="Lucie Mladová">Od hloubkové struktury věty k diskurzním vztahům (Diskurzní vztahy v češtině a jejich zachycení v anotovaném korpusu)</result>
  <result author="Eva Hajičová">What we are talking about and what we are saying about it</result>
  <result author="Ondřej Bojar">English-to-Czech Machine Translation: Should We Go Shallow or Deep?</result>
  <result author="Silvie Cinková"> Speech reconstruction in PDT (on NAP-AAA corpora),   English specifics in TR structure, Coreference, Non-sentential utterances in dialog </result>
  <result author="Ondřej Bojar">Strojový překlad přes tektogramatickou rovinu</result>
  <result author="Silvie Cinková">Semantic annotation of a dialog corpus</result>
  <result author="Zdeněk Žabokrtský">Strojový překlad z angličtiny do češtiny</result>
  <result author="Zdeněk Žabokrtský">Překladový systém TectoMT </result>
  <result author="Otakar Smrž">Programming the Arabic Treebank</result>
  <result author="Ondřej Bojar">Problems of Deep Syntactic English-to-Czech MT</result>
  <result author="Petr Sgall">Velikonoce a jejich lexikální příslušenství</result>
  <result author="Barbora Vidová Hladká">The Czech Academic Corpus 2.0 Guide</result>
  <result author="Zdeňka Urešová">Diathesis and Transformations of Surface Expressions of Valency Arguments </result>
  <result author="Petr Sgall">Jakou češtinu máme, a jak se k ní chováme? Potřebujeme češtinu správnou, spisovnou, nebo standardní?</result>
  <result author="Eva Hajičová">What does sentence annotation say about discourse?</result>
  <result author="David Mareček">Automatic Alignment of Tectogrammatical Trees from Czech-English Parallel Corpus</result>
  <result author="Jiří Mírovský">Netgraph 1.95 - a tool for searching in PDT 2.0</result>
  <result author="Magda Ševčíková">Petr Sgall: Language in its multifarious aspects. Ed. Eva Hajičová – Jarmila Panevová. Karolinum, Charles University Press, Praha 2006. 556 s.</result>
  <result author="Ondřej Bojar">Wrestling with Deep Syntactic Translation from English to Czech</result>
  <result author="Marie Mikulová">Rekonstrukce standardizovaného textu z mluvené řeči</result>
  <result author="Václav Novák">Semantic Network Manual Annotation and its Evaluation</result>
  <result author="Ondřej Bojar">Implementation of Tree Transfer System</result>
  <result author="Daniel Zeman">Neřízená morfologická analýza</result>
  <result author="Ondřej Bojar">Exploiting Linguistic Data in Machine Translation</result>
  <result author="Pavel Pecina">Lexical Association Measures: Collocation Extraction</result>
  <result author="Miroslav Týnovský">Tree Aligner 0.8, Perl implementation</result>
  <result author="Ondřej Bojar">TreeDecode 0.8</result>
  <result author="Ondřej Bojar">UMC 0.1 Czech-English-Russian</result>
  <result author="Barbora Vidová Hladká">Czech Academic Corpus 2.0</result>
  <result author="Silvie Cinková">Speech reconstruction for the syntactic and semantic analysis of the NAP/AAA corpus</result>
  <result author="Otakar Smrž">ElixirFM</result>
  <result author="Ondřej Bojar">Towards English-to-Czech MT via Tectogrammatical Layer</result>
  <result author="Lucie Mladová">Diskurzní vztahy v češtině a jejich zachycení v anotovaném korpusu</result>
  <result author="Václava Kettnerová">Czech Verbs of Communication with respect to Types of Dependent Content Clauses</result>
  <result author="Zdeněk Žabokrtský">TectoMT, Developer's Guide</result>
  <result author="Jiří Mírovský">Netgraph Query Language for the Prague Dependency Treebank 2.0 </result>
  <result author="Nino Peterek">Dialogy.Org 0.2</result>
  <result author="Václav Novák">Semantic Network Manual Annotation and its Evaluation: Extract of Ph.D. Thesis</result>
  <result author="Petr Sgall">Prague school</result>
  <result author="Zuzanna Bedřichová">Problems and Possibilities of the Annotation of the Interpropositional Discourse Relations in PDT 2.0.</result>
  <result author="David Mareček">Improving Word Alignment Using Alignment of Deep Structures</result>
  <result author="Václav Novák">Large-scale Semantic Networks: Annotation and Evaluation</result>
  <result author="Jana Šindlerová">Towards English-Czech Parallel Valency Lexicon via Treebank Examples</result>
  <result author="David Mareček">Using Tectogrammatical Alignment in Phrase‐Based Machine Translation</result>
  <result author="Hana Klempová">Získávání paralelních textů z webu</result>
  <result author="Václav Klimeš">Detecting and Correcting Errors in an English Tectogrammatical Annotation</result>
  <result author="Martin Plátek">Restartovací automaty, DR-stromy a Funkční generativní popis češtiny</result>
  <result author="Anna Nedoluzhko">Razmetka koreferencii na sintaksičeski annotirovannom korpuse češskix tekstov</result>
  <result author="Ondřej Bojar">English-Czech MT in 2008</result>
  <result author="Tomáš Jelínek">Automatic Identification of Prepositional and Non-prepositional Cases in Czech</result>
  <result author="Markéta Lopatková">Segmentation Charts for Czech – Relations among Segments in Complex Sentences</result>
  <result author="Jaroslava Hlaváčová">Stupňování sloves</result>
  <result author="Eneko Agirre">A Study on Similarity and Relatedness Using Distributional and WordNet-based Approaches</result>
  <result author="David Kolovratník">Statistical Machine Translation between Related and Unrelated Languages</result>
  <result author="Petr Homola">Spanish-to-English Mobile MT System</result>
  <result author="Václava Kettnerová">Konstrukce s rozpadem tématu a dikta v češtině</result>
  <result author="Petr Pajas">System for Querying Syntactically Annotated Corpora</result>
  <result author="Jana Kravalová">Czech Named Entity Corpus and SVM-based Recognizer</result>
  <result author="Daniel Zeman">Using Unsupervised Paradigm Acquisition for Prefixes</result>
  <result author="Ondřej Bojar">CzEng 0.9, Building a Large Czech-English Automatic Parallel Treebank</result>
  <result author="Jarmila Panevová">Honorifika v češtině (České vykání - teorie a korpusová data)</result>
  <result author="Jan Hajič">The CoNLL-2009 Shared Task: Syntactic and Semantic Dependencies in Multiple Languages</result>
  <result author="Eva Hajičová">Information structure from the point of view of the relation of function and form</result>
  <result author="Kristýna Čermáková">Annotation of Selected Non-dependency Relations in a Dependency Treebank</result>
  <result author="Barbora Vidová Hladká">Syntactic annotation of spoken utterances: A case study on the Czech Academic Corpus</result>
  <result author="Václava Kettnerová">Changes in Valency Structure of Verbs: Grammar vs. Lexicon</result>
  <result author="Barbora Hladká">Designing a Language Game for Collecting Coreference Annotation</result>
  <result author="Eduard Bejček">Finalising Multiword Annotations in PDT</result>
  <result author="Šárka Zikánová">Identification of Topic and Focus in Czech: Comparative Evaluation on Prague Dependency Treebank</result>
  <result author="Václav Novák">Unsupervised Detection of Annotation Inconsistencies Using Apriori Algorithm</result>
  <result author="Eva Hajičová">From Prague Structuralism to Treebank Annotation</result>
  <result author="Zdeněk Žabokrtský">Hidden Markov Tree Model in Dependency-based Machine Translation</result>
  <result author="David Mareček">Converting Russian Treebank SynTagRus into Praguian PDT Style</result>
  <result author="Анна Юрьевна Недолужко">Разметка кореференции на синтаксически аннотированном корпусе чешских текстов</result>
  <result author="Kateřina Veselovská">A Corpus-based Study of the Constituent Negation in Czech</result>
  <result author="Oldřich Krůza">Obtaining Hidden Relations from a Syntactically Annotated Corpus - From Word Relationships to Clause Relationships</result>
  <result author="Martin Plátek">Restartovací automaty se strukturovaným výstupem a Funkční generativní popis</result>
  <result author="Eduard Bejček">Automatické přiřazování valenčních rámců a jejich slévání</result>
  <result author="Jernej Vičič">A method to restrict the blow-up of hypotheses of a non-disambiguated shallow machine translation system</result>
  <result author="Marie Mikulová">Annotation Quality Checking and Its Implications for Design of Treebank (in Building the Prague Czech-English Dependency Treebank)</result>
  <result author="Silvie Cinková">Semantic Representation of Non-Sentential Utterances in Dialog</result>
  <result author="Petr Homola">Machine Translation Resources for Quechua</result>
  <result author="Pavel Češka">Speech Reconstruction - Overview of State-of-the-art Systems</result>
  <result author="Lucie Mladová">Towards a Discourse Corpus of Czech</result>
  <result author="Barbora Hladká">Play the Language: Play Coreference</result>
  <result author="Ondřej Bojar">English-Hindi Translation – Obtaining Mediocre Results with Bad Data and Fancy Models</result>
  <result author="Silvie Cinková">Tectogrammatical Annotation of the Wall Street Journal</result>
  <result author="Oldřich Krůza">Automatic Extraction of Clause Relationships from a Treebank</result>
  <result author="Lucie Mladová">Annotation of Discourse Connectives for the PDT</result>
  <result author="Daniel Zeman">A Simple Generative Pipeline Approach to Dependency Parsing and Semantic Role Labeling</result>
  <result author="Magda Ševčíková">The meaning of the conditional mood within the tectogrammatical annotation of Prague Dependency Treebank 2.0</result>
  <result author="Petr Homola">A Simple Automatic MT Evaluation Metric</result>
  <result author="Petr Sgall">Rozhovor</result>
  <result author="Petr Sgall">Where to Look for the Fundamentals of Language</result>
  <result author="Vladislav Kuboň">On the Role of Syntactic Analysis of Natural Languages</result>
  <result author="Zdeňka Urešová">Diatheses in the Czech Valency Lexicon PDT-Vallex</result>
  <result author="Markéta Lopatková">Annotation of Sentence Structure; Capturing the Relationship among Clauses in Czech Sentences</result>
  <result author="Drahomíra Spoustová">Semi-Supervised Training for the Averaged Perceptron POS Tagger</result>
  <result author="Ondřej Odcházel">Computer Aided Translation Backed by Machine Translation</result>
  <result author="Anna Nedoluzhko">The Coding Scheme for Annotating Extended Nominal Coreference and Bridging Anaphora in the Prague Dependency Treebank</result>
  <result author="Giang Linh Nguy">Comparison of Classification and Ranking Approaches to Pronominal Anaphora Resolution in Czech</result>
  <result author="Marie Mikulová">Annotation Procedure in Building the Prague Czech-English Dependency Treebank</result>
  <result author="David Mareček">Manual Word Alignment Corpus 0.5</result>
  <result author="Petr Sgall">Jak dál v anotacích textových korpusů?</result>
  <result author="Ondřej Bojar">Special Issue on Open Source Machine Translation Tools</result>
  <result author="Petr Homola">Towards a Rule-Based Machine Translation System Between Czech and Russian</result>
  <result author="Anna Nedoluzhko">Extended Coreferential Relations and Bridging Anaphora in the Prague Dependency Treebank</result>
  <result author="Daniel Zeman">Maximum Spanning Malt: Hiring World's Leading Dependency Parsers to Plant Indian Trees</result>
  <result author="Petr Homola">Shallow Transfer Between Slavic Languages</result>
  <result author="Jan Hajič">CoNLL 2009 Shared Task Czech Trial Set</result>
  <result author="Jan Hajič">PDTSL - Prague Dependency Treebank of Spoken Language - Czech</result>
  <result author="Eduard Bejček">Using Averaged Perceptron Tagger  for Word Sense Disambiguation</result>
  <result author="Ondřej Bojar">Bad News, NLP Hacking and Feature Fishing</result>
  <result author="Jan Hajič">Prague Dependency Treebank of Spoken Language - English</result>
  <result author="Jan Hajič">Prague English Dependency Treebank 1.0</result>
  <result author="Zdeněk Žabokrtský">TectoMT: processing trees</result>
  <result author="Jan Raab">COMPOST Dutch: The Best POS Tagger for Dutch Spoken Language</result>
  <result author="Ondřej Bojar">Strojový překlad na ÚFALu</result>
  <result author="Jan Hajič">CoNLL 2009 Shared Task Czech Training Set</result>
  <result author="Ondřej Bojar">TectoMT for Plaintext Freaks</result>
  <result author="Pavel Pecina">Jak psát a nepsat vědecké články</result>
  <result author="Daniel Zeman">Překlad do hindštiny pro začátečníky</result>
  <result author="Zdeněk Žabokrtský">Tred Extension for Tectogrammatical Analysis of Czech Text</result>
  <result author="Zdeněk Žabokrtský">TectoMT 1.0: Modular Software Framework for NLP Experiments</result>
  <result author="Daniel Zeman">DZ Interset aneb rádoby univerzální převod morfologických značek mezi různými sadami a jazyky</result>
  <result author="Šárka Zikánová">Klasifikace textových vztahů</result>
  <result author="Jarmila Panevová">Odkud pramení shoda českého doplňku?</result>
  <result author="Jan Hajič">CoNLL 2009 Shared Task Czech Development Set</result>
  <result author="Zdeňka Urešová">PDT-Vallex: valenční slovník trochu jinak</result>
  <result author="Zuzanna Bedřichová">Anotace textových vztahů v Pražském závislostním korpusu</result>
  <result author="Jan Štěpánek">Vyhledávání v syntakticky anotovaném korpusu</result>
  <result author="Markéta Lopatková">Towards a Formal Model for Natural Languages</result>
  <result author="Ondřej Bojar">Evaluation of Tree Transfer System</result>
  <result author="Jan Ptáček">TrEd extension for displaying TectoMT framework files</result>
  <result author="Ondřej Bojar">QuickJudge</result>
  <result author="Vladislav Kuboň">On the Role of Restarting Automata in Grammar Checking of Czech</result>
  <result author="Otakar Smrž">ElixirFM 2009 (version 1.1.882-1.1.914)</result>
  <result author="Jimmy Lin">A Cost-effective Lexical Acquisition Process for Large-scale Thesaurus Translation</result>
  <result author="Pavel Pecina">Lexical Association Measures: Collocation Extraction</result>
  <result author="Jana Kravalová">Pojmenované entity v češtině</result>
  <result author="Zdeňka Urešová">Valency approach applied in the PDT</result>
  <result author="Eva Hajičová">The fundamental significance of information structure</result>
  <result author="Jaroslava Hlaváčová">Formalizace systému české morfologie s ohledem na automatické zpracování českých textů</result>
  <result author="Jan Hajič">Prague Dependency Treebank and FGD valency theory </result>
  <result author="Jana Kravalová">Využití syntaxe v metodách pro vyhledávání informací</result>
  <result author="Jana Šindlerová">Building a Multilingual Valency Lexicon</result>
  <result author="Jana Kravalová">Czech Named Entity Corpus 1.0</result>
  <result author="Magda Ševčíková">Funkce kondicionálu z hlediska významové roviny</result>
  <result author="Kamil Kos">Evaluation of Machine Translation Metrics for Czech as the Target Language</result>
  <result author="Ondřej Bojar">Jak se dělá strojový překlad</result>
  <result author="Jana Šindlerová">An Insight into the Semantics of Directional Valency Complementation</result>
  <result author="Pavel Pecina">Lexical Association Measures: Collocation Extraction</result>
  <result author="Martin Popel">Ways to Improve the Quality of English-Czech Machine Translation</result>
  <result author="Jarmila Panevová">K vlastnostem českých infinitivních konstrukcí (subjektový infinitiv)</result>
  <result author="Daniel Zeman">DZ Interset 1.1</result>
  <result author="Petr Homola">Syntactic Analysis in Machine Translation</result>
  <result author="Silvie Cinková">A Contrastive Lexical description of Basic Verbs. Examples from Swedish and Czech.</result>
  <result author="Pavel Pecina">Lexical Association Measures: Collocation Extraction</result>
  <result author="Ondřej Bojar">Czech-English Manual Word Alignments</result>
  <result author="Daniel Zeman">DZ Parser 2.0</result>
  <result author="Daniel Zeman">Morseus 1.1</result>
  <result author="Petr Pajas">CoNLL-2009 TrEd Extension</result>
  <result author="Pavel Pecina">Lexical Association Measures: Collocation Extraction</result>
  <result author="Ondřej Odcházel">AJAX-CAT: Demo of a web editor with machine translation</result>
  <result author="Šárka Zikánová">Anotace textových vztahů v Pražském závislostním korpusu</result>
  <result author="Pavel Pecina">Lexical Association Measures: Collocation Extraction</result>
  <result author="David Kolovratník">UMC003: Czech-English-Russian Tri-parallel Test Set for MT</result>
  <result author="Ondřej Bojar">Manually Flagged Errors in WMT09 Test Set</result>
  <result author="Ondřej Bojar">Trainable Tokenizer</result>
  <result author="Ondřej Bojar">CzEng 0.9</result>
  <result author="Nino Peterek">Dialogy.Org 0.3</result>
  <result author="Ondřej Bojar">Jak se Mojžíš s Jozuem učili hindsky (aneb souboj s mizernými daty při překladu z angličtiny do hindštiny)</result>
  <result author="Petr Homola">Syntactic Analysis in Machine Translation</result>
  <result author="Silvie Cinková">Words that Matter: Towards a Swedish-Czech Colligational Dictionary of Basic Verbs</result>
  <result author="Jan Raab">Compost Dutch</result>
  <result author="Šárka Zikánová">Postavení slovesného přísudku ve starší češtině (1500–1620)</result>
  <result author="Václava Kettnerová">Mapping Semantic Information from FrameNet onto VALLEX</result>
  <result author="Petr Pajas">PML Toolkit</result>
  <result author="Marie Mikulová">Pokyny k překladu určené překladatelům, revizorům a korektorům textů z Wall Street Journal pro projekt PCEDT</result>
  <result author="Ondřej Bojar">Exploiting Linguistic Data in Machine Translation</result>
  <result author="Jiří Mírovský">Searching in the Prague Dependency Treebank</result>
  <result author="Magda Ševčíková">Funkce kondicionálu z hlediska významové roviny</result>
  <result author="Petr Sgall">Zdeněk Kirschner died</result>
  <result author="Kateřina Veselovská">Increasing Prague English Dependency Treebank Credibility</result>
  <result author="Radek Čech">Pitfalls of the Transitivity Hypothesis: Transitivity in Conversation and Written Language in Czech</result>
  <result author="Petr Pajas">PML Tree Query 1.0</result>
  <result author="Pavel Pecina">Lexical Association Measures: Collocation Extraction</result>
  <result author="Martin Popel">Improving English-Czech Tectogrammatical MT</result>
  <result author="Jirka Hana">A Positional Tagset for Russian</result>
  <result author="Jinhua Du">An Augmented Three-Pass System Combination Framework: DCU Combination System for WMT 2010.</result>
  <result author="Patrick Hanks">Lexicography, Printing Technology, and the Spread of Renaissance Culture</result>
  <result author="Kateřina Rysová">Valence jako slovosledný faktor - jak dalece ovlivňuje slovosled české a německé výpovědi</result>
  <result author="Jirka Hana">Error-tagged Learner Corpus of Czech</result>
  <result author="Jarmila Panevová">Kategorie pojmenovávací a usouvztažňovací (Jak František Daneš rozvíjí Viléma Mathesia)</result>
  <result author="Jirka Hana">LAW 1.0</result>
  <result author="Jana Šindlerová">(A)symetrie valenčních vlastností českých a anglických sloves pohybu</result>
  <result author="Jana Straková">When Informatics Meets Neuroscience: Software and Statistics for Human Brain Imaging</result>
  <result author="Jirka Hana">Russian morphologically annotated corpus </result>
  <result author="Jirka Hana">morph</result>
  <result author="Pavel Straňák">Representing Layered and Structured Data in the CoNLL-ST Format</result>
  <result author="Ondřej Bojar">Data Issues in English-to-Hindi Machine Translation</result>
  <result author="Silvie Cinková">Can Corpus Pattern Analysis Be Used in NLP?</result>
  <result author="Marie Mikulová">Ways of Evaluation of the Annotators in Building the Prague Czech-English Dependency Treebank</result>
  <result author="Ondřej Bojar">Tackling Sparse Data Issue in Machine Translation Evaluation</result>
  <result author="Martin Plátek">On the Prague Group of Mathematical and Algebraic Linguistics and Its Formal Tools</result>
  <result author="Vladislav Kuboň">Od segmentů ke klauzím v češtině - analýza vybraných jevů</result>
  <result author="Jirka Hana">Challenges of Cheap Resource Creation for Morphological Tagging</result>
  <result author="Daniel Zeman">Morphological Stickers for Annotation of Check</result>
  <result author="Jarmila Panevová">Ke vztahu kognitivního obsahu a jazykového významu</result>
  <result author="Jiří Diviš">Automatic Source Code Reduction</result>
  <result author="Jirka Hana">feat</result>
  <result author="Jan Ptáček">Integration of Speech and Text Processing Modules into a Real-Time Dialogue System</result>
  <result author="Lucie Mladová">Anotace mezivýpovědních textových vztahů na Ústavu formální a aplikované lingvistiky MFF UK</result>
  <result author="Eva Hajičová">Rhematizers Revisited</result>
  <result author="Martin Plátek">Restarting Automata with Structured Output and Functional Generative Description</result>
  <result author="Markéta Lopatková">O zlomovém bodu introspekce a souvisejících problémech</result>
  <result author="Patrick Hanks">Compiling a monolingual dictionary for native speakers</result>
  <result author="Pavel Novák">On the Prague functional approach. In: Travaux linguistiques de Prague /3, pp. 291-297, 1968, reprinted</result>
  <result author="Jarmila Panevová">"Být posel dobrých zpráv je mi příjemné" (Několik poznámek k infinitivním konstrukcím)</result>
  <result author="Václava Kettnerová">The Representation of Diatheses in the Valency Lexicon of Czech Verbs</result>
  <result author="Anna Feldman">Morphological resources for Russian, Belorussian, Old Czech</result>
  <result author="Jarmila Panevová">Annotation of Morphological Meanings of Verbs Revisited</result>
  <result author="Jarmila Panevová">A Few Czech Additions to Nedjalkov's Typology of Reciprocals and Reflexives</result>
  <result author="Magda Ševčíková">Grammatical number of nouns in Czech: linguistic theory and treebank annotation</result>
  <result author="Václava Kettnerová">Representation of Changes in Valency Structure of Verbs in the Valency Lexicon of Czech Verbs</result>
  <result author="Petr Sgall">Význam a obsah</result>
  <result author="Martin Popel">English-Czech Machine Translation Using TectoMT</result>
  <result author="Martin Popel">Perplexity of n-gram and Dependency Language Models</result>
  <result author="Drahomíra Spoustová">Building a Web Corpus of Czech</result>
  <result author="Jan Hajič">Senior Companion CZ</result>
  <result author="Martin Plátek">(In)Dependencies in Functional Generative Description by Restarting Automata</result>
  <result author="Patrick Hanks">Nine issues in metaphor theory and analysis</result>
  <result author="Petr Homola">Exploiting Charts in the MT Between Related Languages</result>
  <result author="Zdeňka Urešová">PDT-Vallex - trochu jiný valenční slovník</result>
  <result author="Petr Sgall">Perspektivy standardní češtiny</result>
  <result author="Aleš Tamchyna">Bohatá anotace ve frázovém strojovém překladu</result>
  <result author="Radek Čech">Full Valency. Verb Valency without Distinguishing Complements and Adjuncts</result>
  <result author="Magda Ševčíková">Kondicionál přítomný jako součást explicitních performativních formulí</result>
  <result author="Daniel Zeman">Using TectoMT as a Preprocessing Tool for Phrase-Based Statistical Machine Translation</result>
  <result author="Kateřina Rysová">Jak volný je "volný český slovosled"? (O slovosledu české a německé výpovědi)</result>
  <result author="Markéta Lopatková">Towards a formal model of natural language description based on restarting automata with parallel DR-structures</result>
  <result author="David Kolovratník">Exodus – Exploring SMT for EU Institutions</result>
  <result author="Daniel Zeman">Hierarchical Phrase-Based MT at the Charles University for the WMT 2010 Shared Task</result>
  <result author="Eva Hajičová">Tři otázky pro Petra Karlíka (a tři oříšky pro Popelku)</result>
  <result author="Daniel Zeman">Hard Problems of Tagset Conversion</result>
  <result author="Šárka Zikánová">Typical Cases of Annotators’ Disagreement in Discourse Annotations in Prague Dependency Treebank</result>
  <result author="Patrick Hanks">Terminology, Phraseology, and Lexicography</result>
  <result author="Elisabetta Jezek">What lexical sets tell us about conceptual categories</result>
  <result author="Jan Štěpánek">Querying Diverse Treebanks in a Uniform Way</result>
  <result author="Petr Homola">Combining MT Systems Effectively</result>
  <result author="Eduard Bejček">Advanced Searching in the Valency Lexicons Using PML-TQ Search Engine</result>
  <result author="Jana Straková">Czech Information Retrieval with Syntax-based Language Models</result>
  <result author="Jiří Mírovský">Annotation Tool for Discourse in PDT</result>
  <result author="Septina Dian Larasati">A Study of Indonesian-to-Malaysian MT </result>
  <result author="Petr Homola">A Method of Hybrid MT for Related Languages</result>
  <result author="Jiří Mírovský">Connective-Based Measuring of the Inter-Annotator Agreement in the Annotation of Discourse in PDT</result>
  <result author="Jernej Vičič">Speeding up the Implementation Process of a Shallow Transfer Machine Translation System</result>
  <result author="Natalia Klyueva">Verbal Valency in the MT Between Related Languages</result>
  <result author="Michal Hrušecký">Automatické rozpoznávání předpon a přípon s pomocí nástroje Affisix</result>
  <result author="Anna Feldman">A resource-light approach to morpho-syntactic tagging</result>
  <result author="Анна Юрьевна Недолужко">Кореферентные отношения в тексте – сравнительный анализ размеченных данных</result>
  <result author="Martin Popel">TectoMT: Modular NLP Framework</result>
  <result author="Patrick Hanks">How People use Words to Make Meanings</result>
  <result author="Ondřej Bojar">Evaluating Utility of Data Sources in a Large Parallel Czech-English Corpus CzEng 0.9</result>
  <result author="Petr Sgall">Nadějný mladý lingvista</result>
  <result author="Ondřej Bojar">2010 Failures in English-Czech Phrase-Based MT</result>
  <result author="Ondřej Bojar">CzEng 0.9 for AppTek</result>
  <result author="David Mareček">Maximum Entropy Translation Model in Dependency-Based MT Framework</result>
  <result author="Natalia Klyueva">Towards Parallel Czech-Russian Dependency Treebank</result>
  <result author="Patrick Hanks">Elliptical Arguments: a Problem in relating Meaning to Use</result>
  <result author="Jiří Mírovský">Annotation Tool for Extended Textual Coreference and Bridging Anaphora</result>
  <result author="Ondřej Bojar">Building a Bilingual ValLex Using Treebank Token Alignment: First Observations</result>
  <result author="Jarmila Panevová">Významné životní jubileum Adely Rechziegelové</result>
  <result author="Petr Sgall">Markéta Lopatková – Zdeněk Žabokrtský – Václava Kettnerová: Valenční slovník českých sloves. Praha: Karolinum, 2008, 381s.</result>
  <result author="Max Jakob">Mapping between Dependency Structures and Compositional Semantic Representations.</result>
  <result author="Otakar Smrž">ElixirFM 2010 (version 1.1.927-1.1.976)</result>
  <result author="Ondřej Bojar">MT via Deep Syntax</result>
  <result author="Ondřej Bojar">UMC002: English-Hindi Parallel Corpus</result>
  <result author="Eva Hajičová">Treebank Annotation</result>
  <result author="Daniel Zeman">Addicter</result>
  <result author="Martin Popel">Strojový překlad přes tektogramatickou rovinu v systému TectoMT</result>
  <result author="Otakar Smrž">The Other Arabic Treebank: Prague Dependencies and Functions</result>
  <result author="Ondřej Bojar">Jak se dělá strojový překlad</result>
  <result author="Eduard Bejček">Annotation of Multiword Expressions in the Prague Dependency Treebank</result>
  <result author="Pavel Pecina">Lexical Association Measures and Collocation Extraction</result>
  <result author="Daniel Zeman">Tagzplorer</result>
  <result author="Petr Sgall">Uvedení do syntaxe (Větná stavba)</result>
  <result author="Markéta Lopatková">Valency Lexicon of Czech Verbs: Towards Formal Description of Valency and Its Modeling in an Electronic Language Resource</result>
  <result author="Zdeněk Žabokrtský">TectoMT - An Open-source Framework for Natural Language Processing</result>
  <result author="Kateřina Veselovská">Členská negace a způsob jejího vyjadřování v současné češtině</result>
  <result author="Zdeněk Žabokrtský">Výzkum strojového překladu v Centru komputační lingvistiky MFF UK</result>
  <result author="Silvie Cinková">The Lexical Population of Semantic Types in Hanks’s PDEV</result>
  <result author="David Mareček">Maximum Entropy Translation Model in Dependency-Based MT Framework</result>
  <result author="Jirka Hana">Resource-light morphological analysis of highly inflective language</result>
  <result author="Bushra Jawaid">UMC005: English-Urdu Parallel Corpus</result>
  <result author="Keith Brendan Hall">Corrective Dependency Parsing</result>
  <result author="Bushra Jawaid">Statistical Machine Translation between Languages with Significant Word Order Difference</result>
  <result author="Michal Novák">Machine Learning Approach to Anaphora Resolution</result>
  <result author="Drahomíra Spoustová">Dependency Parsing as a Sequence Labeling Task</result>
  <result author="Barbora Hladká">An On-Line Game Instead of the Annotation Editor</result>
  <result author="Jarmila Panevová">O kategorii rezul'tativa (prezhde vsego) v cheshskom jazyke</result>
  <result author="Silvie Cinková">Aim and result – A Swedish-Czech comparison of consecutive clauses</result>
  <result author="Václava Kettnerová">Locative semantic diathesis in Czech</result>
  <result author="Pavel Straňák">Annotation of Multiword Expressions in The Prague Dependency Treebank</result>
  <result author="Kateřina Veselovská">On the Structure of Constituent Negation in Czech</result>
  <result author="Petr Sgall">V postoloprtském lágru</result>
  <result author="Jarmila Panevová">Užitečnost jazykových elektronických korpusu a jejich anotování</result>
  <result author="Ondřej Bojar">Vládce jazyků</result>
  <result author="David Mareček">Dependency tree projection across parallel texts</result>
  <result author="Ondřej Bojar">Syntax and Rich Morphology in MT</result>
  <result author="Ondřej Bojar">Aplikace strojového překladu</result>
  <result author="Martin Popel">Treex: Modular NLP Framework</result>
  <result author="Ondřej Bojar">Czech-English-Russian Corpus for AppTek</result>
  <result author="Daniel Zeman">Transliteration of Urdu to Latin Script</result>
  <result author="Ondřej Bojar">English-to-Czech System Combination</result>
  <result author="Kateřina Rysová">An Older Czech Text Corpus for Linguistic Purposes</result>
  <result author="Lucie Mladová">Corpus Linguistics Conference 2009</result>
  <result author="Ondřej Bojar">UMC004: Hindi Web Texts</result>
  <result author="Barbora Hladká">PlayCoref</result>
  <result author="Daniel Zeman">MD-make</result>
  <result author="Alexandr Rosen">Annotating foreign learners’ Czech</result>
  <result author="Nino Peterek">Dialogy.Org 0.4</result>
  <result author="Jirka Hana">Resource-light morphological analysis of inflective languages</result>
  <result author="Michal Novák">Rozpoznávanie rozšírených anaforických vzťahov v češtine</result>
  <result author="Barbora Hladká">Place the Space</result>
  <result author="Jarmila Panevová">Revize morfologických gramatémů pro Pražský závislostní korpus 3.0</result>
  <result author="Barbora Hladká">Shannon game</result>
  <result author="Jan Raab">Compost English 2.0</result>
  <result author="Karel Pala">Český WordNet 1.9 PDT</result>
  <result author="Zdeněk Žabokrtský">TectoMT Machine Translation System</result>
  <result author="Zdeněk Žabokrtský">Introduction to TectoMT</result>
  <result author="Jan Raab">Compost Swedish 1.0</result>
  <result author="Zdeněk Žabokrtský">From Treebanking to Machine Translation</result>
  <result author="Kateřina Rysová">An Older Czech Text Corpus for Linguistic Purposes</result>
  <result author="Jan Raab">Compost Dutch 2.0</result>
  <result author="Jan Štěpánek">Tred Editor and PML-TQ Query Engine and Query Language</result>
  <result author="Markéta Lopatková">Jak počítače „rozumějí“ češtině? Zachycení významu pro zpracování přirozeného jazyka</result>
  <result author="Eduard Bejček">Lexikálně-sémantická anotace PDT pomocí Českého WordNetu</result>
  <result author="Jan Raab">Compost Icelandic 1.0</result>
  <result author="Veronika Kolářová">Valence deverbativních substantiv v češtině (na materiálu substantiv s dativní valencí)</result>
  <result author="Eduard Bejček">Multiword Expressions in PDT 2.0</result>
  <result author="Barbora Hladká">Play the Language: an alternative way of annotation</result>
  <result author="Ondřej Bojar">Improving Translation Model by Monolingual Data</result>
  <result author="Ondřej Hálek">Named Entities from Wikipedia for Machine Translation</result>
  <result author="Nathan David Green">Dependency Parsing</result>
  <result author="Jirka Hana">Capek</result>
  <result author="Jarmila Panevová">Zvláštní případy shody: doplněk u infinitivu</result>
  <result author="Petra Galuščáková">Czech-Slovak Parallel Corpora</result>
  <result author="Bushra Jawaid">Machine Translation with Significant Word Reordering and Rich Target-Side Morphology</result>
  <result author="Natalia Klyueva">Rux Russian Tagger 1.0</result>
  <result author="Johanka Spoustová">Comparable Fora</result>
  <result author="Martin Popel">Influence of Parser Choice on Dependency-Based MT</result>
  <result author="Jarmila Panevová">Delimitation of information between grammatical rules and lexicon</result>
  <result author="Ondřej Bojar">A Grain of Salt for the WMT Manual Evaluation</result>
  <result author="Jarmila Panevová">Nominalizace vyjádřené slovesnými adjektivy</result>
  <result author="Michal Novák">Utilization of Anaphora in Machine Translation</result>
  <result author="Giang Linh Nguy">Coreference Resolution in the Prague Dependency Treebank</result>
  <result author="Barbora Hladká">Syntaktická proměna Českého akademického korpusu</result>
  <result author="David Mareček">Gibbs Sampling with Treeness constraint in Unsupervised Dependency Parsing</result>
  <result author="Svatava Škodová">Víceúrovňová anotace českého žákovského korpusu</result>
  <result author="Anna Vernerová">Nominal Valency in Lexicons</result>
  <result author="Natalia Klyueva">Translating prepositions from Czech into Russian: challenges for the Machine Translation </result>
  <result author="Kateřina Veselovská">CLARA Joint Training Programme: Course on Treebank Annotation </result>
  <result author="Petr Pajas">TrEd 2.0 - newly refactored tree editor</result>
  <result author="Kateřina Rysová">The Word Order of Inner Participants in Czech, Considering the Systemic Ordering of Actor and Patient</result>
  <result author="David Mareček">Unsupervised Dependency Parsing</result>
  <result author="Jarmila Panevová">O rezultativnosti (především) v češtině</result>
  <result author="Jan Hajič">Prague Czech-English Dependency Treebank 2.0</result>
  <result author="David Mareček">Two-step translation with grammatical post-processing</result>
  <result author="Jirka Hana">feat 2011</result>
  <result author="Petr Sgall">Příběh Oskara Sgalla</result>
  <result author="Loganathan Ramasamy">TamilTB - Tamil Dependency Treebank</result>
  <result author="Daniel Zeman">Hierarchical Phrase-Based MT at the Charles University for the WMT 2011 Shared Task</result>
  <result author="Václava Kettnerová">The Lexicographic Representation of Czech Diatheses: Rule Based Approach</result>
  <result author="Nathan David Green">Effects of Noun Phrase Bracketing in Dependency Parsing and Machine Translation</result>
  <result author="Giang Linh Nguy">Unstated Subject Identification in Czech</result>
  <result author="Jirka Hana">A low-budget tagger for Old Czech</result>
  <result author="Marie Mikulová">Korpusy mluvené češtiny a možnosti jejich využití pro poznání rozdílných "světů" mluvenosti a psanosti</result>
  <result author="Matouš Macháček">Approximating a Deep-Syntactic Metric for MT Evaluation and Tuning</result>
  <result author="Kateřina Rysová">Ke slovosledu v konstrukcích s obligatorními participanty (se zaměřením na slovosled patientu a způsobového slovesného doplnění)</result>
  <result author="Pavlína Jínová">Vybrané problematické aspekty konektivních prostředků v rámci anotace mezivýpovědních významových vztahů v PDT </result>
  <result author="Giang Linh Nguy">Coreference of Deletions – The Case of Control</result>
  <result author="David Mareček">HamleDT - HArmonized Multi-LanguagE Dependency Treebank</result>
  <result author="Loganathan Ramasamy">Tamil Dependency Treebank (TamilTB) - 0.1 Annotation Manual </result>
  <result author="Kateřina Veselovská">Členská negace a způsoby jejího vyjadřování v datech ČNK a PDT 2.0</result>
  <result author="Loganathan Ramasamy">TamilTB: An Effort Towards Building a Dependency Treebank for Tamil</result>
  <result author="Zdeněk Žabokrtský">Treex::Core</result>
  <result author="Martin Majliš">W2C - Web To Corpus</result>
  <result author="Anna Nedoluzhko">Annotating Extended Textual Coreference and Bridging Relations in the Prague Dependency Treebank</result>
  <result author="Ondřej Bojar">Evaluating Quality of Machine Translation from Czech to Slovak</result>
  <result author="Petr Pořízka">MorphCon</result>
  <result author="Kateřina Veselovská">Sentence-Level Polarity Detection in a Computer Corpus</result>
  <result author="Zdeněk Žabokrtský">Treex – an open-source framework for natural language processing</result>
  <result author="Jaroslava Hlaváčová">Problém variantních tvarů slov při automatickém zpracování jazyka</result>
  <result author="Jarmila Panevová">Vybrané problémy ze slovesné valence</result>
  <result author="Petr Sgall">Pamětnice Věra Holznerová Jílková</result>
  <result author="Pavlína Jínová">Sentence Structure and Discourse Structure: Possible Parallels</result>
  <result author="Jirka Hana">morph 2011</result>
  <result author="Radek Čech">The role of syntax in complex networks: Local and global importance of verbs in a syntactic dependency network</result>
  <result author="Vladislav Kuboň">Studying Properties of Czech Complex Sentences from an Annotated Corpus</result>
  <result author="Markéta Lopatková">Počítačová lingvistika: Od věty k významu a zase zpátky</result>
  <result author="Jaroslava Hlaváčová">Přirozený jazyk a počítače</result>
  <result author="Ondřej Bojar">Forms Wanted: Training SMT on Monolingual Data</result>
  <result author="Jan Hajič">Pražská databáze mluvené češtiny</result>
  <result author="Ondřej Bojar">Generating Czech Word Forms in MT: From System Combination to Black Art</result>
  <result author="Šárka Zikánová">Information Structure and Word Order Variation in Older Czech</result>
  <result author="David Mareček">Combining Diverse Word-Alignment Symmetrizations Improves Dependency Tree Projection</result>
  <result author="Jan Hajič">Prague Database of Spoken English</result>
  <result author="Loganathan Ramasamy">Tamil dependency parsing: results using rule based and corpus based approaches</result>
  <result author="Eduard Bejček">Influence of Treebank Design on Representation of Multiword Expressions</result>
  <result author="Magda Ševčíková">Anotace souborového významu substantiv v datech Pražského závislostního korpusu</result>
  <result author="Kateřina Veselovská">Kognice 2010: Reprezentace významu</result>
  <result author="Jan Berka">Quiz-Based Evaluation of Machine Translation</result>
  <result author="Jarmila Panevová">Jazykové korpusy – moderní nástroj pro lingvistický výzkum</result>
  <result author="Ondřej Bojar">Analyzing Error Types in English-Czech Machine Translation</result>
  <result author="Václava Kettnerová">Sémantické diateze z lexikografického hlediska</result>
  <result author="Bushra Jawaid">Word-Order Issues in English-to-Urdu Statistical Machine Translation</result>
  <result author="Kateřina Veselovská">GG, FGP, CxG - srovnání metodik (případová studie)</result>
  <result author="Loganathan Ramasamy">TamilTB - An Effort Towards Building a Treebank for Tamil</result>
  <result author="Zdeněk Žabokrtský">Strojový překlad s využitím závislostní syntaxe</result>
  <result author="Jarmila Panevová">Infinitiv ve funkci atributu</result>
  <result author="Jakub Mlynář">Archiv vizuální historie Institutu USC Shoah Foundation a možnosti jeho využití</result>
  <result author="Lucie Mladová">Annotating Discourse in the Prague Dependency Treebank (An Overview)</result>
  <result author="Šárka Zikánová">Interplay of Discourse, Information Structure and Coreference Relations</result>
  <result author="Šárka Zikánová">Some notes on the comparison of the PDTB and PDT discourse annotation</result>
  <result author="Eva Hajičová">Some aspects of the information structure of the sentence </result>
  <result author="Jarmila Panevová">Absolutní a relativní čas v souvětí a vazbách přechodníkových</result>
  <result author="Ondřej Bojar">Word Alignment as a Combinatorial Task</result>
  <result author="Václava Kettnerová">Lokativní sémantická diateze v češtině</result>
  <result author="Petr Sgall">Jazyk, mluvení, psaní</result>
  <result author="Petr Sgall">Ke zkoumání českého jazyka</result>
  <result author="Kateřina Rysová">Valenčnost volných slovesných doplnění</result>
  <result author="Magdaléna Rysová">Problematic relations in the PDT annotation: Explication and Cause </result>
  <result author="Lucie Mladová">Annotating Discourse in PDT</result>
  <result author="Jakub Mlynář">Centrum vizuální historie Malach při Matematicko-fyzikální fakultě Univerzity Karlovy</result>
  <result author="Jarmila Panevová">On Syntax and Semantics of Czech Infinitival Constructions: A Case Study</result>
  <result author="Jarmila Panevová">Problém elipsy: Co s ním a kam s ním?</result>
  <result author="Barbora Hladká">An attractive game with the document: (im)possible?</result>
  <result author="Septina Dian Larasati">Indonesian Morphology Tool (MorphInd): Towards an Indonesian Corpus</result>
  <result author="Jarmila Panevová">Jak se počítají substantiva v češtině: poznámky ke kategorii čísla</result>
  <result author="Kateřina Rysová">The unmarked word order of free verbal modifications in Czech (with the main reference to the influence of verbal valency in the utterance)  </result>
  <result author="Pavel Pecina">Book Reviews: Syntax-Based Collocation Extraction by Violeta Seretan</result>
  <result author="Kateřina Veselovská">A Constructional Analysis of the Constituent Negation in Czech</result>
  <result author="Daniel Zeman">Addicter 2.0</result>
  <result author="Mark Fishel">Automatic Translation Error Analysis</result>
  <result author="Šárka Zikánová">Contrast as a phenomenon of discourse, information structure and coreference</result>
  <result author="Eva Hajičová">A contrastive look at information structure: A corpus probe</result>
  <result author="Šárka Zikánová">New and Given Information in Coreference Chains: Restrictions for Pronominalization and Ellipsis</result>
  <result author="Barbora Štindlová">A Learner Corpus Of Czech: Current State And Future Directions</result>
  <result author="Ondřej Bojar">Jak nachytat strojový překlad na švestkách</result>
  <result author="Jarmila Panevová">Specializirovannyje tipi obstojatel'stv: Grammatikalizirovannyj ellipsis? </result>
  <result author="Eva Hajičová">On interplay of information structure, anaphoric links and discourse relations</result>
  <result author="Jaroslava Hlaváčová">Prefix Recognition Experiments</result>
  <result author="Markéta Lopatková">Semantic Similarity and Syntactic Variability: Valency Lexicon of Czech Verbs</result>
  <result author="Michal Novák">Resolving Noun Phrase Coreference in Czech</result>
  <result author="Magda Ševčíková">Specificity of the number of nouns in Czech and its annotation in Prague Dependency Treebank</result>
  <result author="Eva Hajičová">Computational Linguistics without Linguistics? View from Prague</result>
  <result author="Daniel Zeman">From the Jungle to a Park: Harmonizing Dependency Treebanks of 30 Languages</result>
  <result author="Česlav Przywara">eppex: Epochal Phrase Table Extraction for Statistical Machine Translation</result>
  <result author="Daniel Zeman">Addicter: What Is Wrong with My Translations?</result>
  <result author="Ondřej Bojar">Rich Morphology and What Can We Expect from Hybrid Approaches to MT</result>
  <result author="Marie Mikulová">Významová reprezentace elipsy</result>
  <result author="Pavlína Jínová">Connective Means of Causal Relation in the Prague Dependency Treebank</result>
  <result author="Martin Popel">TectoMT - machine translation system</result>
  <result author="Zdeňka Urešová">Valence sloves v Pražském závislostním korpusu</result>
  <result author="Martin Majliš">W2C - Large Multilingual Corpus</result>
  <result author="Zdeňka Urešová">Valence sloves v Pražském závislostním korpusu</result>
  <result author="Anna Nedoluzhko">Rozšířená textová koreference a asociační anafora (Koncepce anotace českých dat v Pražském závislostním korpusu)</result>
  <result author="Eduard Bejček">Prague Dependency Treebank 2.5</result>
  <result author="Zdeňka Urešová">Valenční slovník Pražského závislostního korpusu (PDT-Vallex)</result>
  <result author="Silvie Cinková">Prague Czech-English Dependency Treebank 2.0 </result>
  <result author="Jan Hajič">Archiv vizuální historie přístupný v Centru Malach</result>
  <result author="Anna Nedoluzhko">Extended Textual Coreference and Bridging Relations in PDT 2.0</result>
  <result author="Nino Peterek">Dialogy.Org 1.0</result>
  <result author="Marie Mikulová">Významová reprezentace elipsy</result>
  <result author="Ondřej Bojar">CzEng 1.0</result>
  <result author="Vladislav Kuboň">Machine Translation Among Related Slavic Languages</result>
  <result author="Jaroslava Hlaváčová">Příklad pravidelných slovotvorných vzorců  v automatickém zpracování češtiny a ruštiny</result>
  <result author="Kateřina Veselovská">Creating annotated resources for polarity classification in Czech</result>
  <result author="Jirka Hana">Getting more data – Schoolkids as annotators</result>
  <result author="James Henderson">Data-Driven Methods for Spoken Language Understanding</result>
  <result author="Ondřej Bojar">Probes in a Taxonomy of Factored Phrase-Based Models</result>
  <result author="Loganathan Ramasamy">Morphological Processing for English-Tamil Statistical Machine Translation</result>
  <result author="Silvie Cinková">Maintaining consistency of monolingual verb entries with interannotator agreement</result>
  <result author="Eva Hajičová">Od kořenů ke stromům: příběh anotovaných korpusů češtiny</result>
  <result author="Eva Hajičová">The Functional Generative Description as a functionally motivated  formal model of language</result>
  <result author="Kateřina Rysová">Možnosti jednotlivých volných slovesných doplnění být obligatorním členem věty </result>
  <result author="Eva Hajičová">Vilém Mathesius and  Functional Sentence Perspective, and beyond</result>
  <result author="Antonio Toral">Retraining Machine Translation with Post-edits to Increase Post-editing Productivity in Content Management Systems</result>
  <result author="Septina Dian Larasati">A Dataset Comparison for an Indonesian-English Statistical Machine Translation System</result>
  <result author="Jan Hajič">Lingvistika na Matematicko-fyzikální fakultě?</result>
  <result author="Oldřich Krůza">Making Community and ASR Join Forces in Web</result>
  <result author="Natalia Klyueva">Comparing Czech and Russian Valency on the Material of Vallex</result>
  <result author="Magda Ševčíková">Sentence Modality Assignment in the Prague Dependency Treebank</result>
  <result author="Filip Jurčíček">Reinforcement learning for spoken dialogue systems using off-policy natural gradient method</result>
  <result author="Natalia Klyueva">Some differences between Czech and Russian: a parallel corpus study</result>
  <result author="Zdeňka Urešová">Building the PDT-VALLEX valency lexicon</result>
  <result author="Barbora Štindlová">CzeSL – an error tagged corpus of Czech as a second language</result>
  <result author="Mohammed Attia">Improved Spelling Error Detection and Correction for Arabic</result>
  <result author="Magda Ševčíková">Predikativum v gramatickém popisu češtiny</result>
  <result author="Johanka Spoustová">A High-Quality Web Corpus of Czech</result>
  <result author="Nathan David Green">Using an SVM Ensemble System for Improved Tamil Dependency Parsing</result>
  <result author="Pavlína Jínová">Analyzing the Most Common Errors in the Discourse Annotation of the Prague Dependency Treebank</result>
  <result author="Mark Fishel">TerrorCat: a Translation Error Categorization-based MT Quality Metric</result>
  <result author="Nathan David Green">Building parallel corpora through social network gaming</result>
  <result author="Ondřej Bojar">The Joy of Parallelism with CzEng 1.0</result>
  <result author="Petr Pajas">Dspace Modifications for Clarin Compatible (EPIC) Handle Service</result>
  <result author="Milica Gašić">Optimisation for POMDP-Based Spoken Dialogue Systems</result>
  <result author="Bushra Jawaid">Tagger Voting for Urdu</result>
  <result author="Kateřina Veselovská">Using Czech-English Parallel Corpora in Automatic Identification of It</result>
  <result author="Raymond Hendy Susanto">Rule-based Machine Translation between Indonesian and Malaysian</result>
  <result author="Jiří Mírovský">Does Tectogrammatics Help the Annotation of Discourse?</result>
  <result author="Eva Hajičová">What we have learned from complex annotation of topic-focus articulation  in a large Czech corpus </result>
  <result author="Václava Kettnerová">The Rule-Based Approach to Czech Grammaticalized Alternations</result>
  <result author="Veronika Kolářová">Valence dějových substantiv odvozených od sloves s předmětovým genitivem</result>
  <result author="Loganathan Ramasamy">Prague Dependency Style Treebank for Tamil</result>
  <result author="Eva Hajičová">Topic-Focus revisited (Through the eyes of the Prague Dependency Treebank)</result>
  <result author="Jarmila Panevová">Ассиметрии между глубинным и поверхностным преставлением предложения (на примере двух типов обстоятельств в чешском языке)</result>
  <result author="Antonio Toral">Efficiency-based Evaluation of Aligners for Industrial Applications</result>
  <result author="Christian Federmann">The ML4HMT Workshop on Optimising the Division of Labour in Hybrid Machine Translation</result>
  <result author="Eduard Bejček">Prague Dependency Treebank 2.5 -- a revisited version of PDT 2.0</result>
  <result author="Daniel Zeman">CUNI: Feature Selection and Error Analysis of a Transition-Based Parser</result>
  <result author="Lucie Poláková">Interplay of Coreference and Discourse Relations: Discourse Connectives with a Referential Component</result>
  <result author="Jirka Hana">Building a Corpus of Old Czech</result>
  <result author="Michal Richter">Korektor – A System for Contextual Spell-checking and Diacritics Completion</result>
  <result author="Aleš Tamchyna">Selecting Data for English-to-Czech Machine Translation</result>
  <result author="Nathan David Green">Hybrid Combination of Constituency and Dependency Trees into an Ensemble Dependency Parser</result>
  <result author="Jan Hajič">Announcing Prague Czech-English Dependency Treebank 2.0</result>
  <result author="Nathan David Green"> Indonesian Dependency Treebank: Annotation and Parsing</result>
  <result author="František Martínek">On a Corpus of Older Czech Texts and Its Usage</result>
  <result author="Jan Berka">Automatic MT Error Analysis: Hjerson Helping Addicter</result>
  <result author="Petra Galuščáková">Application of Topic Segmentation in Audiovisual Information Retrieval</result>
  <result author="Martin Majliš">Yet Another Language Identifier</result>
  <result author="Magdaléna Rysová">Alternative Lexicalizations of Discourse Connectives in Czech</result>
  <result author="Petra Galuščáková">Penalty Functions for Evaluation Measures of Unsegmented Speech Retrieval</result>
  <result author="Jirka Hana">Building a learner corpus</result>
  <result author="David Mareček">Unsupervised Dependency Parsing using Reducibility and Fertility features</result>
  <result author="Petra Galuščáková">Improving SMT by Using Parallel Data of a Closely Related Language</result>
  <result author="Vladislav Kuboň">On Formalization of Word Order Properties</result>
  <result author="Rudolf Rosa">Dependency Relations Labeller for Czech</result>
  <result author="Martin Majliš">Language Richness of the Web</result>
  <result author="Septina Dian Larasati">Towards an Indonesian-English SMT System: A Case Study of an Under-Studied and Under-Resourced Language, Indonesian</result>
  <result author="Septina Dian Larasati">Improving Word Alignment by Exploiting Adapted Word Similarity</result>
  <result author="Septina Dian Larasati">IDENTIC Corpus: Morphologically Enriched Indonesian-English Parallel Corpus</result>
  <result author="Ondřej Dušek">Formemes in English-Czech Deep Syntactic MT</result>
  <result author="Jirka Hana">Prague Markup Language Framework</result>
  <result author="Pavlína Jínová">Nejčastější konektivní prostředky kauzálního vztahu v Pražském závislostním korpusu</result>
  <result author="Eva Hajičová">On scalarity in information structure</result>
  <result author="Martin Holub">Tailored Feature Extraction for Lexical Disambiguation of English Verbs Based on Corpus Pattern Analysis</result>
  <result author="Václava Kettnerová">The Syntax-Semantics Interface of Czech Verbs in the Valency Lexicon</result>
  <result author="Ondřej Bojar">Towards a Predicate-Argument Evaluation for MT</result>
  <result author="Vladislav Kuboň">Studying Formal Properties of a Free Word Order Language</result>
  <result author="Pavel Pecina">Domain Adaptation of Statistical Machine Translation using Web-Crawled Resources: a Case Study</result>
  <result author="Kateřina Veselovská">Sentence-Level Sentiment Analysis in Czech</result>
  <result author="Mark Fishel">Terra: a Collection of Translation Error-Annotated Corpora</result>
  <result author="Silvie Cinková">A database of semantic clusters of verb usages</result>
  <result author="Silvie Cinková">Managing Uncertainty in Semantic Tagging</result>
  <result author="Zdeněk Žabokrtský">Machine Translation using Dependency Trees</result>
  <result author="Kateřina Veselovská">Mezinárodní konference závislostní lingvistiky Depling 2011 v Barceloně</result>
  <result author="Pavlína Jínová">Semi-Automatic Annotation of Intra-Sentential Discourse Relations in PDT</result>
  <result author="Petra Galuščáková">CUNI at MediaEval 2012 Search and Hyperlinking Task</result>
  <result author="Silvie Cinková">Optimizing semantic granularity for NLP -  report on a lexicographic experiment</result>
  <result author="David Mareček">Exploiting Reducibility in Unsupervised Dependency Parsing</result>
  <result author="Loganathan Ramasamy">The Study of Effect of Length in Morphological Segmentation of Agglutinative Languages</result>
  <result author="Barbora Vidová Hladká">Syntactic annotation of transcriptions in the Czech Academic Corpus: Then and now</result>
  <result author="Barbora Štindlová">Annotating foreign learners’ Czech</result>
  <result author="Daniel Zeman">Intersecting Parallel Corpora</result>
  <result author="Daniel Zeman">Data Issues of the Multilingual Translation Matrix</result>
  <result author="Christian Federmann">Towards Optimal Choice Selection for Improved Hybrid Machine Translation</result>
  <result author="Rudolf Rosa">DEPFIX: A System for Automatic Correction of Czech MT Outputs</result>
  <result author="Niraj Aswani">Khresmoi: Multimodal Multilingual Medical Information Search</result>
  <result author="Eleftherios Avramidis">A Richly Annotated, Multilingual Parallel Corpus for Hybrid Machine Translation</result>
  <result author="Petr Karlík">České syntaktické bádání od Šmilauera po dnešek očima Prahy a Brna</result>
  <result author="Tomáš Jelínek">Combining Manual and Automatic Annotation of a Learner Corpus</result>
  <result author="Vladislav Kuboň">How to Measure Word Order Freedom for Natural Languages?</result>
  <result author="Rudolf Rosa">Using Parallel Features in Parsing of Machine-Translated Sentences for Correction of Grammatical Errors</result>
  <result author="Pavel Pecina">Simple and Effective Parameter Tuning for Domain Adaptation of Statistical Machine Translation</result>
  <result author="Daniel Zeman">HamleDT: To Parse or Not to Parse?</result>
  <result author="Khaled Shaalan">Arabic Word Generation and Modelling for Spell Checking</result>
  <result author="Ondřej Bojar">Wild Experimenting in Machine Translation</result>
  <result author="Pavel Pecina">Lexical Association Measures: Collocation Extraction</result>
  <result author="Ondřej Bojar">Udělá za vás strojový překlad domácí úkol?</result>
  <result author="Jarmila Panevová">Světová slavistika utrpěla citelné ztráty</result>
  <result author="Daniel Zeman">Multilingual SMT: Data, Data, Data…</result>
  <result author="Markéta Lopatková">Annotation of sentence structure: Capturing the relationship between clauses in Czech sentences</result>
  <result author="Ondřej Bojar">Scientific Report on Rich Tree-Based SMT</result>
  <result author="Kateřina Veselovská">Annotating Sentence-Level Polarity in Czech</result>
  <result author="Kateřina Veselovská">Between Good and Evil: Sentence-Level Sentiment Analysis in Czech</result>
  <result author="Lucie Poláková">Annotating Discourse in Prague Dependency Treebank</result>
  <result author="David Mareček">Unsupervised Dependency parsing</result>
  <result author="Václava Kettnerová">Mapping Semantic Information from FrameNet onto VALLEX</result>
  <result author="Zdeněk Žabokrtský">Conversion of Copenhagen Dependency Treebank into Treex</result>
  <result author="Petra Galuščáková">Manually Classified Errors in English-Slovak Translation</result>
  <result author="Petra Galuščáková">English-Slovak Parallel Corpus</result>
  <result author="Kateřina Veselovská">Paralelní závislostní korpusy - the low hanging fruit?</result>
  <result author="Petra Galuščáková">Česko-slovenský paralelný korpus</result>
  <result author="Petra Galuščáková">WMT 2011 Testing Set in Slovak</result>
  <result author="Jakub Mlynář">Vzdělávací využití videozáznamů rozhovorů s pamětníky z Archivu vizuální historie Institutu USC Shoah Foundation</result>
  <result author="Petra Galuščáková">Manually Classified Errors in Czech-Slovak Translation</result>
  <result author="Pavel Pecina">Cross-Language Speech Retrieval and its Evaluation in the Malach Project</result>
  <result author="Ondřej Bojar">Manually ranked outputs of Czech-Slovak translations</result>
  <result author="Jirka Hana">Building an Error-tagged Learner Corpus of Czech</result>
  <result author="Magdaléna Rysová">Alternativní vyjádření konektorů v češtině</result>
  <result author="Jarmila Panevová">Dva pohledy na vývoj českého poválečného syntaktického myšlení</result>
  <result author="Václava Kettnerová">Lexikálně-sémantické konverze ve valenčním slovníku</result>
  <result author="Václava Kettnerová">Syntaktické konstrukce typu Včely se hemží na zahradě – Zahrada se hemží včelami</result>
  <result author="Kateřina Rysová">On sentence information structure in Czech: the usual sentence position of particular sentence components</result>
  <result author="Albert Kim">Concurrent effects of lexical status and letter-rotation during early stages of visual word recognition: evidence from ERPs</result>
  <result author="Kateřina Veselovská">Subjective Frames: A Possible Extension of CxG Structures</result>
  <result author="Michal Novák">Utilization of context in Machine Translation</result>
  <result author="Kateřina Veselovská">Automatická detekce hodnocení v textu: nástroje a data</result>
  <result author="Eva Hajičová">Grammatical Information in Lexicon: A Case Study</result>
  <result author="Natalia Klyueva">Czech-Russian corpus via a simple web interface</result>
  <result author="David Mareček">Unsupervised Dependency Parsing</result>
  <result author="Jarmila Panevová">The Development of PDT 3.0</result>
  <result author="Ondřej Bojar">Strojový překlad</result>
  <result author="Ondřej Bojar">The Czech Language in the Digital Age</result>
  <result author="Nathan David Green">Effects of Noun Phrase Bracketing in Dependency Parsing and Machine Translation</result>
  <result author="Barbora Vidová Hladká">Učíme počítače (nejen) česky: přehled aplikací z ÚFALu</result>
  <result author="Jiří Maršík">TrTok: A Fast and Trainable Tokenizer for Natural Languages</result>
  <result author="Magdaléna Rysová">On Discourse Annotation in PDT</result>
  <result author="Lucie Poláková">Learning about Connectives from Syntactic Annotation</result>
  <result author="Ondřej Bojar">Jak se dělá strojový překlad</result>
  <result author="Jirka Hana">Resource-light Approaches to Computational Morphology Part 1: Monolingual Approaches</result>
  <result author="Nathan David Green">Data Mining in NLP</result>
  <result author="Magdaléna Rysová">Discourse Connectives and Their Alternative Lexicalizations in Czech</result>
  <result author="Jarmila Panevová">Koordinace vs. determinace (Forma nebo význam?)</result>
  <result author="Ondřej Bojar">Generace strojového překladu</result>
  <result author="Kateřina Veselovská">Automatic polarity classification systems for Czech</result>
  <result author="Lucie Poláková">Prague Discourse Treebank 1.0</result>
  <result author="Jaroslava Hlaváčová">Učíme stroje česky</result>
  <result author="Michal Novák">Introducing context lexical models to TectoMT</result>
  <result author="Kateřina Veselovská">K morfologické kategorizaci českých evaluativních výrazů</result>
  <result author="Ondřej Bojar">Additional German-Czech reference translations of the WMT'11 test set</result>
  <result author="Nino Peterek">Dialogy.Org 1.1</result>
  <result author="Lucie Poláková">Manual for Annotation of Discourse Relations in Prague Dependency Treebank</result>
  <result author="Nathan David Green">Ensemble Parsing and its Effect on Machine Translation</result>
  <result author="Ondřej Bojar">Čeština a strojový překlad</result>
  <result author="Ondřej Bojar">eman</result>
  <result author="Markéta Lopatková">VALLEX 2.6</result>
  <result author="Jan Hajič, jr.">Developing Sentiment Annotator in UIMA – the Unstructured Management Architecture for Data Mining Applications</result>
  <result author="Rudolf Rosa">Deepfix: Statistical Post-editing of Statistical Machine Translation Using Deep Syntactic Analysis</result>
  <result author="Eva Hajičová">Vilém Mathesius and functional sentence perspective, and beyond</result>
  <result author="Vincent Kríž">JTagger - Automatic Reference Recognition in Court Decisions</result>
  <result author="Ondřej Bojar">Chimera – Three Heads for English-to-Czech Translation</result>
  <result author="Anna Nedoluzhko">Generic noun phrases and annotation of coreference and bridging  relations in the Prague Dependency Treebank</result>
  <result author="Lubomír Krčmář">Determining Compositionality of Word Expressions Using Various Word Space Models and Measures</result>
  <result author="Nathan David Green">Improvements to Syntax-based Machine Translation using Ensemble Dependency Parsers</result>
  <result author="Ondřej Dušek">Towards a Truly Statistical Natural Language Generator for Spoken Dialogues</result>
  <result author="Matouš Macháček">Results of the WMT13 Metrics Shared Task</result>
  <result author="Eva Hajičová">Ke stratifikačnímu modelování jazyka</result>
  <result author="Petra Galuščáková">CUNI at MediaEval 2013 Search and Hyperlinking Task</result>
  <result author="Jarmila Panevová">Vzpomínka na Světlu Čmejrkovou</result>
  <result author="Veronika Kolářová">Adverbální předmětový genitiv a jeho protějšky v nominálních konstrukcích: Případ posesiva</result>
  <result author="Pavlína Jínová">Subordinators with Elaborative Meanings in Czech and English</result>
  <result author="Jana Straková">A New State-of-The-Art Czech Named Entity Recognizer</result>
  <result author="Anna Nedoluzhko">Annotators’ Certainty and Disagreements in Coreference and Bridging Annotation in Prague Dependency Treebank</result>
  <result author="Marie Mikulová">Úpravy a doplňky Pražského závislostního korpusu (Od PDT 2.0 k PDT 3.0)</result>
  <result author="Niraj Aswani">Khresmoi - multilingual semantic search of medical text and images</result>
  <result author="Lubomír Krčmář">Determining Compositionality of Word Expressions Using Word Space Models</result>
  <result author="Eduard Bejček">Syntactic Identification of Occurrences of Multiword Expressions in Text using a Lexicon with Dependency Structures</result>
  <result author="Ondřej Bojar">Scratching the Surface of Possible Translations</result>
  <result author="Lucie Poláková">Introducing the Prague Discourse Treebank 1.0</result>
  <result author="Thomas Meyer">Machine Translation with Many Manually Labeled Discourse Connectives</result>
  <result author="Jana Šindlerová">Building a Corpus of Evaluative Sentences in Multiple Domains</result>
  <result author="Jana Šindlerová">Verb Valency and Argument Non-correspondence in a Bilingual Treebank</result>
  <result author="Jarmila Panevová">A Message Sent to Heaven</result>
  <result author="Martin Nečaský">Linked Open Data for Legislative Domain - Ontology and Experimental Data</result>
  <result author="Kateřina Veselovská">Czech Subjectivity Lexicon: A Lexical Resource for Czech Polarity Classification</result>
  <result author="Franky  ">A Rule-based Approach for Karmina Generation</result>
  <result author="Eva Hajičová">Professor Ladislav Matejka (1919-2012) passed away</result>
  <result author="Silvie Cinková">Rule-Based Extraction of English Verb Collocates from a Dependency-Parsed Corpus</result>
  <result author="Otakar Smrž">Prague Arabic Dependency Treebank 1.5</result>
  <result author="Vladislav Kuboň">A Case Study of a Free Word Order</result>
  <result author="Natalia Klyueva">Usage of some non-finite constructions in Czech and Russian</result>
  <result author="Jiří Mírovský">(Pre-)Annotation of Topic-Focus Articulation in Prague Czech-English Dependency Treebank</result>
  <result author="Anna Nedoluzhko">A Coreferentially annotated Corpus and Anaphora Resolution for Czech</result>
  <result author="Michal Novák">Translation of "It" in a Deep Syntax Framework</result>
  <result author="Kateřina Veselovská">Why Words Alone Are Not Enough: Error Analysis of Lexicon-based Polarity Classifier for Czech</result>
  <result author="Michal Kalina"> Jak překladač z Matfyzu porazil Google</result>
  <result author="Alexandr Rosen">Evaluating and automating the annotation of a learner corpus</result>
  <result author="Magdaléna Rysová">K explikativním vztahům v češtině </result>
  <result author="Magda Ševčíková">Productivity of selected deadjectival suffixes in Czech</result>
  <result author="Martin Popel">Coordination Structures in Dependency Treebanks</result>
  <result author="Nathan David Green">WMT Dependency Annotations 0.1</result>
  <result author="Ondřej Bojar">Findings of the 2013 Workshop on Statistical Machine Translation</result>
  <result author="Katsiaryna Aharodnik">Automatic Identification of Learners’ Language Background based on their Writing in Czech</result>
  <result author="Thành Long Dương">Simpler unsupervised POS tagging with bilingual projections</result>
  <result author="Martin Plátek">Formalization of Word-Order Shifts by Restarting Automata</result>
  <result author="Niraj Aswani">Khresmoi Professional: Multilingual Semantic Search for Medical Professionals</result>
  <result author="Thành Long Dương">Increasing the quality and quantity of source language data for unsupervised cross-lingual POS tagging.</result>
  <result author="David Mareček">Stop-probability estimates computed on a large corpus improve Unsupervised Dependency Parsing</result>
  <result author="Jana Straková">Czech Named Entity Corpus, version 2.0</result>
  <result author="Matěj Korvas">Correspondence Seminar: Bringing Linguistics to High Schools</result>
  <result author="Aleš Tamchyna">Utilizing Source Context in Statistical Machine Translation</result>
  <result author="Ondřej Dušek">Robust Multilingual Statistical Morphological Generation Models</result>
  <result author="Barbora Štindlová">A learner corpus of Czech: current state and future directions</result>
  <result author="Katrin Wisniewski">MERLIN: An Online Trilingual Learner Corpus Empirically Grounding the European Reference Levels in Authentic Learner </result>
  <result author="Barbora Hladká">Feature Engineering in the NLI Shared Task 2013: Charles University Submission Report</result>
  <result author="Jarmila Panevová">The Role of Grammatical Constraints in Lexical Component in Functional Generative Description</result>
  <result author="Petra Barančíková">Lexical Paraphrasing for Improvement of MT Evaluation</result>
  <result author="Šárka Zikánová">Text annotations in the Prague Dependency Treebank</result>
  <result author="Petra Galuščáková">PhraseFix: Statistical Post-Editing of TectoMT</result>
  <result author="Kateřina Veselovská">Czech SubLex 1.0</result>
  <result author="Jaroslava Hlaváčová">Special domain data mining through DBpedia on the example of Biology</result>
  <result author="Vincent Kríž">Detecting Semantic Relations in Texts and Their Integration with External Data Resources</result>
  <result author="Petra Galuščáková">CUNI at MediaEval 2013 Similar Segments in Social Speech Task</result>
  <result author="Anna Nedoluzhko">How Dependency Trees and Tectogrammatics Help Annotating Coreference and Bridging Relations in Prague Dependency Treebank</result>
  <result author="Anna Vernerová">Towards Automatic Detection of Applicable Diatheses</result>
  <result author="Magda Ševčíková">Česká adverbia s příponou -o v teoretickém popisu a v syntakticky anotovaném korpusu</result>
  <result author="Michal Novák">Two Case Studies on Translating Pronouns in a Deep Syntax Framework</result>
  <result author="Jan Hajič">Joint Morphological and Syntactic Analysis for Richly Inflected Languages</result>
  <result author="Jaroslava Hlaváčová">Intensifying Verb Prefix Patterns in Czech and Russian</result>
  <result author="Karel Bílek">Exploiting Maching Learning for Automatic Semantic Feature Assignment</result>
  <result author="Václava Kettnerová">Corpus Based Identification of Czech Light Verbs</result>
  <result author="Veronika Kolářová">Agents Expressed by Prepositionless Instrumental Modifying Czech Nouns Derived from Intransitive Verbs</result>
  <result author="Kateřina Rysová">K subjektivnímu slovosledu na základě korpusu</result>
  <result author="Magda Ševčíková">Deadjektivní deriváty v češtině jako deriváty syntaktické vs. lexikální</result>
  <result author="Karel Bílek">CUni Multilingual Matrix in the WMT 2013 Shared Task</result>
  <result author="Zdeňka Urešová">An Analysis of Annotation of Verb-Noun Idiomatic Combinations in a Parallel Dependency Corpus</result>
  <result author="Marie Mikulová"> From PDT 2.0 to PDT 3.0 (Modifications and Complements)</result>
  <result author="Vladislav Kuboň">Automatic Processing of Linguistic Data as a Feedback for Linguistic Theory</result>
  <result author="Václava Kettnerová">The Representation of Czech Light Verb Constructions in a Valency Lexicon</result>
  <result author="Lukáš Žilka">Comparison of Bayesian Discriminative and Generative Models for Dialogue State Tracking</result>
  <result author="Marie Mikulová">Anotace na tektogramatické rovině. Dodatky k anotátorské příručce (s ohledem na anotování PDTSC a PCEDT)</result>
  <result author="Maria Eskevich">Multimedia Information Seeking through Search and Hyperlinking</result>
  <result author="Pavel Pecina">Jörg Tiedemann: Bitext Alignment</result>
  <result author="Kateřina Rysová">Skončil 39. ročník Olympiády v českém jazyce</result>
  <result author="Patrick Hanks">Lexical analysis: Norms and Exploitations</result>
  <result author="Ondřej Bojar">Naučíme počítač (cizí) řeči?</result>
  <result author="David Mareček">Cross-language Study on Influence of Coordination Style on Dependency Parsing Performance</result>
  <result author="Tereza Burianová">Počítače asi nikdy nahradí lidského korektora ani překladatele </result>
  <result author="Barbora Hladká">Čapek a iPad v jedné kapse</result>
  <result author="Jan Berka">Tools for Machine Translation Quality Inspection</result>
  <result author="Aleš Tamchyna">No Free Lunch in Factored Phrase-Based Machine Translation</result>
  <result author="Jakub Mlynář">Nový archiv nahrávek rozhovorů v Centru vizuální historie Malach </result>
  <result author="David Vaughan">Dressing up the woman of sticks: the delightful ambiguities of Czech machine translation</result>
  <result author="Magdaléna Rysová">Automatická předanotace TFA v české části PCEDT</result>
  <result author="Veronika Kolářová">Substantiva odvozená od sloves s předmětovým genitivem a jejich přínos k teorii valence substantiv</result>
  <result author="Pavlína Jínová">Anotace textových jevů v Pražském závislostním korpusu</result>
  <result author="Kateřina Rysová">Povrchový slovosled kontextově nezapojených participantů na základě dat v PDT</result>
  <result author="Jirka Hana">Building an Error-tagged Learner Corpus of Czech</result>
  <result author="Ondřej Bojar">The Design of Eman, an Experiment Manager</result>
  <result author="Jaroslava Hlaváčová">Review of the book "Morfologie českého slovesa a tvoření deverbativ jako problém strojové analýzy češtiny"</result>
  <result author="Kateřina Veselovská">Textové jevy v lingvistických aplikacích</result>
  <result author="Martin Popel">Machine Translation Zoo: Tree-to-tree transfer and Discriminative learning</result>
  <result author="Martin Nečaský">Halfway through the INTLIB project</result>
  <result author="Jarmila Panevová">Elipsa (aneb co v korpusu nenajdeme)</result>
  <result author="Jakub Mlynář">Výroční setkání Centra vizuální historie Malach - 28. 1. 2013 </result>
  <result author="Rudolf Rosa">Automatic post-editing of phrase-based machine translation outputs</result>
  <result author="Kateřina Rysová">K anotaci aktuálního členění větného v korpusu Prague Czech-English Dependency Treebank </result>
  <result author="Kateřina Veselovská">Postojová analýza ve forenzní lingvistice a stylometrii</result>
  <result author="Loganathan Ramasamy">EnTam: An English-Tamil Parallel Corpus</result>
  <result author="Kateřina Veselovská">Jazyk emocí - emoce v jazyce</result>
  <result author="Ondřej Bojar">Výzkum na ÚFALu</result>
  <result author="Kateřina Veselovská">Modelling Evaluative Meaning in Czech </result>
  <result author="Eva Hajičová">Tracing salience in the Prague Dependency Treebank </result>
  <result author="Petra Galuščáková"> Segmentation strategies for passage retrieval in audio-visual documents</result>
  <result author="Veronika Kolářová">Czech nouns derived from verbs with an objective genitive: Their contribution to the theory of valency</result>
  <result author="Jan Štěpánek">Querying Dependency Treebanks in PML-TQ </result>
  <result author="Jarmila Panevová">Trebovanija grammatičeskogo komponenta k leksičeskoj informacii v slovare</result>
  <result author="Barbora Hladká">A Gentle Introduction to Machine Learning in NLP using R</result>
  <result author="Jarmila Panevová">Slovníková informace a její použití v gramatice (na příkladu českého slovesa)</result>
  <result author="Jiří Mírovský">Prague Dependency Treebank as a prototype for multilingual corpora</result>
  <result author="Jirka Hana">Computational Morphology</result>
  <result author="Jan Štěpánek">Práce s Pražským závislostním korpusem</result>
  <result author="Aleš Tamchyna">MTMonkey 1.0</result>
  <result author="Martin Popel">Treex Tutorial</result>
  <result author="Natalia Klyueva">Machine Translation between Czech and Russian</result>
  <result author="Ondřej Bojar">Strojový překlad lepší než Google</result>
  <result author="Kateřina Veselovská">Využití korpusu InterCorp při vytváření ručních pravidel pro automatickou detekci pleonastického it  a jeho českých ekvivalentů v závislostních datech</result>
  <result author="Rudolf Rosa">Error Correction of PB SMT Outputs with automatic post-editing shown on English to Czech translation</result>
  <result author="Kateřina Rysová">On Contextual Boundness in PDT</result>
  <result author="Markéta Lopatková">Nestrukturovaná data:Jak popsat přirozený jazyk?</result>
  <result author="Markéta Lopatková">Zachycení nezachytitelného: Syntaktické vztahy v přirozeném jazyce a jejich formální reprezentace.</result>
  <result author="Aleš Tamchyna">Moses Toolkit and our Eman, experiment manager</result>
  <result author="Andrea Abel">A Trilingual Learner Corpus illustrating European Reference Levels</result>
  <result author="Aleš Tamchyna">MTMonkey: A Scalable Infrastructure for a Machine Translation Web Service</result>
  <result author="Kateřina Rysová">Ke slovosledu a k aktuálnímu členění na základě Pražského závislostního korpusu</result>
  <result author="Ondřej Bojar">Korpusy a překladové modely pro společnost Lingea</result>
  <result author="Jakub Mlynář">Visual History Archive in the Social Scientific Research: Some remarks and experiences from the user's perspective</result>
  <result author="Martin Popel">Treex vs. NIF</result>
  <result author="Daniel Zeman">Twenty Flavors of One Text</result>
  <result author="Rudolf Rosa">Depfix: Automatic post-editing of phrase-based machine translation outputs</result>
  <result author="Magda Ševčíková">Slovotvorná produktivita: deadjektivní přípony odvozující názvy vlastností</result>
  <result author="Kateřina Rysová">K zásadám anotace aktuálního členění v Pražském česko-anglickém  závislostním korpusu</result>
  <result author="Jaroslava Hlaváčová">Budeme si rozumět?</result>
  <result author="Daniel Zeman">CzechMate: strojový překlad do češtiny</result>
  <result author="Ondřej Plátek">PyKaldi - v1.0</result>
  <result author="Václava Kettnerová">Lexikalizované alternace v češtině</result>
  <result author="Daniel Zeman">Lingvistické nástroje a data na ÚFALu</result>
  <result author="Vincent Kríž">Detecting Entity Relations in Texts</result>
  <result author="Eduard Bejček">Prague Dependency Treebank 3.0</result>
  <result author="Filip Jurčíček">Alex Dialogue Systems Framework - v0.1 </result>
  <result author="Loganathan Ramasamy">TamilTB - Tamil Dependency Treebank 1.0</result>
  <result author="Marie Mikulová">Liší se mluvené a psané texty ve valenci?</result>
  <result author="Nathan David Green">Votter Corpus: A Corpus of Social Polling Language</result>
  <result author="Kateřina Veselovská">On Linguistic Structure of Evaluative Meaning</result>
  <result author="Jan Švec">MCLAAS - integrovaný systém vyhledávání ve vícejazyčném audioarchívu</result>
  <result author="Magdaléna Rysová">Use of Coreference in Automatic Searching for Multiword Discourse Markers in the Prague Dependency Treebank</result>
  <result author="Eva Hajičová">Three dimensions of the so-called "interoperability" of annotation schemes</result>
  <result author="Filip Jurčíček">Alex: A Statistical Dialogue Systems Framework</result>
  <result author="Zdeňka Urešová">Multilingual Test Sets for Machine Translation of Search Queries for Cross-Lingual Information Retrieval in the Medical Domain</result>
  <result author="Matěj Korvas">Free English and Czech telephone speech corpus shared under the CC-BY-SA 3.0 license</result>
  <result author="Kateřina Veselovská">Fear and Trembling: Annotating Emotions in Czech Holocaust Testimonies</result>
  <result author="Bushra Jawaid">English to Urdu Statistical Machine Translation: Establishing a Baseline</result>
  <result author="Shadi Saleh">CUNI at the ShARe/CLEF eHealth Evaluation Lab 2014</result>
  <result author="Ondřej Dušek">Verbal Valency Frame Detection and Selection in Czech and English</result>
  <result author="Anna Nedoluzhko">Annotation of coreference in Prague Czech-English Dependency Treebank</result>
  <result author="Eduard Šubert">Twitter Crowd Translation -- Design and Objectives</result>
  <result author="Matouš Macháček">Results of the WMT14 Metrics Shared Task</result>
  <result author="Andrea Abel">A Trilingual Learner Corpus illustrating European Reference Levels</result>
  <result author="Martin Plátek">On Minimalism of Analysis by Reduction by Restarting Automata</result>
  <result author="Jiří Mírovský">What can linguists learn from some simple statistics on annotated treebanks</result>
  <result author="Rudolf Rosa">HamleDT 2.0: Thirty Dependency Treebanks Stanfordized</result>
  <result author="Jaroslava Hlaváčová">Vyjádření intenzity slovesného děje pomocí předpon</result>
  <result author="Natalia Pletneva">Observations and Lessons Learnt from Non Health Professionals Evaluating a Health Search Engine </result>
  <result author="Václava Kettnerová">Lexikálně-sémantické konverze ve valenčním slovníku</result>
  <result author="Loganathan Ramasamy">Cross-lingual dependency transfer with harmonized Indian language treebanks</result>
  <result author="Petra Galuščáková">CUNI at MediaEval 2014 Search and Hyperlinking Task: Search Task Experiments</result>
  <result author="Ondřej Bojar">HindEnCorp – Hindi-English and Hindi-only Corpus for Machine Translation</result>
  <result author="Aleš Tamchyna">CUNI in WMT14: Chimera Still Awaits Bellerophon</result>
  <result author="Vladislav Kuboň">A Comparison of MT Methods for Closely Related Languages: a Case Study on Czech – Slovak Language Pair</result>
  <result author="Ondřej Plátek">Integration of an On-line Kaldi Speech Recogniser to the Alex Dialogue Systems Framework</result>
  <result author="Martin Plátek">On the Complexity of Reductions by Restarting Automata.</result>
  <result author="Ondřej Bojar">Findings of the 2014 Workshop on Statistical Machine Translation</result>
  <result author="Jirka Hana">Sentence diagrams: their evaluation and combination</result>
  <result author="Loganathan Ramasamy">Multilingual Dependency Parsing: Using Machine Translated Texts instead of Parallel Corpora</result>
  <result author="Magda Ševčíková">Building a database of Czech derived words</result>
  <result author="Magda Ševčíková">Word-Formation Network for Czech</result>
  <result author="Petra Barančíková">Machine Translation within One Language as a Paraphrasing Technique</result>
  <result author="Jarmila Panevová">Delimitation of information between grammatical rules and lexicon</result>
  <result author="Adriane Boyd">The MERLIN corpus: Learner language and the CEFR</result>
  <result author="Markéta Lopatková">Gramatické závislosti vs. koordinace z pohledu redukční analýzy</result>
  <result author="Pavel Pecina">Khresmoi Query Translation Test Data 1.0</result>
  <result author="Kateřina Rysová">Ohlédnutí za jubilejním 40. ročníkem Olympiády v českém jazyce</result>
  <result author="Rudolf Kadlec">Knowledge-based Dialog State Tracking</result>
  <result author="Kateřina Rysová">Valency and Word Order in Czech ― A Corpus Probe</result>
  <result author="Lucie Poláková">Genres in the Prague Discourse Treebank</result>
  <result author="Vincent Kríž">Data Extraction Using NLP Techniques and Its Transformation to Linked Data</result>
  <result author="Jiří Mírovský">Discourse Relations in the Prague Dependency Treebank 3.0</result>
  <result author="Kateřina Veselovská">ÚFAL: Using Hand-crafted Rules in Aspect Based Sentiment Analysis on Parsed Data</result>
  <result author="Ondřej Plátek">Free on-line speech recogniser based on Kaldi ASR toolkit producing word posterior lattices</result>
  <result author="Eva Hajičová">Charles Fillmore has passed away</result>
  <result author="Michal Novák">Cross-lingual Coreference Resolution of Pronouns</result>
  <result author="Rudolf Rosa">Depfix Manual</result>
  <result author="Magda Ševčíková">Kvalitativní a nekvalitativní význam substantiv s příponou -ost</result>
  <result author="Jana Šindlerová">Resources in Conflict: A Bilingual Valency Lexicon vs. a Bilingual Treebank vs. a Linguistic Theory</result>
  <result author="Bushra Jawaid">A Tagged Corpus and a Tagger for Urdu</result>
  <result author="Magda Ševčíková">Zjišťování slovotvorné produktivity z korpusových dat: přípony odvozující názvy vlastností</result>
  <result author="Rudolf Rosa">Depfix, Automatic Post-editing of SMT</result>
  <result author="Lorraine Goeuriot">ShARe/CLEF eHealth Evaluation Lab 2014, Task 3: User-centred health information retrieval</result>
  <result author="Bushra Jawaid">Two-Step Machine Translation with Lattices</result>
  <result author="Eduard Bejček">Automatic Mapping Lexical Resources: A Lexical Unit as the Keystone</result>
  <result author="Jana Šindlerová">Tracing Sentiments: Syntactic and Semantic Features in a Subjectivity Lexicon </result>
  <result author="Ondřej Dušek">Machine Translation of Medical Texts in the Khresmoi Project</result>
  <result author="Nianwen Xue">Not an Interlingua, But Close: Comparison of English AMRs to Chinese and Czech</result>
  <result author="Václava Kettnerová">An Interplay between Valency Information and Reflexivity</result>
  <result author="Koenraad De Smedt">CLARA: A New Generation of Researchers in Common Language Resources and Their Applications</result>
  <result author="Petra Barančíková">Parmesan: Meteor without Paraphrases with Paraphrased References</result>
  <result author="Marie Mikulová">Annotation on the tectogrammatical level. Additions to annotation manual (with respect to PDTSC and PCEDT)</result>
  <result author="Vincent Kríž">Statistical Recognition of References in Czech Court Decisions</result>
  <result author="Jindřich Libovický">Tolerant BLEU: a Submission to the WMT14 Metrics Task</result>
  <result author="Lucie Poláková">K možnostem korpusového zpracování nadvětných jevů</result>
  <result author="Stephan Oepen">SemEval 2014 Task 8: Broad-Coverage Semantic Dependency Parsing</result>
  <result author="Daniela Majchráková">Semi-automatic Detection of Multiword Expressions in the Slovak Dependency Treebank</result>
  <result author="Zdeňka Urešová">Comparing Czech and English AMRs</result>
  <result author="Yusuke Miyao">In-House: An Ensemble of Pre-Existing Off-the-Shelf Parsers</result>
  <result author="Magdaléna Rysová">The Centre and Periphery of Discourse Connectives</result>
  <result author="Filip Jurčíček">A Factored Discriminative Spoken Language Understanding for Spoken Dialogue Systems</result>
  <result author="Marie Mikulová">Semantic Representation of Ellipsis in the Prague Dependency Treebanks</result>
  <result author="Petra Galuščáková">CUNI at MediaEval 2014 Search and Hyperlinking Task: Visual and Prosodic Features in Hyperlinking</result>
  <result author="Kateřina Veselovská">Sentiment Detection and Annotation in a Treebank</result>
  <result author="Petra Galuščáková">Experiments with Segmentation Strategies for Passage Retrieval in Audio-Visual Documents</result>
  <result author="Anna Vernerová">To pay or to get paid: Enriching a Valency Lexicon with Diatheses</result>
  <result author="Jana Straková">Open-Source Tools for Morphology, Lemmatization, POS Tagging and Named Entity Recognition</result>
  <result author="Irena Holubová">INTLIB - an INTelligent LIBrary</result>
  <result author="Jaroslava Hlaváčová">Productive verb prefixation patterns</result>
  <result author="David Mareček">Dealing with Function Words in Unsupervised Dependency Parsing</result>
  <result author="Dušan Variš">Japonsko-český strojový překlad</result>
  <result author="Václava Kettnerová">Reflexive Verbs in a Valency Lexicon: The Case of Czech Reflexive Morphemes</result>
  <result author="Kateřina Veselovská">25. evropská letní škola jazyka, logiky a informace (ESSLLI 2013)</result>
  <result author="Petra Barančíková">Improving Evaluation of English-Czech MT through Paraphrasing</result>
  <result author="Natalia Klyueva">Automatic Valency Derivation for Related Languages</result>
  <result author="Jirka Hana">Building a learner corpus</result>
  <result author="Rudolf Rosa">Fairytale Child Chatbot</result>
  <result author="Rudolf Kadlec">IBM’s Belief Tracker: Results On Dialog State Tracking Challenge Datasets</result>
  <result author="Ondřej Dušek">Alex: Bootstrapping a Spoken Dialogoue System for a New Domain by Real Users</result>
  <result author="Markéta Lopatková">Jak formálně popsat přirozený jazyk?</result>
  <result author="Rudolf Rosa">Depfix: Automatic post-editing of phrase-based machine translation outputs</result>
  <result author="Mohammed Attia">A corpus-based finite-state morphological toolkit for contemporary Arabic</result>
  <result author="Vincent Kríž">Tailored Feature Extraction for Lexical Disambiguation of English Verbs Based on Corpus Pattern Analysis</result>
  <result author="Jirka Hana">Building an Error-tagged Learner Corpus of Czech</result>
  <result author="Matěj Korvas">Vystadial 2013 – ASR training scripts</result>
  <result author="Vincent Kríž">Statistical Recognition of References in Czech Court Decisions</result>
  <result author="Zdeňka Urešová"> PDT-Vallex: Czech Valency lexicon linked to treebanks</result>
  <result author="Matěj Korvas">Vystadial 2013 – English data</result>
  <result author="Matěj Korvas">Vystadial 2013 – Česká data</result>
  <result author="Jakub Mlynář">Identity as Memory and Narrative: The narrative identifications of Czechoslovak Jewish Holocaust survivors</result>
  <result author="Jakub Mlynář">Technology as a support means for the (re)use of narrative data in social sciences</result>
  <result author="Jakub Mlynář">Sedimenting Past: Towards the Sociology of Oral History</result>
  <result author="Eduard Bejček">Syntactic Identification of Occurrences of Multiword Expressions in Text using a Lexicon with Dependency Structures</result>
  <result author="Kateřina Veselovská">Postojová analýza v češtině – současný stav a výhledy</result>
  <result author="Markéta Lopatková">Přirozený jazyk a matematika:jak popsat češtinu tak, aby jí „porozuměly“ počítače?</result>
  <result author="Jarmila Panevová">Teoretická východiska FGP</result>
  <result author="Zdeňka Urešová">Verb-Noun Idiomatic Combinations in a Czech-English Dependency Corpus</result>
  <result author="Jakub Mlynář">Collective Memory and Language: Insights in Social Theory</result>
  <result author="Jarmila Panevová">Valence pohledem FGP</result>
  <result author="Jarmila Panevová">Syntax jako lingvistická discilina</result>
  <result author="Ondřej Plátek">Speech recognition using Kaldi</result>
  <result author="Vincent Kríž">Tailored Feature Extraction for Lexical Disambiguation of English Verbs Based on Corpus Pattern Analysis</result>
  <result author="Aleš Tamchyna">Integrating a Discriminative Classifier into Phrase-based and Hierarchical Decoding</result>
  <result author="Jana Šindlerová">Emoce v jazyce</result>
  <result author="Jirka Hana">Building an Error-tagged Learner Corpus of Czech</result>
  <result author="Rudolf Rosa">Depfix: Jak dělat strojový překlad lépe než Google Translate</result>
  <result author="Ondřej Bojar">Czech Machine Translation in the project CzechMATE</result>
  <result author="Ondřej Dušek">Khresmoi Summary Translation Test Data 1.1</result>
  <result author="Rudolf Rosa">MSTperl parser</result>
  <result author="Magdaléna Rysová">Czech verbs with connective function at the level of discourse in  the Prague Dependency Treebank </result>
  <result author="Kateřina Veselovská">@#%$!!: Vulgarismy v současné online komunikaci</result>
  <result author="Rudolf Rosa">Using a Collection of Many Treebanks for Exploring the Structure of Natural Language Sentences</result>
  <result author="Kateřina Veselovská">Opinion Target Identification Using Thematic Concentration of the Text</result>
  <result author="Zdeněk Žabokrtský">DeriNet: Lexical Network of Derivational Word-Formation Relations in Czech</result>
  <result author="Martin Nečaský">Data Extraction with NLP Techniques and its Transformation to Linked Data</result>
  <result author="Magdaléna Rysová">Language Means Expressing Discourse Relations in Written and Spoken Czech</result>
  <result author="Jarmila Panevová">Mluvnice současné češtiny 2, Syntax na základě anotovaného korpusu</result>
  <result author="Daniel Zeman">HamleDT 2.0</result>
  <result author="Pavel Straňák">Legal issues in LRT development and use in LINDAT/Clarin</result>
  <result author="Jozef Mišutka">Sustainable linguistic repository built on DSpace</result>
  <result author="Oldřich Krůza">Automatic Recognition of Clauses</result>
  <result author="Anna Nedoluzhko">RU-EVAL-2014: EVALUATING ANAPHORA AND COREFERENCE RESOLUTION FOR RUSSIAN</result>
  <result author="Kateřina Veselovská">Patterns of Evaluative Meaning: The Case of Opinion Target</result>
  <result author="Pavel Straňák">B2SHARE – Store and Share Research Data</result>
  <result author="Ondřej Plátek">Speech recognition using Kaldi</result>
  <result author="Anna Nedoluzhko">"VCHERA NASOCHINYALSYA VOROH STROK": PRODUCTIVE CIRCUMFIXAL INTENSIFYING PATTERNS IN RUSSIAN</result>
  <result author="Veronika Kolářová">Special valency behavior of Czech deverbal nouns</result>
  <result author="Vincent Kríž">Statistical Recognition of References in Czech Court Decisions</result>
  <result author="Jarmila Panevová">Contribution of Valency to the Analysis of Language</result>
  <result author="Ondřej Bojar">Představení projektu MosesCore</result>
  <result author="Petr Sgall">Jak psát a jak nepsat česky</result>
  <result author="Václava Kettnerová">Czech Light Verbs from a Lexicographic Point of View</result>
  <result author="Pavel Pecina">Adaptation of machine translation for multilingual information retrieval in medical domain</result>
  <result author="Lucie Poláková">Annotations "beyond the Sentence Boundary" in the Prague Dependency Treebank</result>
  <result author="Ondřej Bojar">UFAL research introduced to the Police of Czech Republic and its visitors</result>
  <result author="Jozef Mišutka">Sustainable linguistic repository built on DSpace</result>
  <result author="Ondřej Bojar">Moses MT: Jak na statistický překlad</result>
  <result author="Kateřina Veselovská">Subjectivity Lexicon for Czech: Implementation and Improvements</result>
  <result author="Kateřina Veselovská">Sestry manžel byl kamaráda bratr – ke  slovoslednému postavení neshodného  atributu vyjádřeného substantivem v  genitivu</result>
  <result author="Loganathan Ramasamy">Parsing under-resourced languages: Cross-lingual transfer strategies for Indian languages</result>
  <result author="Kateřina Rysová">Sentence information structure – contextual boundness of subordinate clauses in Czech based on the corpus analysis</result>
  <result author="Jozef Mišutka">Using EUDAT B2SAFE safe replication from a DSpace digital repository</result>
  <result author="Rudolf Rosa">Fairytale child</result>
  <result author="Jaroslava Hlaváčová">Multilingual Aspects of the Khresmoi project</result>
  <result author="Eduard Bejček">What is Inside Llewyn Davis? Inner Structure of MWEs</result>
  <result author="Jarmila Panevová">Pridatochnyje predlozhenija i nominalizacii</result>
  <result author="Jana Šindlerová">Alternace subjektu a instrumentu v česko-anglickém paralelním korpusu</result>
  <result author="Magdaléna Rysová">Classification of language means expressing textual relations in Czech: Difference between  discourse connectives and their alternative lexicalizations</result>
  <result author="Kateřina Veselovská">Idiomaticity and Language Complexity: The Case of Czech and English</result>
  <result author="Pavlína Jínová">Sentence Structure and Discourse Structure (Possible parallels)</result>
  <result author="Rudolf Rosa">Depfix, a Tool for Automatic Rule-based Post-editing of SMT</result>
  <result author="Jakub Mlynář">Malach jako brána do minulosti skrze vyprávění přeživších</result>
  <result author="Pavel Straňák">Trusted data services in LINDAT/CLARIN</result>
  <result author="Rudolf Rosa">Jak dělat strojový překlad lépe než Google Translate</result>
  <result author="Pavel Straňák">Services of  LINDAT/CLARIN Centre</result>
  <result author="Kateřina Rysová">On the word order of Actor and Patient in Czech</result>
  <result author="Pavel Straňák">PIDs at LINDAT/CLARIN (Czech CLARIN)</result>
  <result author="Jakub Mlynář">Centrum vizuální historie Malach</result>
  <result author="Jozef Mišutka">AAI: Experiences with Making a Service Available for Users Worldwide</result>
  <result author="Barbora Hladká">Crowdsourcing in language classes can help Natural Language Processing</result>
  <result author="Lukáš Žilka">Test Your Bot: user simulator framework</result>
  <result author="Jinho Choi">Universal Dependencies</result>
  <result author="Ondřej Plátek">Jak funguje rozpoznávání řeči?</result>
  <result author="Rudolf Rosa">Chatbot pohádkové dítě</result>
  <result author="Rudolf Rosa">Představení našeho překladového systému</result>
  <result author="Rudolf Rosa">Terminal-based CoNLL-file viewer</result>
  <result author="Veronika Kolářová">Nominalizované struktury se dvěma aktanty ve formě bezpředložkového genitivu</result>
  <result author="Ondřej Bojar">Deep and Phrase-Based MT into Czech</result>
  <result author="Jarmila Panevová">Koordinace versus determinace (Forma nebo význam?)</result>
  <result author="Daniel Zeman">HamleDT: Harmonized Multi-Language Dependency Treebank</result>
  <result author="Vincent Kríž">Tailored Feature Extraction for Lexical Disambiguation of English Verbs Based on Corpus Pattern Analysis</result>
  <result author="Kateřina Rysová">O slovosledu z komunikačního pohledu</result>
  <result author="Veronika Kolářová">Preference v souvýskytu aktantů u českých substantiv mluvení</result>
  <result author="Jarmila Panevová">Valence v gramatice, valence ve slovníku</result>
  <result author="Veronika Kolářová">Valence vybraných typů deverbativních substantiv ve valenčním slovníku PDT-Vallex</result>
  <result author="Daniel Zeman">Lingua::Interset 2.026</result>
  <result author="Magda Ševčíková">AdjDeriNet: Words Derived from Adjectives in Czech</result>
  <result author="Shadi Saleh">CUNI at the CLEF eHealth 2015 Task 2</result>
  <result author="Jana Šindlerová">Zero Alignment of Verb Arguments in a Parallel Treebank</result>
  <result author="Ondřej Plátek">Self awareness for better common ground </result>
  <result author="Pavel Pecina">KWEC Keyword extractor</result>
  <result author="Roman Sudarikov">TeamUFAL: WSD+EL as Document Retrieval</result>
  <result author="Jan Švec">MCLAAS - integrovaný systém vyhledávání ve vícejazyčném audioarchívu výpovědí svědků holocaustu</result>
  <result author="David Mareček">Multilingual Unsupervised Dependency Parsing with Unsupervised POS tags</result>
  <result author="Kateřina Rysová">Jaký byl 41. ročník Olympiády v českém jazyce?</result>
  <result author="Sarah  Berenji Ardestani">B2SHARE: An Open eScience Data Sharing Platform</result>
  <result author="Kira Droganova">Building a Dependency Parsing Model for Russian with MaltParser and MyStem Tagset</result>
  <result author="Jernej Vičič">A Comparison of MT Methods for Closely Related Languages: A Case Study on Czech - Slovak and Croatian - Slovenian Language Pairs</result>
  <result author="Tam Hoang">WMT2013 Test Set in Vietnamese</result>
  <result author="Lucie Poláková">Signals of Attribution in the Prague Dependency Treebank</result>
  <result author="Kristýna Tomšů">Morphology as processed by the human brain</result>
  <result author="Timo Järvinen">Towards Cross-language Application of Dependency Grammar</result>
  <result author="Aleš Tamchyna">Czech Aspect-Based Sentiment Analysis: A New Dataset and Preliminary Results</result>
  <result author="Pavel Pecina">Domain adaptation of statistical machine translation with domain-focused web crawling</result>
  <result author="Michal Novák">Comparison of Coreference Resolvers for Deep Syntax Translation</result>
  <result author="Victoria Rosén">A survey of multiword expressions in treebanks</result>
  <result author="Ondřej Plátek">Self-awareness: Towards Extracting Knowledge from Dialogue</result>
  <result author="Lukáš Žilka">Incremental LSTM-based Dialog State Tracker</result>
  <result author="Vincent Kríž">Czech Legal Text Treebank 1.0</result>
  <result author="Shadi Saleh">Cross language information retrieval systems</result>
  <result author="Eva Hajičová">Reconstruction of Deletions in a Dependency-based Description of Czech: Selected Issues</result>
  <result author="Kateřina Rysová">Topic–Focus Articulation in English Texts on the Basis of Functional Generative Description </result>
  <result author="Vladislav Kuboň">Free or Fixed Word Order: What Can Treebanks Reveal?</result>
  <result author="Zdeňka Urešová">Bilingual English-Czech Valency Lexicon Linked to a Parallel Corpus</result>
  <result author="Vladislav Kuboň">Word-Order Analysis Based Upon Treebank Data</result>
  <result author="Ondřej Dušek">Using Parallel Texts and Lexicons for Verbal Word Sense Disambiguation</result>
  <result author="Šárka Zikánová">Zachycení výstavby textu v Pražském závislostním korpusu </result>
  <result author="Roman Sudarikov">Giving a Sense: A Pilot Study in Concept Annotation from Multiple Resources</result>
  <result author="Magdaléna Rysová">Secondary Connectives in the Prague Dependency Treebank </result>
  <result author="Vincent Kríž">RExtractor: a Robust Information Extractor</result>
  <result author="Ineke Schuurman">CLARIN Concept Registry: the new semantic registry replacing ISOcat</result>
  <result author="Ondřej Bojar">Findings of the 2015 Workshop on Statistical Machine Translation</result>
  <result author="Petra Galuščáková">Audio Information for Hyperlinking of TV Content</result>
  <result author="Eva Fučíková">Czech-English Bilingual Valency Lexicon Online</result>
  <result author="Natalia Klyueva">Analysis of MultiWord Expression translation errors in Statistical Machine Translation</result>
  <result author="Loganathan Ramasamy">Improvements to Korektor: A case study with native and non-native Czech</result>
  <result author="Anna Nedoluzhko">Across Languages and Genres: Creating a Universal Annotation Scheme for Textual Relations</result>
  <result author="Ivana Lukšová">Delving deep into some UFAL data and tools</result>
  <result author="Ondřej Dušek">Training a Natural Language Generator From Unaligned Data</result>
  <result author="Jan Hajič">Deletions and node reconstructions in a dependency-based mutlilevel annotation scheme</result>
  <result author="Vincent Kríž">Feature Extraction for Native Language Identification Using Language Modeling</result>
  <result author="Kateřina Rysová">On an apparent freedom of Czech word order. A case study</result>
  <result author="Vladislav Kuboň">Analysis of Coordinating Constructions in a Dependency Treebank</result>
  <result author="Miroslav Vodolán">Knowledge-based Dialog</result>
  <result author="Ondřej Klejch">CloudASR - v1.0</result>
  <result author="Petra Galuščáková">CUNI at MediaEval 2015 Search and Anchoring in Video Archives: Anchoring via Information Retrieval</result>
  <result author="Miloš Stanojević">Results of the WMT15 Tuning Shared Task</result>
  <result author="Ondřej Klejch">MT-ComparEval</result>
  <result author="Tam Hoang">CsEnVi Pairwise Parallel Corpora</result>
  <result author="Markéta Lopatková">DATLOWE: software pro textovou analytiku</result>
  <result author="Rudolf Rosa">MSTParser Model Interpolation for Multi-source Delexicalized Transfer</result>
  <result author="Magda Ševčíková">Morphology within the Multi-Layered Annotation Scenario of the Prague Dependency Treebank</result>
  <result author="Milan Straka">Parsing Universal Dependency Treebanks using Neural Networks and Search-Based Oracle</result>
  <result author="Ondřej Klejch">CloudASR: Platform &amp; Service</result>
  <result author="Václava Kettnerová">At the Lexicon-Grammar Interface: The Case of Complex Predicates in the Functional Generative Description</result>
  <result author="Rudolf Rosa">Translation Model Interpolation for Domain Adaptation in TectoMT</result>
  <result author="Franky  ">Resources for Indonesian Sentiment Analysis</result>
  <result author="Aleš Tamchyna">What a Transfer-Based System Brings to the Combination with PBMT</result>
  <result author="Radoslav Klíč">Resource-Light Acquisition of Inflectional Paradigms</result>
  <result author="Ondřej Bojar">CUNI in WMT15: Chimera Strikes Again</result>
  <result author="Ondřej Dušek">New Language Pairs in TectoMT</result>
  <result author="Daniel Zeman">Slavic Languages in Universal Dependencies</result>
  <result author="Ondřej Bojar">TMODS:ENG-CZE - systém pro překlad souvislého textu pro jazykový pár en-cs</result>
  <result author="Stephan Oepen">SemEval 2015 Task 18: Broad-Coverage Semantic Dependency Parsing</result>
  <result author="Aleš Tamchyna">A Discriminative Model for Semantics-to-String Translation</result>
  <result author="Jonáš Vidra">DeriNet verze 1.0</result>
  <result author="Lukáš Žilka">LecTrack: Incremental Dialog State Tracking with Long Short-Term Memory Networks</result>
  <result author="Miloš Stanojević">Results of the WMT15 Metrics Shared Task</result>
  <result author="Jindřich Libovický">A Machine Learning Approach to Hypothesis Decoding in Scene Text Recognition</result>
  <result author="Barbora Hladká">A Gentle Introduction to Machine Learning for Natural Language Processing: How to start in 16 practical steps</result>
  <result author="Zdeňka Urešová">CzEngVallex: Mapping Valency between Languages</result>
  <result author="Jonáš Vidra">Implementation of a Search Engine for DeriNet</result>
  <result author="Ahmad Aghaebrahimian">Machine Learning for Semantic Parsing in Review</result>
  <result author="Vít Baisa">SemEval-2015 Task 15: A CPA dictionary-entry-building task</result>
  <result author="Jan Hajič">LINDAT/CLARIN: data a technologie pro výzkum založený na analýze psaného a mluveného jazyka</result>
  <result author="Roman Sudarikov">Instalace a uživatelské nastavení pro česko-anglický a anglicko-český překlad českých odborných termínů směrnice INSPIRE a thesaurů GEMET a AgroVoc (prostorová data) pro výhradní použití ve výzkumném projektu</result>
  <result author="Jakub Mlynář">Malach Center for Visual History</result>
  <result author="Ondřej Klejch">MT-ComparEval: Graphical evaluation interface for Machine Translation development</result>
  <result author="Rudolf Rosa">Multi-source Cross-lingual Delexicalized Parser Transfer: Prague or Stanford?</result>
  <result author="Roman Sudarikov">Giving a Sense: A Pilot Study in Concept Annotation from Multiple Resources</result>
  <result author="Rudolf Rosa">A new parsing algorithm</result>
  <result author="Rudolf Rosa">KLcpos3 - a Language Similarity Measure for Delexicalized Parser Transfer</result>
  <result author="Antonio Toral">Linguistically-augmented Perplexity-based Data Selection for Language Models</result>
  <result author="Petra Barančíková">Targeted Paraphrasing on Deep Syntactic Layer for MT Evaluation</result>
  <result author="Jan Hajič, jr.">Matching Illustrative Images to “Soft News” Articles</result>
  <result author="João Palotti">Retrieving information about medical symptoms</result>
  <result author="Matouš Macháček">Evaluating Machine Translation Quality Using Short Segments Annotations</result>
  <result author="Miroslav Vodolán">Hybrid Dialog State Tracker</result>
  <result author="Ahmad Aghaebrahimian">Constraint-based semantic parsing</result>
  <result author="Kateřina Rysová">Analyzing Text Coherence via Multiple Annotation in the Prague Dependency Treebank</result>
  <result author="Anna Nedoluzhko">Towards comprehensive approaches to discourse-structuring devices: PDiT - GECCo Scientific mission</result>
  <result author="Joakim Nivre">Universal Dependencies 1.0</result>
  <result author="Jan Hajič">Překlad archívu VHA:projekt AMALACH</result>
  <result author="Magda Ševčíková">Lexikální síť DeriNet</result>
  <result author="Jan Hajič">A-GOOGLE: software a data pro anotaci</result>
  <result author="Rudolf Rosa">Depfix: Automatic Post-editing of SMT</result>
  <result author="Jan Hajič">Treebanks and MWEs</result>
  <result author="Magdaléna Rysová">On Definition of Discourse Connectives:  Primary vs. Secondary Connectives (Based on a Corpus Probe)</result>
  <result author="Ekaterina Lapshinova-Koltunski">Finding Nexus in the PDiT and GECCo Annotation Schemes</result>
  <result author="Jan Hajič">Language technology for the medical domain</result>
  <result author="Jan Hajič">Abstract Meaning Representation: comparing languages and their representations</result>
  <result author="Kateřina Veselovská">Automatická detekce emocí v textu</result>
  <result author="Michal Novák">Srovnání koreferenčních výrazů v češtině a angličtině</result>
  <result author="Eduard Bejček">Identification of Multiword BBN Named Entities in Dependency Annotation of Wall Street Journal</result>
  <result author="Ondřej Bojar">MT for Industry from Researchers’ Point of View</result>
  <result author="Pavel Straňák">Prague Trees</result>
  <result author="Vincent Kríž">RExtractor: robustní informační extraktor</result>
  <result author="Jan Hajič">A Summary of Research Activities: Technologies – Demands – Gaps – Roadmaps</result>
  <result author="Ondřej Plátek">PechaKucha Ústí nad Labem - Jak počítače naučit mluvit</result>
  <result author="Anna Nedoluzhko">Coreference in Czech and cross-lingually – ideas and perspectives</result>
  <result author="Anna Nedoluzhko">Annotation of textual phenomena in the Prague Dependency Treebank</result>
  <result author="Jan Hajič">Machine Translation of Natural Languages</result>
  <result author="Michal Novák">Coreferential expressions in English and Czech</result>
  <result author="Veronika Kolářová">Using the Sketch Engine in Preparation for a Valency Lexicon of Czech Nouns: The Case of Nominalizations of Support Verb Constructions</result>
  <result author="Anna Nedoluzhko">Разметка анафорических отношений и дискурса в PDT</result>
  <result author="Vincent Kríž">RExtractor: robustní informační extraktor</result>
  <result author="Željko Agić">Universal Dependencies 1.1</result>
  <result author="Jozef Mišutka">How to set up a CLARIN B-centre using a modified DSpace: DSpace &amp; becoming a B centre</result>
  <result author="Anna Nedoluzhko">Coreference chains in Czech, English and Russian: Preliminary findings</result>
  <result author="Rudolf Rosa">MSTperl delexicalized parser transfer scripts and configuration files</result>
  <result author="Anna Nedoluzhko">Текстовые явления - подходы и инструменты</result>
  <result author="Rudolf Rosa">MSTperl parser (2015-05-19)</result>
  <result author="Jan Hajič">Abstract Meaning Representation across Languages</result>
  <result author="Ondřej Košarko">Repozitář pro jazyková data a nástroje LINDAT/CLARIN (DSpace@ÚFAL)</result>
  <result author="Jozef Mišutka">Attractive and Effective Data Sharing</result>
  <result author="Jozef Mišutka">Sharing and reusing data legally</result>
  <result author="Rudolf Rosa">Parsing Natural Language Sentences by Semi-supervised Methods</result>
  <result author="Kateřina Veselovská">On the Linguistic Structure of Emotional Meaning in Czech</result>
  <result author="Jarmila Panevová">Odešel prof. dr. Fr. Daneš (23.7.1919-18.3.2015)</result>
  <result author="Lucie Poláková">Discourse Relations in Czech</result>
  <result author="Eduard Bejček">Automatické propojování lexikografických zdrojů a korpusových dat</result>
  <result author="Jozef Mišutka">Data Citation Box</result>
  <result author="Radek Čech">Polysemy and Synonymy in Syntactic Dependency Networks</result>
  <result author="Ondřej Bojar">Machine translation</result>
  <result author="Daniel Zeman">From the Jungle to a Park: Harmonizing Annotations across Languages</result>
  <result author="Anna Nedoluzhko">Information Structure and Anaphoric Links – A Case Study and Probe</result>
  <result author="Natalia Klyueva">Linguistic Issues in Machine Translation between Czech and Russian</result>
  <result author="Daniel Zeman">HamleDT 3.0</result>
  <result author="Václava Kettnerová">Shoda doplňku v reflexivních konstrukcích v češtině</result>
  <result author="Václava Kettnerová">Syntactic Structure of Czech Light Verb Constructions</result>
  <result author="Michal Novák">Correspondences between Czech and English Coreferential Expressions</result>
  <result author="Magda Ševčíková">Morphology within the Multi-Layered Annotation Scenario of the Prague Dependency Treebank</result>
  <result author="Jan Hajič">Deep Linguistic Information in Machine Translation</result>
  <result author="Jan Hajič">The LINDAT/CLARIN large infrastructure: data and services</result>
  <result author="Vincent Kríž">RExtractor: a Robust Information Extractor</result>
  <result author="Jakub Mlynář">Malach Center for Visual History</result>
  <result author="Eduard Bejček">Propojování valenčních slovníků</result>
  <result author="Petra Galuščáková">SHAMUS: UFAL Search and Hyperlinking Multimedia System</result>
  <result author="Magdaléna Rysová">Diskurzní konektory v češtině  (Od centra k periferii) </result>
  <result author="Kateřina Veselovská">Vyjadřování emocí v češtině: lingvistická analýza a praktické aplikace</result>
  <result author="Anna Nedoluzhko">Analysis of DRD-related Contrasts in Spoken Czech, English and German</result>
  <result author="Jan Hajič">Experience of the Institute of Formal and Applied Linguistics: Framework ICT projects</result>
  <result author="Jozef Mišutka">Consistent User Experience and Cross-referencing inside LINDAT/CLARIN infrastructure</result>
  <result author="Tam Hoang">TmTriangulate: A Tool for Phrase Table Triangulation</result>
  <result author="Zdeňka Urešová">CzEngVallex - Czech English Valency Lexicon</result>
  <result author="Jakub Mlynář">Unique collection of interviews with Armenian genocide witnesses and survivors is available at the Charles University in Prague</result>
  <result author="Jan Hajič">Evaluation of Research Programs at the Technology Agency of the Czech Republic</result>
  <result author="Martin Šmok">"Narodila jsem se v Československu..." Dvacáté století ve vzpomínkách pamětnic z Podkarpatské Rusi uložených v archivu USC Shoah Foundation</result>
  <result author="Joakim Nivre">Universal Dependencies 1.2</result>
  <result author="Milan Straka">MorphoDiTa</result>
  <result author="Šárka Zikánová">Discourse and Coherence. From the Sentence Structure to Relations in Text</result>
  <result author="Ondřej Bojar">Jak pracuje automatický  překlad</result>
  <result author="Barbora Hladká">Strojové učení a pravidla pro extrakci informací z textů</result>
  <result author="Jarmila Panevová">Příslovečné určení srovnání v češtině</result>
  <result author="Ondřej Bojar">Jaká data se používají ve strojovém překladu</result>
  <result author="Barbara  J. Grosz">Obituary - Jane J. Robinson</result>
  <result author="Milan Straka">NameTag</result>
  <result author="David Mareček">LiStr - Linguistic Structure Induction toolkit</result>
  <result author="Milan Straka">Parsito</result>
  <result author="Vít Baisa">VPS-GradeUp</result>
  <result author="Ondřej Plátek">A Dataset of Operator-client Dialogues Aligned with Database Queries for End-to-end Training</result>
  <result author="Aleš Tamchyna">UFAL at SemEval-2016 Task 5: Recurrent Neural Networks for Sentence Classification</result>
  <result author="Vít Baisa">VPS-GradeUp: Graded Decisions on Usage Patterns</result>
  <result author="Michal Novák">Pronoun Prediction with Linguistic Features and Example Weighing</result>
  <result author="Aleš Tamchyna">Manual and Automatic Paraphrases for MT Evaluation</result>
  <result author="Jiří Mírovský">Searching in the Penn Discourse Treebank Using the PML-Tree Query</result>
  <result author="David Mareček">Twelve Years of Unsupervised Dependency Parsing</result>
  <result author="Ondřej Dušek">A Context-aware Natural Language Generator for Dialogue Systems</result>
  <result author="Paweł Kamocki">The Public License Selector: Making Open Licensing Easier</result>
  <result author="Ondřej Košarko">VIADAT-REPO</result>
  <result author="Nikita Mediankin">ConFarm: Extracting Surface Representations of Verb and Noun Constructions from Dependency Annotated Corpora of Russian</result>
  <result author="Roman Barták">On Similarities Between Workflow Verification and Grammar Checking</result>
  <result author="Rudolf Rosa">Moses &amp; Treex Hybrid MT Systems Bestiary</result>
  <result author="Guido Zuccon">The IR Task at the CLEF eHealth Evaluation Lab 2016: User-centred Health Information Retrieval</result>
  <result author="Ekaterina Lapshinova-Koltunski">From monolingual annotations towards cross-lingual resources: An interoperable approach to the analysis of discourse</result>
  <result author="Martin Víta">Word2vec Based System for Recognizing Partial Textual Entailment</result>
  <result author="Natalia Klyueva"> Incorporation of a valency lexicon into a TectoMT pipeline</result>
  <result author="Ondřej Bojar">A Pilot Eye-Tracking Study of WMT-Style Ranking Evaluation</result>
  <result author="Magda Ševčíková">Enrichment of a lexical network of Czech derived words by exploiting inflectional paradigms</result>
  <result author="Jaroslava Hlaváčová">Homonymy and Polysemy in the Czech Morphological Dictionary</result>
  <result author="Ondřej Bojar">UFAL Submissions to the IWSLT 2016 MT Track</result>
  <result author="Roman Sudarikov">Using MT-ComparEval</result>
  <result author="David Mareček">Merged bilingual trees based on Universal Dependencies in Machine Translation</result>
  <result author="Vladislav Kuboň">Searching for a Measure of Word Order Freedom</result>
  <result author="Natalia Klyueva">Improving Corpus Search via Parsing</result>
  <result author="Phil Williams">Edinburgh’s Statistical Machine Translation Systems for WMT16</result>
  <result author="Miroslav Vodolán">Question Dialogs Dataset</result>
  <result author="Aleš Tamchyna">Target-Side Context for Discriminative Models in Statistical Machine Translation</result>
  <result author="Ekaterina Lapshinova-Koltunski">An interoperable approach to the analysis of discourse</result>
  <result author="Anna Roitberg">Bridging Corpus for Russian in comparison with Czech</result>
  <result author="Michal Sedlák">Public License Selector</result>
  <result author="Petra Galuščáková">CUNI at TRECVID 2015 Video Hyperlinking Task</result>
  <result author="Zdeňka Urešová">CzEngVallex: a bilingual Czech-English valency lexicon</result>
  <result author="Vincent Kríž">Czech Legal Text Treebank 1.0</result>
  <result author="Rosa Gaudio">SMT and Hybrid systems of the QTLeap project in the WMT16 IT-task</result>
  <result author="Ondřej Dušek">Sequence-to-Sequence Generation for Spoken Dialogue via Deep Syntax Trees and Strings</result>
  <result author="Václava Kettnerová">Lexicographic Description of Complex Predicates in Czech: Between Lexicon and Grammar</result>
  <result author="Zdeněk Žabokrtský">Merging Data Resources for Inflectional and Derivational Morphology in Czech</result>
  <result author="Ondřej Plátek">Recurrent Neural Networks for Dialogue State Tracking</result>
  <result author="Roman Sudarikov">Verb Sense Disambiguation in Machine Translation</result>
  <result author="Nikita Mediankin">Building NLP Pipeline for Russian with a Handful of Linguistic Knowledge</result>
  <result author="David Mareček">Delexicalized and Minimally Supervised Parsing on Universal Dependencies</result>
  <result author="Ahmad Aghaebrahimian">Constraint-Based Open Question Answering via Knowledge Graph Search </result>
  <result author="Jernej Vičič">Automated implementation process of machine translation system for related languages.</result>
  <result author="Jana Straková">Neural Networks for Featureless Named Entity Recognition in Czech</result>
  <result author="Jan Hajič, jr.">Further Steps towards a Standard Testbed for Optical Music Recognition</result>
  <result author="Le Thanh">Using Term Position Similarity and Language Modeling for Bilingual Document Alignment</result>
  <result author="Martin Komenda">Automatic Keyword Extraction from Medical and Healthcare Curriculum</result>
  <result author="Ahmad Aghaebrahimian">Open-domain Factoid Question Answering via Knowledge Graph Search</result>
  <result author="Rudolf Rosa">Czechizator</result>
  <result author="Amal Abdelsalam">Bilingual Embeddings and Word Alignments for Translation Quality Estimation</result>
  <result author="Tom Kocmi">SubGram: Extending Skip-gram Word Representation with Substrings</result>
  <result author="Milan Straka">UDPipe: Trainable Pipeline for Processing CoNLL-U Files Performing Tokenization, Morphological Analysis, POS Tagging and Parsing</result>
  <result author="Jozef Mišutka">Linguistic digital repository based on DSpace 5.2</result>
  <result author="Ondřej Bojar">Results of the WMT16 Metrics Shared Task</result>
  <result author="Anna Nedoluzhko">Contrasting Coreference in Czech and German: from Different Frameworks to Joint Results</result>
  <result author="Ondřej Bojar">Dávkový překlad IBM</result>
  <result author="Roman Barták">Using a Grammar Checker to Validate Compliance of Processes with Workflow Models</result>
  <result author="Ondřej Bojar">Ten Years of WMT Evaluation Campaigns: Lessons Learnt</result>
  <result author="Nathan David Green">Creating Hybrid Dependency Parsers for Syntax-Based MT</result>
  <result author="Vincent Kríž">Improving Dependency Parsing Using Sentence Clause Charts</result>
  <result author="Ondřej Dušek">A Context-aware Natural Language Generation Dataset for Dialogue Systems</result>
  <result author="Shadi Saleh">Reranking Hypotheses of Machine-Translated Queries for Cross-Lingual Information Retrieval</result>
  <result author="Markéta Lopatková">VALLEX 3.0 - Valenční slovník českých sloves</result>
  <result author="Kateřina Rysová">42. ročník Olympiády v českém jazyce</result>
  <result author="Markéta Lopatková">DATLOWE: software pro textovou analytiku</result>
  <result author="Jan Hajič, jr.">MUSCIMarker 1.1</result>
  <result author="Jindřich Libovický">A Dataset and Evaluation Metric for Coherent Text Recognition  from Scene Images</result>
  <result author="Miroslav Vodolán">Data Collection for Interactive Learning through the Dialog</result>
  <result author="Aleš Tamchyna">CUNI-LMU Submissions in WMT2016: Chimera Constrained and Beaten</result>
  <result author="Zdeňka Urešová">Non-projectivity and valency</result>
  <result author="Jan-Thorsten Peter">The QT21/HimL Combined Machine Translation System</result>
  <result author="Eva Fučíková">Enriching a Valency Lexicon by Deverbative Nouns</result>
  <result author="Stephan Oepen">Towards Comparability of Linguistic Graph Banks for Semantic Parsing</result>
  <result author="Jindřich Libovický">Neural Scoring Function for MST Parser</result>
  <result author="Viktor Kocúr">Particle Swarm Optimization Submission for WMT16 Tuning Task</result>
  <result author="Václava Kettnerová">Distribution of Valency Complements in Czech Complex Predicates: Between Verb and Noun</result>
  <result author="Katrin Přikrylová">The Role of Conjunctions in Adjective Polarity Analysis in Czech</result>
  <result author="Bushra Jawaid">Enriching Source for English-to-Urdu Machine Translation</result>
  <result author="Silvie Cinková">Graded and Word-Sense-Disambiguation Decisions in Corpus Pattern Analysis: a Pilot Study</result>
  <result author="Anna Nedoluzhko">A new look at possessive reflexivization: A comparative study between Czech and Russian</result>
  <result author="Jindřich Libovický">CUNI System for WMT16 Automatic Post-Editing and Multimodal Translation Tasks</result>
  <result author="Kateřina Rysová">Koreference a elipsa v Pražském závislostním korpusu</result>
  <result author="Victoria Rosén">MWEs in Treebanks: From Survey to Guidelines</result>
  <result author="Amir Kamran">shortref.org</result>
  <result author="Amir Kamran">AAI released attribute aggregator</result>
  <result author="Jana Klímová">Towards a Corpus-based Valency Lexicon of Czech Nouns </result>
  <result author="Shadi Saleh">Adapting SMT Query Translation Reranker to New Languages in Cross-Lingual Information Retrieval</result>
  <result author="Zdeňka Urešová">Inherently Pronominal Verbs in Czech: Description and Conversion Based on Treebank Annotation</result>
  <result author="Markéta Lopatková">Alternations: From Lexicon to Grammar And Back Again</result>
  <result author="Petra Galuščáková">Klasifikátor ruských dokumentů pro ACREA CR, spol. s r.o.</result>
  <result author="Arantxa Otegi">QTLeap WSD/NED Corpora: Semantic Annotation of Parallel Corpora in Six Languages</result>
  <result author="David Kuboň">Politician</result>
  <result author="Katrin Přikrylová">Logical vs. Natural Language Conjunctions in Czech: A Comparative Study</result>
  <result author="Ondřej Bojar">CzEng 1.6: Enlarged Czech-English Parallel Corpus with Processing Tools Dockered</result>
  <result author="Jiří Mírovský">Designing CzeDLex – A Lexicon of Czech Discourse Connectives</result>
  <result author="Eva Fučíková">Joint search in a bilingual valency lexicon and an annotated corpus</result>
  <result author="Jozef Mišutka">SHORTREF.ORG Making URLs Easy-to-Cite</result>
  <result author="Zhiwei Yu">If You Even Don't Have a Bit of Bible: Learning Delexicalized POS Taggers</result>
  <result author="Mohammed Attia">Arabic Spelling Error Detection and Correction</result>
  <result author="Nora Aranberri">Tools and Guidelines for Principled Machine Translation Development</result>
  <result author="Anna Nedoluzhko">Abstract Coreference in a Multilingual Perspective: a View on Czech and German</result>
  <result author="Rudolf Rosa">Dictionary-based Domain Adaptation of MT Systems without Retraining</result>
  <result author="Petra Galuščáková">SHAMUS: UFAL Search and Hyperlinking Multimedia System</result>
  <result author="Eleftherios Avramidis">Deeper Machine Translation and Evaluation for German</result>
  <result author="Ondřej Bojar">Findings of the 2016 Conference on Machine Translation (WMT16)</result>
  <result author="Fabienne Braune">A Framework for Discriminative Rule Selection in Hierarchical Moses</result>
  <result author="Bushra Jawaid">Results of the WMT16 Tuning Shared Task</result>
  <result author="Silvie Cinková">WordSim353 for Czech</result>
  <result author="Ineke Schuurman">CLARIN Concept Registry: The New Semantic Registry</result>
  <result author="Silvie Cinková">What Do Graded Decisions Tell Us about Verb Uses</result>
  <result author="Kateřina Rysová">Automatic evaluation of surface coherence in L2 texts in Czech</result>
  <result author="Jan Hajič">Verb Argument Pairing in Czech-English Parallel Treebank</result>
  <result author="Anna Nedoluzhko">Coreference in Prague Czech-English Dependency Treebank</result>
  <result author="Joakim Nivre">Universal Dependencies v1: A Multilingual Treebank Collection</result>
  <result author="Shadi Saleh">Task3 Patient-Centred Information Retrieval: Team CUNI</result>
  <result author="Adam Przepiórkowski">Phraseology in two Slavic valency dictionaries: limitations and perspectives</result>
  <result author="Daniel Zeman">Planting Trees in the Desert: Delexicalized Tagging and Parsing Combined</result>
  <result author="Lucie Poláková">Discourse Annotation Theories and Tools</result>
  <result author="Silvie Cinková">WordSim353-cs: Evaluation Dataset for Lexical Similarity and Relatedness based on WordSim353</result>
  <result author="Anna Nedoluzhko">Discourse annotation theories and tools</result>
  <result author="Kateřina Veselovská">Jak spočítat emoce v jazyce</result>
  <result author="Anna Nedoluzhko">Dicourse annotation tools</result>
  <result author="Lucie Poláková">Connective Movement - A demonstration on Czech</result>
  <result author="Zdeněk Žabokrtský">To tree or not to tree? (The quest for sentence structure in natural language processing)</result>
  <result author="Gabriel Altman">Nový encyklopedický slovník češtiny</result>
  <result author="Natalia Klyueva">Exploiting KonText for querying Lindat corpora</result>
  <result author="Kateřina Veselovská">Vyjadřování emocí v češtině a možnosti extrakce emocionality z psaného textu</result>
  <result author="Anna Nedoluzhko">Prague Czech-English Dependency Treebank 2.0 Coref</result>
  <result author="David Mareček">Deltacorpus</result>
  <result author="Markéta Lopatková">Valenční slovník českých sloves VALLEX: od slovníku ke gramatice</result>
  <result author="Kateřina Veselovská">Analýza sentimentu textu</result>
  <result author="Kateřina Veselovská">Automatický sentiment aneb Kam spěje svět</result>
  <result author="David Mareček">Gibbs Sampling Segmentation of Parallel Dependency Trees for Tree-Based Machine Translation</result>
  <result author="Ondřej Dušek">Alex Context NLG Dataset</result>
  <result author="Markéta Lopatková">VALLEX, Family of Electronic Valency Lexicons of Verbs</result>
  <result author="Eva Hajičová">Putting things together: Correlating discourse relations with other types of linguistic data</result>
  <result author="Ondřej Bojar">Jaká data se používají ve strojovém překladu</result>
  <result author="Eduard Bejček">Named Entities within Multiword Addresses</result>
  <result author="Daniel Zeman">Universal Annotation of Slavic Verb Forms</result>
  <result author="Jakub Mlynář">From search to exploration: Barriers and opportunities in using oral history archives as data resources</result>
  <result author="Ondřej Bojar">Jak pracuje automatický překlad</result>
  <result author="Kateřina Veselovská">Machine Learning Approaches to Sentiment Analysis</result>
  <result author="Vincent Kríž">RExtractor: a Robust Information Extractor</result>
  <result author="Kira Droganova">NLP Pipeline for Russian: an Easy-to-Use Web Application for Morphological and Syntactic Annotation</result>
  <result author="Amir Kamran">How to set up a CLARIN B-centre using a modified DSpace</result>
  <result author="Vladislav Kuboň">Analysis of Word Order in Multiple Treebanks</result>
  <result author="Joakim Nivre">Universal Dependencies 1.3</result>
  <result author="Ondřej Bojar">WMT Metrics Task: Past Great Metrics, Current Evaluation Experiments, Future Metrics Challenges</result>
  <result author="Kateřina Veselovská">Combining Hand-Crafted Rules and Machine Learning Methods in Opinion Target Identification</result>
  <result author="Martin Popel">TectoMT – a deep-­linguistic core of the combined Chimera MT system</result>
  <result author="Dan Flickinger">SDP 2014 &amp; 2015: Broad Coverage Semantic Dependency Parsing</result>
  <result author="Vincent Kríž">Statistical Recognition of References in Czech Court Decisions</result>
  <result author="Milan Straka">UDPipe</result>
  <result author="Rudolf Rosa">Delexicalized Cross-lingual Transfer of Statistical Syntactic Parsers for Automatic Analysis of Low-resourced Natural Languages</result>
  <result author="Rudolf Rosa">Czech and English abstracts of ÚFAL papers	</result>
  <result author="Kira Droganova">Conversion of SynTagRus (the Russian dependency treebank) to Universal Dependencies</result>
  <result author="Václava Kettnerová">Diatheses of Complex Predicates in Czech</result>
  <result author="Dan Flickinger">Open SDP</result>
  <result author="Jarmila Panevová">Syntax Vladimíra Šmilauera včera a dnes</result>
  <result author="Natalia Klyueva">MWEs in a corpus query system</result>
  <result author="Ondřej Plátek">Vystadial 2016 – Česká data</result>
  <result author="Kateřina Veselovská">Using Universal Dependencies for Cross-linguistic Comparison of Syntactic Features in Evaluative Structures</result>
  <result author="Eduard Bejček">Annotation of MWEs, Representation in a Lexicon</result>
  <result author="Anna Vernerová">Diatheses of Czech Verbs with Genitive Complementation</result>
  <result author="Anna Nedoluzhko">Possessives in Parallel English‑Czech-Russian Texts</result>
  <result author="Jan Hajič">The Chimera-TectoMT architecture of Machine   Translation with Deep Linguistic Analysis</result>
  <result author="Paweł Kamocki">« Trust me. I’m a License Selector ». Licensing for Digital Humanities</result>
  <result author="Petra Galuščáková">Machine Translation of Medical Text in the KConnect Project</result>
  <result author="Kateřina Veselovská">Umělá inteligence s názorem: objektivita v počítačové lingvistice</result>
  <result author="Dušan Variš">Automatic Error Correction of Machine Translation Output</result>
  <result author="Ondřej Bojar">CzEng 1.6 pipeline: Docker container</result>
  <result author="Jakub Mlynář">Minulost jako vzpomínka a vyprávění: Archiv vizuální historie USC Shoah Foundation v kontextu orální historie</result>
  <result author="Radek Čech">Quantitative Analysis of Syntactic Dependency in Czech</result>
  <result author="Daniel Zeman">Universal Dependencies for Slavic Languages (invited talk)</result>
  <result author="Markéta Lopatková">Diateze ve Valenčním slovníku českých sloves VALLEX</result>
  <result author="Natalia Klyueva">MWEs in Universal Dependencies 1.3</result>
  <result author="Václava Kettnerová">Syntaktická struktura komplexních predikátů a její popis ve valenčním slovníku</result>
  <result author="Héctor Martínez Alonso">Universal Dependencies for the AnCora treebanks</result>
  <result author="Jana Šindlerová">Hlásili to v rozhlase aneb vzájemné mapování lokace a aktora v dvojjazyčném závislostním korpusu</result>
  <result author="Milan Straka">Complete Analysis from Unstructured Text to Dependency Tree with UDPipe and NameTag</result>
  <result author="Anna Nedoluzhko">Osobní a reflexivní posesiva v češtině ve srovnání s ruštinou</result>
  <result author="Jarmila Panevová">Valence v gramatice, valence ve slovníku</result>
  <result author="Magda Ševčíková">Lexikální síť DeriNet: elektronický zdroj pro výzkum derivace v češtině</result>
  <result author="Ondřej Bojar">CzEng 1.6</result>
  <result author="Václava Kettnerová">Distribution of Valency Complementations in Light Verb Constructions</result>
  <result author="Eduard Bejček">PARSEME Shared Task and PDT: Comparison and Data Conversion</result>
  <result author="Vincent Kríž">Improving Dependency Parsing Using Sentence Clause Charts</result>
  <result author="Olga Lyashevskaya">Universal Dependencies for Russian: A New Syntactic Dependencies Tagset</result>
  <result author="Jarmila Panevová">In favour of the Argument-Adjunct Distinction (from the Perspective of FGD)</result>
  <result author="Jan Hajič">Linguistically Annotated Corpus as an Invaluable Resource for Advancements in Linguistic Research: A Case Study</result>
  <result author="Jonáš Vidra">DeriNet verze 1.2</result>
  <result author="Jozef Mišutka">AAI: systematically addressing the attribute release problem</result>
  <result author="Kateřina Veselovská">Počítačové zpracování emocí v textu</result>
  <result author="Anna Nedoluzhko">Discourse annotation approaches to Czech and German</result>
  <result author="David Mareček">Czech-English Manual Word Alignment</result>
  <result author="Michal Novák">Prague Czech-English Dependency Treebank 2.0 - Russian Translation, version 0.5</result>
  <result author="Kateřina Rysová">EVALD 1.0</result>
  <result author="Kateřina Rysová">EVALD 1.0 for Foreigners</result>
  <result author="Joakim Nivre">Universal Dependencies 1.4</result>
  <result author="Rudolf Rosa">Jak pracuje internetový vyhledávač</result>
  <result author="Daniel Zeman">The Universe of Dependencies: Past and Future</result>
  <result author="Markéta Lopatková">Valenční slovník českých sloves VALLEX</result>
  <result author="Magdaléna Rysová">Prague Discourse Treebank 2.0</result>
  <result author="Kateřina Veselovská">Postojová modalita a možnosti automatické extrakce emocionality z psaného textu</result>
  <result author="Rudolf Rosa">Error Analysis of Cross-lingual Tagging and Parsing</result>
  <result author="Silvie Cinková">Are Annotators' Word-Sense Disambiguation Decisions Affected by Textual Entailment between Lexicon Glosses?</result>
  <result author="Eduard Bejček">Extracting Verbal Multiword Data from Rich Treebank Annotation</result>
  <result author="Jana Šindlerová">Lingvistické opodstatnění konstruktivistické didaktiky při výuce slovních druhů </result>
  <result author="David Mareček">CUNI Experiments for WMT17 Metrics Task</result>
  <result author="Antonio Valerio Miceli Barone">Deep Architectures for Neural Machine Translation</result>
  <result author="Daniel Zeman">Core Arguments in Universal Dependencies</result>
  <result author="Josef Šimandl">Slovník afixů užívaných v češtině</result>
  <result author="Natalia Klyueva">Neural Networks for Multi-Word Expression Detection</result>
  <result author="Jonáš Vidra">Online Software Components for Accessing Derivational Networks</result>
  <result author="Jana Šindlerová">Emotions Translated: Enhancing a Subjectivity Lexicon Using a Parallel Valency Lexicon</result>
  <result author="Daniel Zeman">CoNLL 2017 Shared Task: Multilingual Parsing from Raw Text to Universal Dependencies</result>
  <result author="Tom Kocmi">LanideNN: Multilingual Language Identification on Character Window</result>
  <result author="Marie Mikulová">PDTSC 2.0 - Spoken Corpus with Rich Multi-layer Structural Annotation</result>
  <result author="Mostafa Abdou">Variable Mini-Batch Sizing and Pre-Trained Embeddings</result>
  <result author="Magdaléna Rysová">Discourse Connectives: From Historical Origin to Present-Day Development </result>
  <result author="Milan Straka">Tokenizing, POS Tagging, Lemmatizing and Parsing UD 2.0 with UDPipe</result>
  <result author="Petra Galuščáková">Visual Descriptors in Methods for Video Hyperlinking</result>
  <result author="Jan Hajič, jr.">Groundtruthing (not only) Music Notation with MUSCIMarker: a Practical Overview</result>
  <result author="Kateřina Rysová">Proběhl 43. ročník Olympiády v českém jazyce</result>
  <result author="Miroslav Vodolán">Denotation Extraction for Interactive Learning in Dialogue Systems</result>
  <result author="Pavlína Synková">Extracting a Lexicon of Discourse Connectives in Czech from an Annotated Corpus</result>
  <result author="Kateřina Rysová">Possibilities of Text Coherence Analysis in the Prague Dependency Treebank </result>
  <result author="Ondřej Bojar">Findings of the 2017 Conference on Machine Translation (WMT17)</result>
  <result author="Martin Popel">Udapi: Universal API for Universal Dependencies</result>
  <result author="Michal Novák">EVALD 2.0</result>
  <result author="Eduard Bejček">The Relation of Form and Function in Linguistic Theory and in a Multi-layer Treebank</result>
  <result author="Kateřina Rysová">Introducing EVALD  – Software Applications for Automatic Evaluation of Discourse in Czech</result>
  <result author="Ondřej Bojar">Results of the WMT17 Neural MT Training Task</result>
  <result author="Jindřich Helcl">CUNI System for the WMT17 Multimodal Translation Task</result>
  <result author="Michal Novák">EVALD 2.0 pro cizince</result>
  <result author="Zdeňka Urešová">Syntactic-Semantic Classes of Context-Sensitive Synonyms Based on a Bilingual Corpus</result>
  <result author="Dušan Variš">CUNI System for WMT17 Automatic Post-Editing Task</result>
  <result author="Václava Kettnerová">Complex Predicates with Light Verbs in VALLEX: From Formal Model to Lexicographic Description</result>
  <result author="Natalia Klyueva">Querying Multiword Expressions Annotation with NoSke</result>
  <result author="Matiss Rikters">Paying Attention to Multi-Word Expressions in Neural Machine Translation</result>
  <result author="Markéta Lopatková">DATLOWE: software pro textovou analytiku</result>
  <result author="Matthias Huck">Producing Unseen Morphological Variants in Statistical Machine Translation</result>
  <result author="Petra Barančíková">ParaDi: Slovník parafrází českých komplexních predikátů s kategoriálním slovesem</result>
  <result author="Petr Plecháč">Distribuce předpon v českém sylabotónickém trocheji</result>
  <result author="Ondřej Dušek">Khresmoi Query Translation Test Data 2.0</result>
  <result author="Barbora Hladká">Parsing Writings of Non-Native Czech</result>
  <result author="Václava Kettnerová">Syntaktická struktura komplexních predikátů v češtině</result>
  <result author="Tom Kocmi">An Exploration of Word Embedding Initialization in Deep-Learning Tasks</result>
  <result author="Jindřich Libovický">Attention Strategies for Multi-Source Sequence-to-Sequence Learning</result>
  <result author="Jana Šindlerová">Annotation of the Evaluative Language in a Dependency Treebank</result>
  <result author="Jakub Mlynář">Sociologie (a) orální historie: Archiv vizuální historie USC Shoah Foundation dostupný v Centru vizuální historie Malach při Univerzitě Karlově</result>
  <result author="Matthias Dorfer">On the Potential of Fully Convolutional Neural Networks for Musical Symbol Detection</result>
  <result author="Šárka Zikánová">Pražský workshop Discourse Relations in Multilingual Context (Kontakt II)</result>
  <result author="Veronika Kolářová">Possible but not probable: A quantitative analysis of valency behaviour of Czech nouns in the Prague Dependency Treebank</result>
  <result author="Alexey  Sorokin">MorphoRuEval-2017: an evaluation track for the automatic morphological analysis methods for Russian</result>
  <result author="Petra Barančíková">ParaDi: Dictionary of Paraphrases of Czech Complex Predicates with Light Verbs</result>
  <result author="Christophe Onambélé">Converting Latin Treebank Data into an SQL Database for Query Purposes</result>
  <result author="Pavel Ircing">Combining Textual and Speech Features in the NLI Task Using State-of-the-Art Machine Learning Techniques</result>
  <result author="Magda Ševčíková">Identification of aspectual pairs of verbs derived by suffixation in the lexical database DeriNet</result>
  <result author="Jan Hajič, jr.">The MUSCIMA++ Dataset for Handwritten Optical Music Recognition</result>
  <result author="Tom Kocmi">CUNI NMT System for WAT 2017 Translation Tasks</result>
  <result author="Michal Novák">Incorporating Coreference to Automatic Evaluation of Coherence in Essays</result>
  <result author="Ondřej Bojar">Dávkový překlad IBM</result>
  <result author="Ondřej Bojar">Results of the WMT17 Metrics Shared Task</result>
  <result author="Jana Straková">Czech Named Entity Corpus</result>
  <result author="Ahmad Aghaebrahimian">Constrained Deep Answer Sentence Selection</result>
  <result author="Dima Taji">Universal Dependencies for Arabic</result>
  <result author="Roman Sudarikov">Instalace a uživatelské nastavení pro česko-anglický a anglicko-český překlad českých odborných termínů směrnice INSPIRE a thesaurů GEMET a AgroVoc (prostorová data) pro výhradní použití ve výzkumném projektu</result>
  <result author="Kira Droganova">Elliptic Constructions: Spotting Patterns in UD Treebanks</result>
  <result author="Klára Osolsobě">Nová automatická morfologická analýza češtiny</result>
  <result author="Milan Straka">Prague at EPE 2017: The UDPipe System</result>
  <result author="Kateřina Veselovská">Sentiment Analysis in Czech</result>
  <result author="Václava Kettnerová">Deverbal Nouns in Czech Light Verb Constructions</result>
  <result author="Bedřich Pišl">Communication with Robots using Multilayer Recurrent Networks</result>
  <result author="Zdeňka Urešová">CzEngClass – Towards a Lexicon of verb Synonyms with Valency linked to Semantic Roles</result>
  <result author="Rudolf Rosa">Slavic Forest, Norwegian Wood</result>
  <result author="Barbora Hladká">STYX .1.0</result>
  <result author="Antonio Jimeno Yepes">Findings of the WMT 2017 Biomedical Translation Shared Task</result>
  <result author="Petra Barančíková">ParaDi 2.0: Slovník jednoslovných parafrází komplexních predikátů</result>
  <result author="Michal Novák">Coreference Resolution System Not Only for Czech</result>
  <result author="Ahmad Aghaebrahimian">Hybrid Deep Open-Domain Question Answering</result>
  <result author="Shadi Saleh">Task3 Patient-Centred Information Retrieval: Team CUNI</result>
  <result author="Jan Hajič, jr.">How to Exploit Music Notation Syntax for OMR?</result>
  <result author="Eva Hajičová"> A Glimpse Under the Surface: Language Understanding May Need Deep Syntactic Structure</result>
  <result author="Jan-Thorsten Peter">The QT21 Combined Machine Translation System for English to Latvian</result>
  <result author="Michal Novák">Projection-based Coreference Resolution Using Deep Syntax</result>
  <result author="Jindřich Helcl">Neural Monkey: An Open-source Tool for Sequence Learning</result>
  <result author="Ondřej Bojar">CUNI Submission in WMT17: Chimera Goes Neural</result>
  <result author="Tom Kocmi">Curriculum Learning and Minibatch Bucketing in Neural Machine Translation</result>
  <result author="Veronika Kolářová">Valence českých deverbativních substantiv reprezentujících vybrané sémantické třídy</result>
  <result author="Marie Mikulová">Subcategorization of Adverbial Meanings Based On Corpus Data</result>
  <result author="Ondřej Dušek">Khresmoi Summary Translation Test Data 2.0</result>
  <result author="Rudolf Rosa">MonoTrans: Statistical Machine Translation from Monolingual Data</result>
  <result author="Vinit Ravishankar">A Universal Dependencies Treebank for Marathi</result>
  <result author="Loganathan Ramasamy">Tamil Dependency Treebank</result>
  <result author="Miroslav Vodolán">Hybrid Dialog State Tracker with ASR Features</result>
  <result author="Ahmad Aghaebrahimian">Quora Question Answer Dataset</result>
  <result author="David Klusáček">EFCL channelizer</result>
  <result author="Agata Savary">Annotated corpora and tools of the PARSEME Shared Task on Automatic Identification of Verbal Multiword Expressions (edition 1.0)</result>
  <result author="Rudolf Rosa">Slavic Forest, Norwegian Wood (models)</result>
  <result author="Petra Galuščáková">Česká kolekcia Malach pre testovanie multijazyčného vyhľadávania v hovorenej reči</result>
  <result author="Jakub Mlynář">Analysing Oral Histories: Social Roles and Narrative Self-Regulation in Holocaust Survivors’ Testimonies </result>
  <result author="Petra Galuščáková">Kolekcia pre viacjazyčné vyhľadávanie v českých nahrávkach korpusu Malach</result>
  <result author="Rudolf Rosa">Slavic Forest, Norwegian Wood (scripts)</result>
  <result author="Marie Mikulová">Pražský závislostní korpus mluvené češtiny (PDTSC 2.0)</result>
  <result author="Patrice Pognan">Système linguistique et calculabilité des langues slaves de l'Ouest (Nord et Sud): approches d'une complexité comparée</result>
  <result author="Rudolf Rosa">Jak pracuje internetový vyhledávač</result>
  <result author="Jan Hajič, jr.">Optical Music Recognition: Because music notation is text, too!</result>
  <result author="Ondřej Bojar">UFAL Medical Corpus 1.0</result>
  <result author="Pavel Pecina">KConnect Project</result>
  <result author="Ondřej Košarko">CLARIN DSpace</result>
  <result author="Michal Novák">Rozpoznávanie koreferencie s použitím paralelných korpusov</result>
  <result author="Ondřej Bojar">Strojový překlad do roku 2016</result>
  <result author="Eva Hajičová">What can we learn from J.-M.Zemb about negation and information structure: A view from Prague</result>
  <result author="Joakim Nivre">Universal Dependencies 2.0</result>
  <result author="Daniel Zeman">The CoNLL-U Format</result>
  <result author="Adam Przepiórkowski">Phraseology in two Slavic valency dictionaries: limitations and perspectives</result>
  <result author="Ondřej Bojar">Neural Machine Translation</result>
  <result author="Filip Ginter">CoNLL 2017 Shared Task - Automatically Annotated Raw Texts and Word Embeddings</result>
  <result author="Eva Hajičová">Theme</result>
  <result author="Ondřej Bojar">Hluboká revoluce ve strojovém překladu</result>
  <result author="Pavel Pecina">Medical-domain Machine Translation in KConnect</result>
  <result author="Jernej Vičič">Česílko Goes Open-source</result>
  <result author="Ondřej Bojar">NMT at CUNI</result>
  <result author="Joakim Nivre">EACL tutorial on Universal Dependencies</result>
  <result author="Anna Nedoluzhko">Coreference in Discourse</result>
  <result author="Veronika Kolářová">Difference between Written and Spoken Czech: The Case of Verbal Nouns Denoting an Action</result>
  <result author="Anna Nedoluzhko">Coreference in Discourse</result>
  <result author="Veronika Kolářová">NomVallex: Valenční slovník českých substantiv založený na korpusu</result>
  <result author="Ondřej Bojar">CUNI Neural Experiments</result>
  <result author="Magda Ševčíková">Modelování slovotvorných vztahů ve slovní zásobě češtiny</result>
  <result author="Daniel Zeman">Multilingual Parsing from Raw Text to Universal Dependencies. CoNLL 2017 shared task</result>
  <result author="Joakim Nivre">Universal Dependencies 2.0 – CoNLL 2017 Shared Task Development and Test Data</result>
  <result author="Magda Ševčíková">Inflectional and derivational paradigm of verbs in Czech: the role of the category of aspect</result>
  <result author="Jana Straková">Neural Network Based Named Entity Recognition</result>
  <result author="Ondřej Košarko">Beyond simple usage of handles - PIDs in DSpace</result>
  <result author="Kateřina Rysová">Hodnocení písemných prací z hlediska koherence textu</result>
  <result author="Daniel Zeman">Universality in space and time – Modern treebanking for ancient languages</result>
  <result author="Eva Hajičová">Semantic Relevance of Information Structure and its Consequences for Machine Translation</result>
  <result author="Veronika Kolářová">NomVallex: Valency Patterns of Semantically Classified Czech Nouns</result>
  <result author="Jan Hajič">Prague Dependency Treebank</result>
  <result author="Dima Taji">Universal Dependencies for Arabic</result>
  <result author="Jan Hajič">MorpInd tool for Clarabridge</result>
  <result author="Jindřich Helcl">Neural Monkey lab</result>
  <result author="Jindřich Helcl">Deep Learning in MT / NMT</result>
  <result author="Michal Novák">Coreference Resolution System Not Only for Czech</result>
  <result author="Magda Ševčíková">The suffixes -ismus and -ita in nouns in Czech: borrowing or derivation?</result>
  <result author="Daniel Zeman">Report on the CoNLL 2017 Shared Task on “Multilingual Parsing from Raw Text to Universal Dependencies”</result>
  <result author="Jarmila Panevová">Grammaticalization and Lexicalization in the Slavic Languages </result>
  <result author="Jarmila Panevová">K marginálním infinitivním konstrukcím (zejména v češtině)</result>
  <result author="Eva Hajičová">Syntax-Semantics Interface: A Plea for a Deep Dependency Sentence Structure</result>
  <result author="Jonáš Vidra">DeriNet verze 1.5</result>
  <result author="Petra Galuščáková">Text Mining</result>
  <result author="Šárka Zikánová">Understanding text coherence: Implicit discourse relations</result>
  <result author="Anna Nedoluzhko">A start is always a start of something: Unexpressed anaphoric relations as a cohesive device in Czech</result>
  <result author="Daniel Zeman">CoNLL 2017 Shared Task System Outputs</result>
  <result author="Jarmila Panevová">Od valence slovesa k valenci substantiv a adjektiv</result>
  <result author="Anna Nedoluzhko">Discourse and Coherence: A Complex Approach to Textual Phenomena in the Prague Dependency Treebank</result>
  <result author="Jan Hajič, jr.">Prototyping Full-Pipeline OMR With MUSCIMarker</result>
  <result author="Jiří Mírovský">Building a Lexicon of Discourse Connectives in an Effective Way</result>
  <result author="Anna Nedoluzhko">Comparable coreference expressions in parallel Czech, English,  Polish and Russian data</result>
  <result author="Anna Nedoluzhko">Transformations in Discourse: Interplay between DRDs, Coreference and Bridging</result>
  <result author="Karolína Hořeňovská">Výpočetní lingvistika</result>
  <result author="Jan Hajič, jr.">Detecting Noteheads in Handwritten Scores with ConvNets and Bounding Box Regression</result>
  <result author="Matiss Rikters">Visualizing Neural Machine Translation Attention and Confidence</result>
  <result author="Lucie Poláková">CzeDLex and other Lexicons of Discourse Connectives</result>
  <result author="Jiří Mírovský">CzeDLex – A Lexicon of Czech Discourse Connectives</result>
  <result author="Jiří Hana">Czech clitics - word order and haplology</result>
  <result author="Jozef Mišutka">clarin-dspace Architecture and RDA-DFT/FAIR/OAIS</result>
  <result author="Ondřej Bojar">Úvod do neuronového strojového překladu nejen pro korpusové lingvisty</result>
  <result author="Ondřej Bojar">Catching the Falling Knife of Neural MT</result>
  <result author="Jana Šindlerová">Hlásili to v rozhlase aneb vzájemné mapování lokace a aktoru v dvojjazyčném závislostním korpusu</result>
  <result author="Václava Kettnerová">Ke koreferenci u komplexních predikátů s kategoriálním slovesem</result>
  <result author="Jiří Mírovský">Petr Pořízka: Tvorba korpusů a vytěžování jazykových dat: metody, modely, nástroje.</result>
  <result author="Rudolf Rosa">Terminal-based CoNLL-file viewer, v2</result>
  <result author="Ondřej Bojar">(Not Just) An Empirical Comparison of NMT Toolkits</result>
  <result author="Ondřej Bojar">Překladatele nahradit a rozpitvat</result>
  <result author="Jan Hajič, jr.">MUSCIMA++</result>
  <result author="Joakim Nivre">Universal Dependencies 2.1</result>
  <result author="Ondřej Bojar">Strojový wikipedista? Strojovým překladem to začíná </result>
  <result author="Jaroslava Hlaváčová">Golden Rule of Morphology and Variants of Wordforms</result>
  <result author="Eva Hajičová">Syntax-Semantics Interface</result>
  <result author="Lucie Poláková">Signalling Implicit Relations: A PDTB - RST Comparison</result>
  <result author="Daniel Zeman">Slovak Dependency Treebank in Universal Dependencies</result>
  <result author="Jiří Mírovský">CzeDLex 0.5</result>
  <result author="Silvie Cinková">Modeling Semantic Distance in the Pattern Dictionary  of English Verbs</result>
  <result author="Rudolf Rosa">Cross-lingual Transfer of Dependency Parsers</result>
  <result author="Markéta Lopatková">Mezi gramatikou a slovníkem: Rodina elektronických valenčních slovníků VALLEX</result>
  <result author="Marie Mikulová">ForFun 1.0</result>
  <result author="Jaroslava Hlaváčová">Využití velkých korpusů pro morfematickou analýzu českých slovesných předpon</result>
  <result author="Dušan Variš">Improving a Neural-based Tagger for Multiword Expression Identification</result>
  <result author="Matthias Dorfer">Learning Audio–Sheet Music Correspondences for Cross-Modal Retrieval and Piece Identification</result>
  <result author="Daniel Kondratyuk">LemmaTag: Jointly Tagging and Lemmatizing for Morphologically Rich Languages with BRNNs</result>
  <result author="Michal Novák">Topic–Focus Articulation: A Third Pillar of Automatic Evaluation of Text Coherence</result>
  <result author="Marie Mikulová">What Can We Find Out about Time and Space in the ForFun Database?</result>
  <result author="Jindřich Helcl">CUNI System for the WMT18 Multimodal Translation Task</result>
  <result author="Markéta Lopatková">DATLOWE: software pro textovou analytiku</result>
  <result author="David Mareček">Extracting Syntactic Trees from Transformer Encoder Self-Attentions</result>
  <result author="Dominik Macháček">Morphological and Language-Agnostic Word Segmentation for NMT</result>
  <result author="Jakub Mlynář">Towards a Sociological Conception of Artificial Intelligence</result>
  <result author="Martin Popel">CUNI Transformer Neural MT System for WMT18</result>
  <result author="Ahmad Aghaebrahimian">Deep Neural Networks at the Service of Multilingual Parallel Sentence Extraction</result>
  <result author="Kateřina Rysová">Olympiáda v českém jazyce: 44. ročník</result>
  <result author="Jakub Náplava">Diacritics Restoration Using Neural Networks</result>
  <result author="Anna Nedoluzhko">Correlating DRDs with other types of discourse phenomena: Cross-linguistic analysis of the interplay between DRDs, coreference and bridging</result>
  <result author="Michal Novák">A Fine-grained Large-scale Analysis of Coreference Projection</result>
  <result author="Ondřej Bojar">Dávkový překlad IBM</result>
  <result author="Vincent Kríž">Czech Legal Text Treebank 2.0</result>
  <result author="Flavio Massimiliano Cecchini">Challenges in Converting the Index Thomisticus Treebank into Universal Dependencies</result>
  <result author="Franck Burlot">The WMT’18 Morpheval test suites for English-Czech, English-German, English-Finnish and Turkish-English</result>
  <result author="Jorge Calvo-Zaragoza">Discussion Group Summary: Optical Music Recognition</result>
  <result author="Václava Kettnerová">Lexicographic Potential of the Syntactic Properties of Verbs:  The Case of Reciprocity in Czech</result>
  <result author="Milan Straka">UDPipe 2.0 Prototype at CoNLL 2018 UD Shared Task</result>
  <result author="Jan Hajič, jr."> How current optical music recognition systems are becoming useful for digital libraries</result>
  <result author="Milan Straka">SumeCzech: Large Czech News-Based Summarization Dataset</result>
  <result author="Jindřich Libovický">Machine Translation Evaluation beyond the Sentence Level</result>
  <result author="Mateusz Lango">Semi-Automatic Construction of Word-Formation Networks (for Polish and Spanish)</result>
  <result author="Zdeňka Urešová">Creating a Verb Synonym Lexicon Based on a Parallel Corpus</result>
  <result author="David Kuboň">Politician -- An Imitation Game</result>
  <result author="Jindřich Libovický">Multimodal Abstractive Summarization for Open-Domain Videos</result>
  <result author="Ágnes Abuczki">Translation of "and" in a parallel TED Talk corpus of English, Czech, Hungarian, Lithuanian and French: functions and omissions</result>
  <result author="Jan Hajič, jr.">Towards Full-Pipeline Handwritten OMR with Musical Symbol Detection by U-Nets</result>
  <result author="Eva Hajičová">Identification of Thematic Discourse Relations on the Data from an Annotated Corpus of Czech</result>
  <result author="Kira Droganova">Data Conversion and Consistency of Monolingual Corpora: Russian UD Treebanks</result>
  <result author="Jaroslava Hlaváčová">Prefixal Morphemes of Czech Verbs</result>
  <result author="Petr Bělohlávek">Using Adversarial Examples in Natural Language Processing</result>
  <result author="Kira Droganova">Mind the Gap: Data Enrichment in Dependency Parsing of Elliptical Constructions</result>
  <result author="Ondřej Bojar">Findings of the 2018 Conference on Machine Translation (WMT18)</result>
  <result author="Zdeňka Urešová">A CROSS-LINGUAL SYNONYM CLASSES LEXICON</result>
  <result author="Zdeňka Urešová">Synonymy in Bilingual Context: The CzEngClass Lexicon</result>
  <result author="Silvie Cinková">Testsuite on Czech–English Grammatical Contrasts</result>
  <result author="Anna Nedoluzhko">PAWS: A Multi-lingual Parallel Treebank with Anaphoric Relations</result>
  <result author="Kateřina Rysová">The Correlation between Discourse-Anaphoric Devices and an Overall Communicative Competence in Learners‘ Essays</result>
  <result author="Zdeňka Urešová">  CzEngClass 0.1</result>
  <result author="Rudolf Rosa">CUNI x-ling: Parsing under-resourced languages in CoNLL 2018 UD Shared Task</result>
  <result author="Vladislav Kuboň">Analysis of Word Order in Multiple Treebanks</result>
  <result author="Marie Mikulová">ForFun 1.0: Prague Database of Forms and Functions -- An Invaluable Resource for Linguistic Research</result>
  <result author="Jindřich Libovický">End-to-End Non-Autoregressive Neural Machine Translation with Connectionist Temporal Classification</result>
  <result author="Václava Kettnerová">Mezi reflexivitou a reciprocitou: Poznámky k reflexivním a recipročním konstrukcím vybraných českých sloves</result>
  <result author="Tom Kocmi">CUNI NMT System for WAT 2018 Translation Tasks</result>
  <result author="Eva Hajičová">Discourse Coherence Through the Lens of an Annotated Text Corpus: A Case Study</result>
  <result author="Ondřej Cífka">Are BLEU and Meaning Representation in Opposition?</result>
  <result author="Tom Kocmi">CUNI Basque-to-English Submission in IWSLT18</result>
  <result author="Ahmad Aghaebrahimian">Deep Multi-Lingual Cross Sentence Alignment</result>
  <result author="Zdeňka Urešová">Tools for Building an Interlinked Multilingual Synonym Lexicon Network</result>
  <result author="Magdaléna Rysová">Describing CzeDLex – a Lexicon of Czech Discourse Connectives</result>
  <result author="Oldřich Krůza">Second-Generation Web Interface to Correcting ASR Output</result>
  <result author="Ondřej Bojar">EvalD Reference-Less Discourse Evaluation for WMT18</result>
  <result author="Jindřich Libovický">Solving Three Czech NLP Tasks End-to-End with Neural Models</result>
  <result author="Zdeňka Urešová">  CzEngClass 0.2</result>
  <result author="Michal Novák">A Study on Bilingually Informed Coreference Resolution</result>
  <result author="Zdeňka Urešová">Defining Verbal Synonyms: between Syntax and Semantics</result>
  <result author="Jana Šindlerová">Alternace konstrukcí s aktorem a instrumentem v paralelním česko-anglickém závislostním korpusu</result>
  <result author="Shantipriya Parida">Translating Short Segments with NMT: A Case Study in English-to-Hindi</result>
  <result author="Alexander Pacha">A Baseline for General Music Object Detection with Deep Learning</result>
  <result author="Qingsong Ma">Results of the WMT18 Metrics Shared Task: Both characters and embeddings achieve good performance</result>
  <result author="Daniel Zeman">CoNLL 2018 Shared Task: Multilingual Parsing from Raw Text to Universal Dependencies</result>
  <result author="Oldřich Krůza">Phonetic Transcription by Untrained Annotators</result>
  <result author="Erhard Hinrichs">Bridging the LAPPS Grid and CLARIN</result>
  <result author="Magdaléna Rysová">Diskurzní konektory v češtině: Od centra k periferii</result>
  <result author="Gosse Bouma">Expletives in Universal Dependency Treebanks</result>
  <result author="Ahmad Aghaebrahimian">Linguistically-based Deep Unstructured Question Answering</result>
  <result author="Jirka Hana">Universal Dependencies and Non-Native Czech</result>
  <result author="Kira Droganova">Parse Me if You Can: Artificial Treebanks for Parsing Experiments on Elliptical Constructions</result>
  <result author="Ronald Cardenas">A Morphological Analyzer for Shipibo-Konibo</result>
  <result author="Jindřich Helcl">Neural Monkey: The Current State and Beyond</result>
  <result author="Magdaléna Rysová">Primary and secondary discourse connectives: Constraints and preferences</result>
  <result author="Eva Hajičová">What We Can Learn From J.-M. Zemb About Negation and Information Structure: A View From Prague</result>
  <result author="Sonja Marković">Reflexives in Universal Dependencies</result>
  <result author="Laurence Danlos">Primary and secondary discourse connectives: definitions and lexicons</result>
  <result author="Tom Kocmi">CUNI Submissions in WMT18</result>
  <result author="Magdaléna Rysová">Practicing Students‘ Writing Skills through eLearning: Automated Evaluation of Text Coherence in Czech</result>
  <result author="Tom Kocmi">Trivial Transfer Learning for Low-Resource Neural Machine Translation</result>
  <result author="Václava Kettnerová">Enriching VALLEX with Light Verbs: From Theory to Data and Back Again</result>
  <result author="Kateřina Rysová">Discourse Connectives and Reference</result>
  <result author="Veronika Kolářová">Valency Lexicon of Czech Nouns NomVallex: Starting Point and Goals</result>
  <result author="Kira Droganova">Cross-Tagset Parsing Evaluation for Russian</result>
  <result author="Shadi Saleh">CUNI team: CLEF eHealth Consumer Health Search Task 2018</result>
  <result author="Jindřich Libovický">Input Combination Strategies for Multi-Source Transformer Decoder</result>
  <result author="Tomáš Musil">Hluboké neuronové sítě: když se počítače učí lidský jazyk</result>
  <result author="Ondřej Bojar">Neural Machine Translation: From Basics to Semiotics</result>
  <result author="Ondřej Bojar">Umělá inteligence nahrazuje překladatele</result>
  <result author="Jindřich Helcl">Czech Version of the Multi30k dataset</result>
  <result author="Jan Hajič">Prague Dependency Treebank 3.5</result>
  <result author="Kira Droganova">Artificial Treebank with Ellipsis</result>
  <result author="Ágnes Abuczki">Translation of “and” in a parallel TED Talk corpus of English, Czech, Hungarian, Lithuanian and French: functions and omissions</result>
  <result author="Tomáš Musil">Hegelovo prázdninové boogie</result>
  <result author="Puneet Dwivedi">The Forest Lion and the Bull: Morphosyntactic Annotation of the Panchatantra</result>
  <result author="Dominik Macháček">NMT System Comparison</result>
  <result author="Ondřej Bojar">Kdy neuronový strojový překlad nahradı́ překladatele?</result>
  <result author="Magda Ševčíková">Lexikální síť DeriNet: Derivační vztahy v české slovní zásobě</result>
  <result author="Jindřich Libovický">Umělá inteligence a automatický překlad</result>
  <result author="Marie Mikulová">Search for the Relation of Form and Function Using the ForFun Database</result>
  <result author="Rudolf Rosa">Modelování závislostní syntaxe napříč jazyky</result>
  <result author="Martin Popel">Training Tips for the Transformer Model</result>
  <result author="Markéta Lopatková">Mezi reflexivitou a reciprocitou: Poznámky k reflexivním a recipročním konstrukcím vybraných českých sloves</result>
  <result author="Rudolf Rosa">Plaintext Wikipedia dump 2018</result>
  <result author="Aleksei Kelli">Implementation of an Open Science Policy in the context of management of CLARIN language resources: a need for changes?</result>
  <result author="Ágnes Abuczki">The underspecified connective "and" in a parallel TED Talk corpus: functions, translation and implicitation</result>
  <result author="Šárka Zikánová">A pilot study on underspecified discourse connectives in the TED Talk parallel corpus</result>
  <result author="Anna Nedoluzhko">PAWS</result>
  <result author="Magda Ševčíková">Modelling Morphographemic Alternations in Derivation of Czech</result>
  <result author="Magda Ševčíková">Discerning action nouns formed by a zero suffix from unmotivated nouns</result>
  <result author="Anna Nedoluzhko">Pronominal Adverbs in German and their Equivalents in English, Czech and Russian: Evidence from the Parallel Corpus</result>
  <result author="Daniel Zeman">Uniformity versus Diversity: Dependency Grammar for All</result>
  <result author="Daniel Zeman">Core Arguments in Universal Dependencies</result>
  <result author="Zdeňka Urešová">A Cross-lingual Synonym Classes Lexicon</result>
  <result author="Rudolf Rosa">Discovering the structure of natural language sentences by semi-supervised methods</result>
  <result author="Anna Nedoluzhko">Analysis of coreferential expressions in PAWS</result>
  <result author="Ondřej Bojar">Rozumí neuronový strojový překlad tomu, co překládá?</result>
  <result author="Rudolf Rosa">Looking for linguistic structures in neural networks</result>
  <result author="Tomáš Musil">Neuronové sítě a matematická lingvistika</result>
  <result author="Matthias Dorfer">Attention as a Perspective for Learning Tempo-invariant Audio Queries</result>
  <result author="Joakim Nivre">Universal Dependencies 2.2</result>
  <result author="Jindřich Libovický">Czech image captioning, machine translation, and sentiment analysis (Neural Monkey models)</result>
  <result author="Loïc Barrault">Grounded Sequence-to-Sequence Transduction</result>
  <result author="Eva Hajičová">Topic/Focus vs. Given/New: Information Structure and Coreference Relations in an Annotated Corpus</result>
  <result author="Jarmila Panevová">Diateze a reciprocita (na materiálu češtiny)</result>
  <result author="Václava Kettnerová">Poznámky k systému tzv. komplementů v češtině</result>
  <result author="Ronald Cardenas">Morphological Analyzer for Shipibo-Konibo</result>
  <result author="Magda Ševčíková">Hranice flektivní a derivační morfologie: Případ předpony po- u českých sloves</result>
  <result author="Jakub Mlynář">„To jsme všechny měly ten pocit – musíme se toho zbavit, musíme na to zapomenout“: Reflexe připomínání holocaustu v rozhovorech s česko-slovenskými přeživšími</result>
  <result author="Anna Nedoluzhko">Interplay between conjunctions, coreference and bridging in Geman, English and Czech</result>
  <result author="David Mareček">Extracting Syntactic Trees from NMT Encoder Self-Attentions</result>
  <result author="Jan Hajič, jr.">A Case for Instrinsic Evaluation of Optical Music Recognition</result>
  <result author="Ondřej Bojar">A Vision for (Computational) Linguistics</result>
  <result author="Jan Hajič, jr.">Optical Music Recognition for Dummies</result>
  <result author="Kira Droganova">An interface between the Czech valency lexicon PDT-Vallex and corpus manager KonText</result>
  <result author="Jonáš Vidra">Morphological segmentation of Czech Words</result>
  <result author="Martin Popel">Machine Translation Using Syntactic Analysis</result>
  <result author="Michal Novák">Coreference from the Cross-lingual Perspective</result>
  <result author="Jonáš Vidra">DeriNet verze 1.6</result>
  <result author="Magda Ševčíková">A language resource specialized in Czech word-formation: Recent achievements in developing the DeriNet database</result>
  <result author="Markéta Lopatková">The Tricky Case of Czech Reflexives</result>
  <result author="Rudolf Rosa">Cross-lingual Syntactic Parsing</result>
  <result author="Jarmila Panevová">Konkurence předložkových pádů u jádra lokálních určení v češtině</result>
  <result author="Radek Čech">Quantitative Analysis of Syntactic  Dependency in Czech</result>
  <result author="Jiří Mírovský">EVALD 3.0 for Foreigners – Evaluator of Discourse</result>
  <result author="Daniel Zeman">CoNLL 2018 Shared Task System Outputs</result>
  <result author="Jirka Hana">Syntactic annotation of a second-language learner corpus</result>
  <result author="Rudolf Rosa">Digital Humanities at Dibris, University of Genova, Italy</result>
  <result author="Agata Savary">The PARSEME multilingual corpus of verbal multiword expressions</result>
  <result author="Jiří Mírovský">EVALD 3.0 – Evaluator of Discourse</result>
  <result author="Jakub Mlynář">Collective memory as an interactional practice: The case of the Czech-Jewish experience in Switzerland during the WWII period</result>
  <result author="Joakim Nivre">Universal Dependencies 2.3</result>
  <result author="Martin Popel">Strojový překlad a umělá inteligence</result>
  <result author="Lukáš Kyjánek">Morphological Resources of Derivational Word-Formation Relations</result>
  <result author="Lucie Poláková">Building Lexicons of Discourse Connectives</result>
  <result author="Petra Barančíková">Paraphrases of verbal multiword expressions: the case of Czech light verbs and idioms</result>
  <result author="Ondřej Bojar">Promises and Pitfalls of Neural MT</result>
  <result author="Daniel Zeman">Universal Dependencies and the Slavic Languages</result>
  <result author="Jakub Mlynář">Praktická časovost práce s digitální orální historií na třech gymnáziích v ČR</result>
  <result author="Šárka Zikánová">Enriched Discourse Annotation of PDiT Subset 1.0 (PDiT-EDA 1.0)</result>
  <result author="Markéta Lopatková">VALLEX 3.5 - Valenční slovník českých sloves</result>
  <result author="Ondřej Bojar">Počítačová lingvistika a strojový překlad: Zcela nový svět díky hlubokému učení</result>
  <result author="Daniel Zeman">The World of Tokens, Tags and Trees</result>
  <result author="Jarmila Panevová">Aktant, nebo volné doplnění? (K netypickým formám ve valenčním poli substantiv)</result>
  <result author="Magda Ševčíková">Derivation of Czech verbs and the category of aspect</result>
  <result author="Michal Novák">Coreference from the Cross-lingual Perspective</result>
  <result author="Veronika Kolářová">Předložková vyjádření adnominálních valenčních doplnění</result>
  <result author="Tereza Vojtěchová">SAO WMT19 Test Suite: Machine Translation of Audit Reports</result>
  <result author="Ondřej Dušek">Automatic Quality Estimation for Natural Language Generation: Ranting (Jointly Rating and Ranking)</result>
  <result author="Tomáš Musil">Examining Structure of Word Embeddings with PCA</result>
  <result author="Behzad Moradi">Unsupervised Word Sense Disambiguation Using Word Embeddings</result>
  <result author="Eva Hajičová">MICHAEL ALEXANDER KIRKWOOD HALLIDAY (1925–2018) (obituary)</result>
  <result author="Magdaléna Rysová">Coherence Errors in Learners’ Essays and a Possibility of Their Improvement through EVALD (Automated Evaluator of Discourse)</result>
  <result author="Kira Droganova">ÚFAL–Oslo at MRP 2019: Garage Sale Semantic Parsing</result>
  <result author="Jindřich Helcl">CUNI System for the WMT19 Robustness Task</result>
  <result author="Ronald Cardenas">CUNI–Malta system at CoNLL–SIGMORPHON 2019 Shared Task on Morphological Analysis and Lemmatization in context: Operation-based word formation</result>
  <result author="Václava Kettnerová">Reflexives in Czech from a Dependency Perspective</result>
  <result author="Giedre Valunaite Oleskeviciene">Fuzzy Boundaries in the Different Functions and Translations of the Discourse Marker and</result>
  <result author="Dušan Variš">Unsupervised Pretraining for Neural Machine Translation Using Elastic Weight Consolidation</result>
  <result author="Ludivine Crible">Functions and translations of underspecified discourse markers in TED Talks: a parallel corpus study on five languages</result>
  <result author="Rudolf Rosa">Attempting to separate inflection and derivation using vector space representations</result>
  <result author="Michal Novák">Exploiting Large Unlabeled Data in Automatic Evaluation of Coherence in Czech</result>
  <result author="Ivan Smurov">AGRR-2019: Automatic Gapping Resolution for Russian</result>
  <result author="Lukáš Kyjánek">Universal Derivations Kickoff: A Collection of Harmonized Derivational Resources for Eleven Languages</result>
  <result author="Hamid Haghdoost">Building a Morphological Network for Persian on Top of a Morpheme-Segmented Lexicon</result>
  <result author="Daniel Kondratyuk">Replacing Linguists with Dummies: A Serious Need for Trivial Baselinesin Multi-Task Neural Machine Translation</result>
  <result author="Petra Barančíková">In Search for Linear Relations  in Sentence Embedding Spaces</result>
  <result author="Marie Mikulová">Subkategorizace adverbiálních významů (hranice mezi obsahem a významem)</result>
  <result author="Eva Hajičová">Již Čapkovi roboti byli obdařeni řečí</result>
  <result author="Jaroslava Hlaváčová">Aggregates and Variants in two Czech morphological approaches</result>
  <result author="Svatava Škodová">Comparison of Automatic and Human Evaluation of L2 Texts in Czech</result>
  <result author="Meisyarah Dwiastuti">English-Indonesian Neural Machine Translation for Spoken Language Domains</result>
  <result author="Toshiaki Nakazawa">Overview of the 6th Workshop on Asian Translation</result>
  <result author="Marie Mikulová">Delimiting Adverbial Meanings. A corpus-based comparative study on Czech spatial prepositions and their English equivalents</result>
  <result author="Milan Straka">ÚFAL MRPipe at MRP 2019: UDPipe Goes Semantic in the Meaning Representation Parsing Shared Task</result>
  <result author="Klára Osolsobě">NovaMorf: konec dlouhého období konvergencí a divergencí ve zpracování české morfologie</result>
  <result author="Simon Keizer">User Evaluation of a Multi-dimensional Statistical Dialogue System</result>
  <result author="Vladimír Petkevič">Parts of Speech in NovaMorf, a New Morphological Annotation of Czech</result>
  <result author="Tomáš Musil">Derivational Morphological Relations in Word Embeddings</result>
  <result author="Thuong-Hai Pham">Promoting the Knowledge of Source Syntax in Transformer NMT Is Not Needed</result>
  <result author="Jindřich Libovický">Neuronové sítě a automatický překlad</result>
  <result author="Eva Hajičová">Různé pojetí dichotomie v informační struktuře věty ve světle anotovaného korpusu</result>
  <result author="Ondřej Dušek">Semantic Noise Matters for Neural Natural Language Generation</result>
  <result author="Ondřej Dušek">Neural Generation for Czech: Data and Baselines</result>
  <result author="Kateřina Rysová">A Test Suite and Manual Evaluation of Document-Level NMT at WMT19</result>
  <result author="Shantipriya Parida">OdiEnCorp: Odia-English and Odia-Only Corpus for Machine Translation</result>
  <result author="Stephan Oepen">MRP 2019: Cross-Framework Meaning Representation Parsing</result>
  <result author="Jan Hajič">A Multilingual Crossover between Types of Resources</result>
  <result author="Kira Droganova">Towards Deep Universal Dependencies</result>
  <result author="Ivana Kvapilíková">CUNI Systems for the Unsupervised News Translation Task in WMT 2019</result>
  <result author="Shruti Palaskar">Multimodal Abstractive Summarization for How2 Videos</result>
  <result author="Eva Hajičová">Ordering of Adverbials of Time and Place in Grammars and in an Annotated English–Czech Parallel Corpus</result>
  <result author="Martin Popel">Domain Adaptation of Document-Level NMT in IWSLT19</result>
  <result author="Magdaléna Rysová">Jana Hoffmannová, Jiří Homoláč, Kamila Mrázková (eds.): Syntax mluvené češtiny, Praha: Academia, 2019</result>
  <result author="Hamed Alavi">On the Temporality of Adaptive Built Environments</result>
  <result author="Kateřina Rysová">Anaphoric Connective Database</result>
  <result author="Anna Nedoluzhko">Towards Automatic Minuting of Meetings</result>
  <result author="Milan Straka">Czech Text Processing with Contextual Embeddings: POS Tagging, Lemmatization, Parsing and NER</result>
  <result author="Qingsong Ma">Results of the WMT19 Metrics Shared Task: Segment-Level and Strong MT Systems Pose Big Challenges </result>
  <result author="Jakub Náplava">CUNI System for the Building Educational Applications 2019 Shared Task: Grammatical Error Correction</result>
  <result author="Zdeňka Urešová">CzEngClass: Contextually-based Synonymy and Valency of Verbs in a Bilingual Setting</result>
  <result author="Rudolf Rosa">CoNLL 2018 Shared Task Team CUNI-x-ling</result>
  <result author="Tom Kocmi">CUNI Submission for Low-Resource Languages in WMT News 2019</result>
  <result author="Milan Straka">UDPipe at SIGMORPHON 2019: Contextualized Embeddings, Regularization with Morphological Categories, Corpora Merging</result>
  <result author="Jarmila Panevová">Úvahy nad příslovečnými určeními a jejich klasifikací</result>
  <result author="Erion Çano">Efficiency Metrics for Data-Driven Models: A Text Summarization Case Study</result>
  <result author="Šárka Zikánová">Explicit and Implicit Discourse Relations in the Prague Discourse Treebank</result>
  <result author="Kateřina Rysová">Jubilejní 45. ročník Olympiády v českém jazyce</result>
  <result author="Shantipriya Parida">Idiap NMT System for WAT 2019 Multi-Modal Translation Task</result>
  <result author="David Mareček">From Balustrades to Pierre Vinken: Looking for Syntax in Transformer Self-Attentions</result>
  <result author="Maria Ponomareva">AGRR 2019: Corpus for Gapping Resolution in Russian</result>
  <result author="Jonáš Vidra">DeriNet 2.0: Towards an All-in-One Word-Formation Resource</result>
  <result author="Daniel Kondratyuk">75 Languages, 1 Model: Parsing Universal Dependencies Universally</result>
  <result author="Ebrahim Ansari">Supervised Morphological Segmentation Using Rich Annotated Lexicon</result>
  <result author="Ondřej Bojar">Representation of sentence meaning (A JNLE Special Issue)</result>
  <result author="Francis M. Tyers">A Biscriptual Morphological Transducer for Crimean Tatar</result>
  <result author="Martin Popel">English-Czech Systems in WMT19: Document-Level Transformer</result>
  <result author="Jana Straková">Neural Architectures for Nested NER through Linearization</result>
  <result author="Erion Çano">Sentiment Analysis of Czech Texts: An Algorithmic Survey</result>
  <result author="Shantipriya Parida">Hindi Visual Genome: A Dataset for Multimodal English-to-Hindi Machine Translation</result>
  <result author="Jakub Náplava">Grammatical Error Correction in Low-Resource Scenarios</result>
  <result author="Jindřich Libovický">Neural Networks as Explicit Word-Based Rules</result>
  <result author="Erion Çano">Keyphrase Generation: A Multi-Aspect Survey</result>
  <result author="Zdeňka Urešová">SynSemClass 1.0</result>
  <result author="Dominik Macháček">A Speech Test Set of Practice Business Presentations with Additional Relevant Texts</result>
  <result author="Shadi Saleh">Term Selection for Query Expansion in Medical Cross-Lingual Information Retrieval</result>
  <result author="Loïc Barrault">Findings of the 2019 Conference on Machine Translation (WMT19)</result>
  <result author="Erion Çano">Keyphrase Generation: A Text Summarization Struggle</result>
  <result author="Zdeňka Urešová">Parallel Dependency Treebank Annotated with Interlinked Verbal Synonym Classes and Roles</result>
  <result author="Shadi Saleh">An Extended CLEF eHealth Test Collection for Cross-lingual Information Retrieval in the Medical Domain</result>
  <result author="Eva Hajičová">A Plea for Information Structure as a Part of Meaning Representation</result>
  <result author="Ondřej Bojar">Strojový překlad pro investigativní účely</result>
  <result author="Pavel Pecina">Cross-lingual Information Retrieval</result>
  <result author="Rudolf Rosa">Deep Neural Networks in Natural Language Processing</result>
  <result author="Jindřich Libovický">Multimodality in Machine Translation</result>
  <result author="Pavel Straňák">CLARIN-DSpace repository at LINDAT/CLARIN : LINDAT/CLARIN FAIR repository for language data</result>
  <result author="Ondřej Bojar">Otevírá umělá inteligence cestu k porozumění lidské řeči?</result>
  <result author="Shadi Saleh">Extended CLEF eHealth 2013-2015 IR Test Collection</result>
  <result author="Daniel Zeman">Reflexiva v Universal Dependencies</result>
  <result author="Pavel Straňák">CLARIN-DSpace - Fully integrated repository for scientific data and tools</result>
  <result author="Šárka Zikánová">Cohesion in Czech: Semantics of implicit and explicit discourse relations</result>
  <result author="Joakim Nivre">Universal Dependencies 2.4</result>
  <result author="Jakub Mlynář">Sociological aspects of oral history in the digital age</result>
  <result author="Jonáš Vidra">DeriNet verze 2.0</result>
  <result author="Aleksei Kelli">Processing personal data without the consent of the data subject for the development and use of language resources</result>
  <result author="Anna Nedoluzhko">Schnellere Sterne tendieren dazu, sehr hell zu sein: A case of correlative constructions as German, Czech and Russian translations from English</result>
  <result author="Jindřich Libovický">Multimodality in Machine Translation</result>
  <result author="Pavel Pecina">Breaking the Language Barrier in Health-related Web Search</result>
  <result author="Milan Straka">Evaluating Contextualized Embeddings on 54 Languages in POS Tagging, Lemmatization and Dependency Parsing</result>
  <result author="Silvie Cinková">Žánrová preference v narativech dětí mladšího školního věku</result>
  <result author="Rudolf Rosa">Unsupervised Lemmatization as Embeddings-Based Word Clustering</result>
  <result author="Rudolf Rosa">Inducing Syntactic Trees from BERT Representations</result>
  <result author="Jakub Mlynář">The temporal organization of classroom work with digital oral history</result>
  <result author="Jindřich Libovický">Probing Representations Learned by Multimodal Recurrent and Transformer Models</result>
  <result author="Magda Ševčíková">Aspect in loan verbal neologisms in Czech</result>
  <result author="Eva Hajičová">Information Structure in an Annotated Parallel English-Czech Corpus: A Comparative Probe</result>
  <result author="Václava Kettnerová">The role of the reflexives in valency: Evidence from Czech</result>
  <result author="Tom Kocmi">MTM19 Tutorial: Transfer Learning for Low-Resource Languages</result>
  <result author="Jarmila Panevová">Studie z české morfologie a syntaxe (Vybrané stati)</result>
  <result author="David Mareček">LSD: Linguistic Structure Representation in Neural Networks</result>
  <result author="Lukáš Kyjánek">Universal Derivations v0.5</result>
  <result author="Jakub Mlynář">Making sense of digital oral history</result>
  <result author="Rudolf Rosa">Automatic Generation of Theatre Play Scripts</result>
  <result author="Anna Vernerová">Lexicographic treatment of the valency aspects of verbal diatheses</result>
  <result author="Václava Kettnerová">Reflexiva v češtině z valenčního hlediska</result>
  <result author="Lucie Poláková">Anaphoric Connectives and Long-Distance Discourse Relations in Czech</result>
  <result author="Silvie Cinková">Stylometry in Literary Translation via Universal Dependencies: Finally Breaking the Language Barrier?</result>
  <result author="Jiří Kocián">Challenges of integrating multiple divergent audiovisual oral history collections: the case of the Malach Center for visual history in Prague</result>
  <result author="Silvie Cinková">Evaluation of taggers for 19th-century fiction</result>
  <result author="Michal Novák">EVALD 4.0 for Foreigners – Evaluator of Discourse</result>
  <result author="Jakub Sláma">On the Valency of Various Types of Adverbs and Its Lexicographic Description</result>
  <result author="Jaroslava Hlaváčová">Modifications of the Czech morphological dictionary for consistent corpus annotation</result>
  <result author="Michal Novák">EVALD 4.0 for Beginners – Evaluator of Discourse</result>
  <result author="Václava Kettnerová">Towards Reciprocal Deverbal Nouns in Czech: From Reciprocal Verbs to Reciprocal Nouns</result>
  <result author="Jakub Mlynář">Double touch: A single case analysis of embodied action in classroom interaction</result>
  <result author="Michal Novák">EVALD 4.0 – Evaluator of Discourse</result>
  <result author="Zdeňka Urešová">Meaning and Semantic Roles in CzEngClass Lexicon</result>
  <result author="Veronika Kolářová">Non-systemic valency behavior of Czech deverbal nouns based on the NomVallex lexicon</result>
  <result author="Šárka Zikánová">Nepřišel, pršelo. Implicitní diskurzní vztahy v češtině.</result>
  <result author="Michal Novák">Coherence Evaluation in Czech: Utilization of Large Unlabeled data</result>
  <result author="Magda Ševčíková">Introducing Semantic Labels into the DeriNet Network</result>
  <result author="Kateřina Rysová">EVALD – a Pioneer Application for Automated Essay Scoring in Czech</result>
  <result author="Martin Popel">Biases and perils of MT evaluation</result>
  <result author="Daniel Zeman">Universal Dependencies 2.5</result>
  <result author="Eva Hajičová">Odešel významný český lingvista Petr Sgall </result>
  <result author="Daniel Zeman">Towards Deep Universal Dependencies</result>
  <result author="Jindřich Libovický">How Language-Neutral is Multilingual BERT?</result>
  <result author="Jana Straková">Hluboké učení v automatické analýze českého textu</result>
  <result author="Kateřina Rysová">Lexicon of Czech and German Anaphoric Connectives</result>
  <result author="Pavlína Synková">CzeDLex 0.6</result>
  <result author="Tom Kocmi">Exploring Benefits of Transfer Learning in Neural Machine Translation</result>
  <result author="Martin Popel">CUNI English-Czech and English-Polish Systems in WMT20: Robust Document-Level Training</result>
  <result author="Shantipriya Parida">OdiEnCorp 2.0: Odia-English Parallel Corpus for Machine Translation</result>
  <result author="Petra Barančíková">COSTRA 1.0: A Dataset of Complex Sentence Transformations</result>
  <result author="Zdeněk Kasner">Data-to-Text Generation with Iterative Text Editing</result>
  <result author="Eva Hajičová">K otázce tzv. kulisy ve světle paralelního korpusu</result>
  <result author="Václava Kettnerová">Ke způsobům vyjádření vzájemnosti v češtině</result>
  <result author="Jiří Mírovský">CzeDLex 0.6 and its Representation in the PML-TQ</result>
  <result author="Kateřina Rysová">Odborný seminář Jazyk, text, dialog – vzpomínka na Světlu Čmejrkovou a Františka Daneše</result>
  <result author="Jonáš Vidra">Next Step in Online Querying and Visualization of Word-Formation Networks</result>
  <result author="Václava Kettnerová">Towards a Semi-Automatic Detection of Reflexive and Reciprocal Constructions and Their Representation in a Valency Lexicon</result>
  <result author="Zdeněk Kasner">Train Hard, Finetune Easy: Multilingual Denoising for RDF-to-Text Generation</result>
  <result author="Ọlájídé Ishola">Yorùbá Dependency Treebank (YTB)</result>
  <result author="Ivana Kvapilíková">Unsupervised Multilingual Sentence Embeddings for Parallel Corpus Mining</result>
  <result author="Dominik Macháček">ELITR Non-Native Speech Translation at IWSLT 2020</result>
  <result author="Peter Polák">CUNI Neural ASR with Phoneme-Level Intermediate Step for Non-Native SLT at IWSLT 2020</result>
  <result author="Tom Kocmi">Efficiently Reusing Old Models Across Languages via Transfer Learning</result>
  <result author="Atul Kumar Ojha">Universal Dependency Treebanks for Low-Resource Indian Languages: The Case of Bhojpuri</result>
  <result author="Zdeňka Urešová">Syntactic-Semantic Classes of Context-Sensitive Synonyms Based on a Bilingual Corpus</result>
  <result author="Loïc Barrault">Findings of the 2020 Conference on Machine Translation (WMT20)</result>
  <result author="Marie Mikulová">Manual for Morphological Annotation, Revision for the Prague Dependency Treebank - Consolidated 2020 release</result>
  <result author="Ivana Kvapilíková">CUNI Systems for the Unsupervised and Very Low Resource Translation Task in WMT20</result>
  <result author="Maria Eskevich">CLARIN: Distributed Language Resources and Technology in a European Infrastructure</result>
  <result author="Rudolf Rosa">THEaiTRE: Artificial Intelligence to Write a Theatre Play</result>
  <result author="Dario Franceschini">Removing European Language Barriers with Innovative Machine Translation Technology</result>
  <result author="Ondřej Dušek">Evaluating Semantic Accuracy of Data-to-Text Generation with Natural Language Inference</result>
  <result author="Ulrich Germann">Speed-optimized, Compact Student Models that Distill Knowledge from a Larger Teacher Model: the UEDIN-CUNI Submission to the WMT 2020 News Translation Task</result>
  <result author="Tomasz Limisiewicz">Universal Dependencies according to BERT: both more specific and more general</result>
  <result author="Gosse Bouma">Overview of the IWPT 2020 Shared Task on Parsing into Enhanced Universal Dependencies</result>
  <result author="Jindřich Libovický">The LMU Munich System for the WMT20 Very Low Resource Supervised MT Task</result>
  <result author="Veronika Kolářová">NomVallex 1.0 - Valenční slovník substantiv</result>
  <result author="Petra Barančíková">Costra 1.1: An Inquiry into Geometric Properties of Sentence Spaces</result>
  <result author="Václava Kettnerová">Derived Lexical Reciprocal Verbs in Czech</result>
  <result author="Jonathan Verner">PyVallex: A Processing System for Valency Lexicon Data</result>
  <result author="Ika Alfina">Selecting the Universal Dependencies Morphological Features for Indonesian Dependency Treebank</result>
  <result author="Nitika Mathur">Results of the WMT20 Metrics Shared Task</result>
  <result author="Martin Vastl">Predicting Typological Features in WALS using Language Embeddings and Conditional Probabilities: ÚFAL Submission to the SIGTYP 2020 Shared Task</result>
  <result author="Tomáš Nekvinda">One Model, Many Languages: Meta-learning for Multilingual Text-to-Speech</result>
  <result author="Tom Kocmi">Gender Coreference and Bias Evaluation at WMT 2020</result>
  <result author="Erion Çano">How Many Pages? Paper Length Prediction from the Metadata</result>
  <result author="Václava Kettnerová">Reciprocity in Czech Light Verb Constructions: The Dependency Perspective</result>
  <result author="Ebrahim Ansari">FINDINGS OF THE IWSLT 2020 EVALUATION CAMPAIGN</result>
  <result author="Lucie Poláková">Mining Local Discourse Annotation for Features of Global Discourse Structure</result>
  <result author="Jonáš Kratochvíl">Large Corpus of Czech Parliament Plenary Hearings</result>
  <result author="Zdeňka Urešová">SynSemClass 3.0</result>
  <result author="Joakim Nivre">Universal Dependencies v2: An Evergrowing Multilingual Treebank Collection</result>
  <result author="Kateřina Macková">Reading Comprehension in Czech via Machine Translation and Cross-lingual Transfer</result>
  <result author="Akshay Aggarwal">Estimating POS Annotation Consistency of Different Treebanks in a Language</result>
  <result author="Jindřich Libovický">On the Language Neutrality of Pre-trained Multilingual Representations</result>
  <result author="Toshiaki Nakazawa">Overview of the 7th Workshop on Asian Translation</result>
  <result author="Vilém Zouhar">Outbound Translation User Interface Ptakopet: A Pilot Study</result>
  <result author="Ondřej Bojar">ELITR: European Live Translator</result>
  <result author="Jarmila Panevová">Reciproka ve slovníku a v syntaxi</result>
  <result author="Veronika Kolářová">Substantiva tvořená od sloves se supletivními kořeny: Korpusová studie deverbativ s kořeny klád a lož</result>
  <result author="Jan Hajič">Prague Dependency Treebank - Consolidated 1.0</result>
  <result author="Stephan Oepen">MRP 2020: The Second Shared Task on Cross-Framework and Cross-Lingual Meaning Representation Parsing</result>
  <result author="Abhishek Agrawal">Eyes on the Parse: Using Gaze Features in Syntactic Parsing</result>
  <result author="Jarmila Panevová">Funkční generativní popis  – rámec pro konzistentní popis gramatiky</result>
  <result author="Eva Hajičová">Read, if you want to be read by others</result>
  <result author="Jindřich Libovický">Expand and Filter: CUNI and LMU Systems for the WNGT 2020 Duolingo Shared Task</result>
  <result author="Vilém Zouhar">WMT20 Document-Level Markable Error Exploration</result>
  <result author="Shubham Agarwal">Proceedings of the 1st Workshop on Evaluating NLG Evaluation</result>
  <result author="Xinnuo Xu">Fact-based Content Weighting for Evaluating Abstractive Summarisation</result>
  <result author="Rudolf Rosa">Measuring Memorization Effect in Word-Level Neural Networks Probing</result>
  <result author="Jiří Kocián">Malach User Interface 1.0</result>
  <result author="Lucie Poláková">GeCzLex: Lexicon of Czech and German Anaphoric Connectives</result>
  <result author="Magda Ševčíková">The suffixes -ismus and -ita in nouns in Czech</result>
  <result author="Georg Rehm">The European Language Technology Landscape in 2020: Language-Centric and Human-Centric AI for Cross-Cultural Communication in Multilingual Europe</result>
  <result author="Erion Çano">Two Huge Title and Keyword Generation Corpora of Research Articles</result>
  <result author="Zdeňka Urešová">SynSemClass Linked Lexicon: Mapping Synonymy between Languages</result>
  <result author="Barbora Štěpánková">K možnostem zachycení pragmatické složky významu v jednojazyčném výkladovém slovníku (na příkladu hesel z oblasti etnografie a antropologie)</result>
  <result author="Tomasz Limisiewicz">Syntax Representation in Word Embeddings and Neural Networks – A Survey</result>
  <result author="Milan Straka">UDPipe at EvaLatin 2020: Contextualized Embeddings and Treebank Embeddings</result>
  <result author="Jan Vainer">SpeedySpeech: Efficient Neural Speech Synthesis</result>
  <result author="Shantipriya Parida">ODIANLP’s Participation in WAT2020</result>
  <result author="Hadi Abdi Khojasteh">LSCP: Enhanced Large Scale Colloquial Persian Language Understanding</result>
  <result author="Jan Hajič">MorfFlex CZ 2.0</result>
  <result author="Daniel Zeman">FGD at MRP 2020: Prague Tectogrammatical Graphs</result>
  <result author="Marsida Toska">Universal Dependencies for Albanian</result>
  <result author="Jorge Calvo-Zaragoza">Understanding Optical Music Recognition</result>
  <result author="Jiří Kocián">Malach Center for Visual History on its 10th Anniversary: Compendium of Papers of the Prague Visual History and Digital Humanities Conference 2020.</result>
  <result author="Jan Bodnár">Semi-supervised Induction of Morpheme Boundaries in Czech Using a Word-Formation Network</result>
  <result author="Silvie Cinková">Stylometry in a Bilingual Setup</result>
  <result author="Barbora Štěpánková">The MorfFlex Dictionary of Czech as a Source of Linguistic Data</result>
  <result author="Zdeňka Urešová">SynSemClass 2.0</result>
  <result author="Jan Oldřich Krůza">Czech parliament meeting recordings as ASR training data</result>
  <result author="Georg Rehm">European Language Grid: An Overview</result>
  <result author="David Samuel">ÚFAL at MRP 2020: Permutation-invariant Semantic Parsing in PERIN</result>
  <result author="Barbora Hladká">Compiling Czech Parliamentary Stenographic Protocols into a Corpus</result>
  <result author="Shadi Saleh">Document Translation vs. Query Translation for Cross-Lingual Information Retrieval in the Medical Domain</result>
  <result author="Dominik Macháček">Presenting Simultaneous Translation in Limited Space</result>
  <result author="Jindřich Libovický">Towards Reasonably-Sized Character-Level Transformer NMT by Finetuning Subword Systems</result>
  <result author="Mateusz Lango">Semi-Automatic Construction of Word-Formation Networks</result>
  <result author="Daniel Zeman">Universal Dependencies</result>
  <result author="Karolína Bukovská">Prisoner tattoo as a situated social object in Holocaust survivors’ visual history testimonies</result>
  <result author="Ondřej Dušek">Evaluating the state-of-the-art of End-to-End Natural Language Generation: The E2E NLG challenge</result>
  <result author="Lucie Poláková">Implicit relation questions surfacing in Prague discourse projects</result>
  <result author="Šárka Zikánová">Factors influencing implicit discourse relations in Czech</result>
  <result author="Hadi Abdi Khojasteh">Large-Scale Colloquial Persian 0.5</result>
  <result author="Jakub Mlynář">"The phenomenon of repetition": Re-watching a video clip in classroom work with digital oral history</result>
  <result author="Daniel Zeman">Enhanced and Deep Universal Dependencies for Many Languages</result>
  <result author="Rudolf Rosa">Cross-Lingual Information Retrieval DEMO</result>
  <result author="Lucia Specia">Grounded Sequence to Sequence Transduction</result>
  <result author="Magda Ševčíková">Vzorce v odvozování slov v češtině: Aplikace paradigmatického přístupu na českou slovotvorbu</result>
  <result author="Rudolf Rosa">Cross-Lingual Information Retrieval</result>
  <result author="Barbora Hladká">ParCzech PS7 1.0</result>
  <result author="Karolína Houžvičková Šolcová">Umělá inteligence píše divadelní hru</result>
  <result author="Micha Theo Neri de Rijk">Using Word Embeddings and Collocations for Modelling Word Associations</result>
  <result author="Lukáš Kyjánek">Universal Derivations v1.0</result>
  <result author="Daniel Zeman">Universal Dependencies 2.6</result>
  <result author="Rudolf Rosa">Deliverable D7.2 Report on NLP Technologies Workshop at EUROSAI Congress</result>
  <result author="Erion Çano">Automating Text Naturalness Evaluation of NLG Systems</result>
  <result author="Erion Çano">Human or Machine: Automating Human Likeliness Evaluation of NLG Texts</result>
  <result author="Jan Hajič">ÚFAL @ Troja</result>
  <result author="Kira Droganova">Deep Universal Dependencies 2.6</result>
  <result author="Karolína Houžvičková Šolcová">R.U.R. v dobách umělé inteligence: Divadelní hru k 100 letům Čapkova díla píše robot z Matfyzu</result>
  <result author="Gosse Bouma">IWPT 2020 Shared Task Data and System Outputs</result>
  <result author="Alireza Abbas Alipour">An Advanced Profile Hidden Markov Model for Malware Detection</result>
  <result author="Jarmila Panevová">Světla Čmejrková – František Daneš: Jejich setkávání na poli gramatiky. Jazykovědné aktuality 57, č. 1 a 2, 2020, 35 – 38.</result>
  <result author="Veronika Kolářová">NomVallex I. Valenční slovník substantiv</result>
  <result author="Aleksei Kelli">The Impact of Copyright and Personal Data Laws on the Creation and Use of Language Models</result>
  <result author="Magda Ševčíková">Zero-derived nominals in a language with obligatory verbal suffixes: The case of Czech</result>
  <result author="Rudolf Rosa">Umělá inteligence a kreativita</result>
  <result author="Ingrid Fadelli">THEaiTRE: A theatre play written entirely by machines</result>
  <result author="Eva Hajičová">Focalizers and discourse relations</result>
  <result author="Rudolf Rosa">THEaiTRE: Artificial Intelligence to Write a Theatre Play</result>
  <result author="Ondřej Novotný">Scénář: Robot. Ve Švandově divadle píše hru k výročí R.U.R. umělá inteligence</result>
  <result author="Martin Popel">Strojový překlad a umělá inteligence</result>
  <result author="Zdeněk Žabokrtský">Sentence Meaning Representations across Languages: What Can We Learn from Existing Frameworks?</result>
  <result author="Daniel Zeman">SIGTYP 2020 Shared Task</result>
  <result author="Ondřej Bojar">Multi-Lingual MT Research at ÚFAL, Charles University</result>
  <result author="Daniel Zeman">Universal Dependencies: A Search for Harmonized Morphological and Syntactic Annotation</result>
  <result author="Jana Straková">NameTag 2</result>
  <result author="Martin Popel">Transforming machine translation: a deep learning system reaches news translation quality comparable to human professionals</result>
  <result author="Milan Straka">UDPipe 2</result>
  <result author="Dušan Variš">Image Captioning with Visual Object Representations Groundedin the Textual Modality</result>
  <result author="Eva Hajičová">Focalizers and Discourse Relations</result>
  <result author="Vilém Zouhar">Extending Ptakopět for Machine Translation User Interaction Experiments</result>
  <result author="Petr Král">Robot píše divadelní hru</result>
  <result author="David Mareček">Are Multilingual Neural Machine Translation Models Better at Capturing Linguistic Features?</result>
  <result author="Lukáš Kyjánek">Universal Derivations 1.0, A Growing Collection of Harmonised Word-Formation Resources</result>
  <result author="Alexandr Rosen">Compiling and annotating a learner corpus for a morphologically rich language – CzeSL, a corpus of non-native Czech</result>
  <result author="Jaroslava Hlaváčová">Konzistence morfologického slovníku MorfFlex</result>
  <result author="Veronika Dostálová">Dočkáme se digitálního Shakespeara? AI jako autor divadelní hry</result>
  <result author="Daniel Zeman">Universal Dependencies 2.7</result>
  <result author="Martin Uhlíř">Ze života robotů</result>
  <result author="Hamid Haghdoost">Morphological Networks for Persian and Turkish: What Can Be Induced from Morpheme Segmentation?</result>
  <result author="Marie Mikulová">Vyjadřování prostorových určení v textu psaném a mluveném (Případová studie)</result>
  <result author="Pavel Pecina">eTranslation - strojový překlad pro veřejnou správu</result>
  <result author="Rudolf Rosa">THEaiTRE: Umělá inteligence píše divadelní hru</result>
  <result author="Pavel Pecina">Vyhledávání informací v medicínských textech</result>
  <result author="Lucie Poláková">CzeDLex 0.7</result>
  <result author="Václava Kettnerová">Valence českých verbálních jmen v nominálních konstrukcích a ve verbonominálních predikátech s kategoriálním slovesem</result>
  <result author="Barbora Hladká">ParCzech PS7 2.0</result>
  <result author="Rudolf Rosa">THEaiTRE: Umělá inteligence píše divadelní hru</result>
  <result author="David Mareček">Hidden in the Layers: Interpretation of Neural Networks for Natural Language Processing</result>
  <result author="Jarmila Panevová">Subcategorization of Adverbials  (The Case of Temporal Meanings)</result>
  <result author="Jan Hajič">Prague Dependency Treebank - Consolidated 1.0 (PDT-C 1.0)</result>
  <result author="Markéta Lopatková">VALLEX 4.0</result>
  <result author="Rudolf Rosa">Science Café rozhovor: S Rudolfem Rosou o umělé inteligenci a projektu THEaiTRE</result>
  <result author="Veronika Kolářová">Vztah afirmativní a negované formy adjektiv a substantiv z hlediska jejich valence</result>
  <result author="Zdeňka Urešová">PDT-Vallex: Valenční slovník češtiny propojený se korpusy 4.0</result>
  <result author="Eva Hajičová">Několik poznámek ke slovosledu a aktuálnímu členění ve světle anglicko-českého paralelního korpusu</result>
  <result author="Rudolf Rosa">Technická zpráva o vývoji projektu THEaiTRE v roce 2020</result>
  <result author="Pavel Straňák">LINDAT/CLARIAH-CZ: oborový repozitář nejen pro jazyková data</result>
  <result author="Silvie Cinková">EngVallex - English Valency Lexicon 2.0</result>
  <result author="Rudolf Rosa">THEaiTRobot 1.0</result>
</results>
